[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
> with Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D the fun will never end È
D It's Adventure Time È
JAKE:
[ grunting ]
[ sighs ]
Hey, man.
[ chuckling ]
[ video game beeping ]
What's so funny?
Oh, you know, just taking
this garbage bag of butter [grunts]
into the house.
[ chuckling ]
Dude, that's not
that funny.
Agh!
- [ laughs ]
Aw! Butter-pranked!
| can't believe
| didn't see that coming!
Heh!
Yeah, I'm a genius.
You have offended my honor, sir,
and in so doing, you have
awoken the pranking demon
that sleeps in my pits!
The demon is coming for you, mortal.
It is going to prank you so hard!
Whatever.
I'm gonna take a day-long nap.
[ yawns ]
That's right, suckal!
Go nap it up!
For when you awake, the pranking
demon will be upon youl!
Aw, man!
Nothing's better than throwing
a big bag of butter at someone!
[ grunts ]
Gotta think!
What's... a better prank... than butter?
Answer me, book.
What's better than butter?
A unicorn...
a treasure hunter...
a battleship...
a pie...
a young girl in lo--
Wait!
Book, rewind!
That's it!
I'll throw never-ending pies
at Jake's face forever!
[ laughs evilly ]
2 I'm gonna build me
a pie-throwing robot J
2 that throws never-ending
pi-i-i-es È
> on Jake's ugly fa-a-a-ce JÈ
D and he won't know
what hit him
J 'cause the pies are
ne-ne-ne-never...
ne-ne-ne-never-ending J
It's never-ending-pie-throwing
time!
Come on, dude!
Turn on!
Why isn't it working?!
[ breathing heavily ]
I'll never make a prank
better than Jake's garbage bag
full of butter.
[ thunder crashes ]
ROBOT:
Ouch!
Holy stuff!
It talked!
Wow cow chow!
Greetings, Creator.
Oh, whoa! Hey, man!
My name is NEPTR, which stands for
"never-ending-pie-throwing robot."
Oh, perfect.
You're exactly the kind of robot
| was trying to make.
Creator, | am eager to commence
the creation and propulsion of pies forever.
But my pie-hucking appendage is...
[ grunts ]
malfunctioning.
And my oven lamp is cold.
And my tank treads do not roll!
They only do skids!
Why, Creator?
-[gasps ]
Does it please you
to watch me struggle?
NEPTR, don't say stuff like that.
Look, | know we just met,
and you're probably going through
a lot of personal stuff right now,
but | really like you, NEPTR.
And I'm not gonna rest
until you're working properly
and throwing hot pie
at my best friend's face.
Together, we're going
to prank the poots out of Jake.
Ha ha. I'll always love you, Creator.
| know you will, NEPTR.
Now, all we need is more lightning power
SO you can be operating at full capacity.
And [ think | know just the dumb-hole
who we can get some from.
NEPTR:
Ooh!
What beautiful piles of sugar!
[ chuckles ]
No, NEPTR.
We call that "snow."
Sno-0-0-w?
Agh!
[ squeaking ]
Did y'all smack me into that
mountain on purpose?
ALL:
Yeah!
Take note, NEPTR --
these guys are grade-A pranksters.
You guys hang out in case
we need a daring escape.
Yeah, sure.
Daring escape, yeah.
Absolutely.
We got your back.
| got his wallet.
[ laughter ]
Just got to sneak around
until we find his lightning-bolt stash.
But, Creator, is not breaking
and entering wrong?
No, we're pranking and entering,
which is awesome.
NEPTR:
Sneaking...
We're sneaking.
Shush, NEPTR!
- Sneaking...
- Shh!
Sneaking...
NEPTR, you're gonna get us caught!
- Sneaking!
- Is that you, honey?
How was your day at work?
[ high-pitched ]
Terrible!
How could | possibly stand to be apart
from you, the Ice King?
[ normal voice ]
You see, Gunter,
that's how it would go
if | actually had a wife.
- Wenk!
- Game timel!
Kill the frog! Kill the frog!
Ah, come on!
Oh, he's right in front of you!
Lower!
[ grunts ]
Stupid lady! Kill it!
Creator, if we get caught,
| want you to know
that | will
always love you.
Shh!
You already told me that.
And we're not getting caught.
We're gonna get you working
SO we can prank Jake.
He could wake up from his nap
at any second!
[ snoring ]
I might wake up at any moment!
Nah, I'm still asleep.
Oh, no!
That frog is casting magic missiles on my babe!
[ grunts ]
Quickly, while he's distracted.
Oh, come on!
Get out of the--
[ grunts ]
Move!
Wenk!
Bah!
This game cheats anyway!
Huh?!
Look what you did, Gunter!
[ wenking ]
We're home-free, NEPTR.
What are you on about?
[ wenking ]
You're starting to infuriate me.
Wenk! Wenk!
It's almost like
you're trying to alert me,
warn me about --
| don't know --
an intruder or something.
Perhaps he's lurking in this very room,
just outside my field of vision.
- [ wenking ]
- Well, knock it off!
What do we do, Creator?
We're gonna prank him,
NEPTR -- hard-core.
Ah.
[ whistles ]
You're looking kind of fat, Gunter.
Look at these arms --
fat, fat, fat.
Daddy's little fatty.
Oh, you'll never get a prom date
with all that tub on your face, you know.
Oh! Cold!
Blast these melty ceilings!
[ laughs ]
Creator, you have shown me
the joys of pranking.
| cannot wait to throw pies
infinitely at Jake's face.
[ grunts ]
The ceiling really /s melty.
Whoal!
- Wenk! Wenk!
What was that?
Aaaaaaah!
[ grunting ]
BOTH:
Alarm! Alarm! Alarm! Alarm!
Figs!
- Alarm! Alarm!
- Huh? Intruder!
Maybe a beautiful princess, like in my poems.
Whoa!
We got to find that lightning
as fast as --
Creator! Lightning!
It's a lightning-shaped door!
And we're gonna smash right into it!
Hold on, NEPTR.
| got a plan.
Whoa!
That was a great plan.
Nah, that wasn't my plan.
We got lucky.
Are those my tickets
to the gun show, Creator?
FINN:
Mm-hmm.
You're gonna be fully functional,
just like | promised.
[ rumbling ]
Whoa, ice-o-pede!
Ohh!
Finn?!
Ugh!
Why can't you ever be a princess?!
Ice-0-pede, attack!
Ice-0-pede, no! Aah!
Let's grab some lightning
and get out of here!
[ cackles ]
Finish him off, my semi-loyal pet!
Wah! Aah!
Look -- an innocent bystander!
Zap!
- NEPTR, n-0-0-0-0-0-0!
[ screaming ]
N-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0!
Oh, yeah -- that's what
we wanted to happen.
NEPTR is fully functional!
Yay!
Ha ha ha!
NEPTR! Yeah!
Crush him!
Crush him like you crushed me/
Creator?
NEPTR, the pies! Pies!
Oh, right.
[ treads screech ]
Aw, come on!
What was in those pies?
Just boysenberries.
[ chuckles ]
And also poison.
[ chuckles evilly ]
[ thinking ]
NEPTR is acting different.
ALL:
Quick, Finn! Jump!
[ grunts ]
WELL
- [ laughter ]
[ chuckles ]
You guys got me.
Something about
that robot | tried to Kill
fills me with deep longing.
Thanks, guys.
Your blood oath is fulfilled.
ALL:
Yay! To the mesosphere!
Finally, we can die!
| am troubled, Creator --
troubled by a sudden urge
to collect princesses.
NEPTR, that's a heavy
unsettling thing to say.
But pull yourself together!
We're about to prank Jake!
Uh-huh. Sure.
One...
two...
Three!
- Run, NEPTR!
- Ooooh!
Hah! Hah! Hah!
- Zap!
- Aw, man.
I've come to take
my son.
- Yourson?!
- Come to pappy, son.
| won't attack you,
unless provoked.
He's not your son!
If anything, he's my son!
It was my power that activated
his full potential.
Bzzz!
Ooh!
When you were struck with my lightning,
you also became infused
with my private particles.
He wants to be with me, Finn!
No way! NEPTR wants
to help me prank Jake!
| am torn.
| am processing a love for both
princesses and pranking.
Don't worry, son.
I'll show you the life you deserve.
[ wind whistles ]
No! NEPTR!
Wh-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0al!
Yes!
Now that we've entered
my imagination zone,
allow me to
tantalize you with this/
[ snaps fingers |
Princesses!
As my son,
you will carry on the tradition
of capturing ladies.
Tell me more, pappy.
No, NEPTR!
| want a son who
can do better than |,
one who can succeed where |....
have failed.
You can mate with robot princesses!
Can | still prank
with Finn after?
No!
I'll show you what will happen
if you hang out with Finn!
[ both farting ]
BOTH:
Yeah! Pootin' on NEPTR to the max!
Ha ha.
Yeah, | love Finn's pranks!
N-0-0-0-0-0-0!
I'm through
playing around, son.
Who do you choose?!
Come on, NEPTR.
Choose me, buddy.
Choose pranks.
uh, | choose...
Ice King!
What?!
You've got to be flippin' kidding me!
He made his choice.
Get over it, crybaby.
I'm not finished.
| choose Ice King to prank --
hard-core!
What?!
Agh! My face!
[ both laugh ]
| birthed you,
and | can unbirth you!
- Never!
- Unh!
Sleep well, pappy,
in your imagination zone
full of beautiful princesses.
You want to prank Jake?
It's why | was created.
[ laughs ]
Okay, let's g-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0!
Jake! Wake up!
JAKE:
Ah, hey, du-- Aah!
[ thudding ]
Sun is going down.
Shall we capture princesses now, Pappy?
No, let's just stay here a little longer, son.
| love you forever, pappy.
È Come along with me È
2 and the butterflies and bees È
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree È