[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
FINN:
Ha ha! Time to protect the sun.
JAKE:
Ha ha, yeah.
He knows how
to get things started.
Fire pit number 1.
Easy-peasy, livin' greasy.
You wonder why
they even put it there.
It's probably
a computel gleech.
[ laughs ]
Now comes some real trouble.
It's Bouncy Bee.
He's gonna get
that sun, man.
FINN:
Ha ha, please.
Bleep.
- Ha ha!
| had my eyes closed on
that one.
JAKE:
Yeah, that was cool.
Oh, oh, you missed
a coin, dude. Go back.
lain'tin it
for the money, man.
I'm in it to crush
the enemies of the sun,
like this sloppy butt
right here.
JAKE:
Hunny bunny.
FINN:
I'm like, "hunny bunny, don't you ever learn?
I've always got the bombuh."
[ beeping ]
JAKE:
Man, you are hot tonight.
Think you can do it
this time?
Can you beat Sleepy Sam?
Oh, | very can.
JAKE:
Remember, use a combo move.
Okay, here it goes.
BOTH:
Up, down, left, left,
right, right, down.
Spin, down, up, left.
Faster, dude.
Right, left, down.
Ohh! Every time!
Beemo, this game is the worst.
If we were really
inside that game,
man, we would crush
Sleepy Sam, breezily...
with my mitts.
Oh, no.
It's much more dangerous
than you think.
Whoa, whoa, wait!
Beemo, is there a way for us
to get in the game for real?
Yes, of course, Jake.
If | push this button...
If /push this button,
you will both be dangerously transported
into my main-brain-game-frame,
where it is very dangerous.
Oh, man! Oh, Beemo!
You got to let us
in that game.
No. It's a far-too-dangerous
incredible adventure for you.
That's final.
Oh. Okay, Beemo.
Well, time for bed.
Finn?
Time for bed,
right, Jake?
Oh, right.
[ chuckles ]
Good night, Beemo.
Time for bed.
[ laughs evilly ]
[ groans ]
[ gasps ]
[ screams ]
- Wow!
- Whoa!
Whoa!
We're in the game!
Look, there's the sunshine
we got to protect.
And there's the hole we're
supposed to go down.
And there's you...
doing whatever you're doing.
I'm looking at my bits.
My leg is math!
Mm, that sunshine feels good.
Feels good all over.
No wonder all
the monsters in this game
want to get
their grubby mitts on it.
Let's go kick their digital bootays!
Doot-doot.
Doot-doot-doot.
Beep-boop.
È We are in
the computer world È
È We're computer boys, not
computer girls JÈ
2 Inagame, | can be
who | virtually am )
> | can walk and sing J
2 | can kill Silly Sam È
[ sniffs ]
Hey, what stinks?
Smells like...
Pit!
Looks a mite bigger
inside the game.
Jumping over this pit
is easy, remember?
We can do this backwards
with our eyes closed.
Aah! I'm burning!
Jake!
JAKE:
[ chuckles ] What, man?
Wha?!
Jake, what the shank?
Check it out --
extra lives.
You still have two left.
[ laughs ]
Aah-hal
Ow! It burns!
Ow! Aah-ha!
Jake!
> Do, do-do-do )
Dude, what if losing
all your lives in here
makes you die in real life?
Or worse?
That makes me just want
to sit here and feel bad.
No way, man.
We're gonna cross that hole
with real-world grit.
Come on!
Faster, Jake.
Get ready to stretch it.
Watch out, Jake!
Wow!
Whew!
That was pretty intense, dude.
We're pretty intense dudes.
Yeah!
[ buzzing ]
What's that sound?
It sounds like...
BOTH:
Bouncy Bee!
Whoa!
Hyah! Ho!
You ready to flippinÕ
this guy up, Jake?
Easy peasy, livin' greasy.
[ screaming ]
[ beeps ]
No!
[ gasps ]
Finn's dead.
Finn, no.
Why?
[ breathing deeply ]
No!!
Curse this false virtual world.
[ grunts ]
Oh, Finn.
Yo, what up?
Oh, Finn!
You're alive.
Yeah, | got extra
lives, man.
Oh, my gosh.
Let's never die again.
There's nothing more precious
than a life.
Ooh, dude, look -- coins.
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Hee, hee, hee.
Ooh!
Oh, man, dude,
these coins are thick.
Let's take them back
to the real world.
We'll be filthy,
stinking rich.
[ both laugh ]
[ growling ]
Whoa!
BOTH:
Hunny Bunny!
N-0-0-0!
Time to use the bombuh.
Come to me, bombuh.
Bombuh!
Oh, bombuh,
| can't select you
without my controller.
[ growls ]
Let's get out of here, Finn.
Man, we never run away
from Hunny Bunny.
[ growls ]
Aah!
Fire pit, Bouncy Bee,
Hunny Bunny --
they're supposed
to be the easy parts.
They're all hard as butts.
Sleepy Sam is gonna be
the ultimate butt-kicker.
Look, Finn, the most
important thing to remember
is that | still have
one giant coin.
Man, get ahold of your brains.
We need to stay alert for
Sleepy Sam.
Hey, that's him
right there.
Get down.
What's he doing?
He's probably trying
to psyche me out.
[ beep ]
[ grunts ]
I'm gonna break you, Sam.
When I'm done,
they'll call you, uh...
Stinky Sam...
stupid frog.
[ slurps ]
[ shrieks ]
Aah!
[ beep ]
Ugh!
My -- my mitts didn't --
didn't work.
Come on,
help me punch him.
Okay!
Roarl
[ beeping ]
[ shrieks ]
Let's get out of here, man!
We're gonna die!
[ growls ]
[ beep ]
[ buzzing ]
| can see the lights.
We're almost there!
Ugh!
Oh, no, man.
It's the edge of the screen.
We're trapped, and they'll be
here any second.
Wait, dude. The bombuh.
We can't get the bombuh.
Wait, dude.
Hmm.
- Jake? Jake?
What if I...
FINN:
That's not how it works.
[ zapping ]
Error, error, error.
Jake, let go of that.
But we need the bombuh.
[ straining ]
Whoops.
[ screams ]
Finn!
Huh?
[ gasping ]
Oh, holy cow!
That was nuts, man!
Yeah, man.
And | got my coin.
What?! A penny?!
[ groans ]
Beemo! Oh, no!
Are you all right, buddy?
[ gasps ]
You -- you have to -- y-you --
Oh, no!
Too late! Run!
[ both scream ]
[ growls ]
Aah!
No. No. No.
Don't kill us.
We don't have extra lives.
No!
Whoa, wait.
Hold up, guys.
Check it out.
Sunshine.
Oh, boy.
That feels good.
All right.
See you later, Sam.
You mean that's it?
You're not gonna Kill us?
[ chuckles ]
No, of course not.
The game's over. We won.
All we wanted was
the sunshine...
and to kill that computer
that's been imprisoning us
for so many years.
What?
Help! Oh, no!
BOTH:
Beemo!
Oh, sure, he's dangerous.
If he hits his button again,
back we go.
Beemo, quick!
Hit your button!
I-I can't, Finn.
I'm stuck.
You want him
to hit his button?!
What's wrong with you?!
We'll save you, Beemo.
Finn, go!
They're too strong.
Use the combo move, Finn.
The combo move!
Combo move?
That never works.
Listen, you got this, man.
| know you --
| know you can do it, buddy.
You got this!
Okay, okay.
You got this, Finn.
For your friends.
[ inhales deeply ]
Up, down, left, left, right,
right, down, spin, down, up,
left, right, left, down, spin,
up, down, jump!
[ distorted ]
Aah!
[ panting ]
Whoa.
- Whoo-hoo!
You did it, Finn!
| knew you had the stuff.
Right, Beemo?
Ohh!
[ groans ]
- Oh, crud.
- Beemo!
I'm sorry, buddy.
Finn, | told you about
the danger, and now look --
you fricasseed my stuff
and broke our house all up.
| know, | know.
| was double-butt, for real.
But, man, now that we know
what to expect,
next time will be way
more fun.
Yeah, yeah!
How about it, Beemo?
You in?
Up, down...
Hey, don't do the combo
move on us.
W-We were only joking.
Beemo!
Stop messing around.
...left, down...
È Come along with me È
2 and the butterflies and bees È
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree...
FINN:
This party is so crazy!