[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog and Finn the Human )
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
You want some more
eggs, Beemo?
Yes, please.
How about you, Finny?
Need a refill?
I'm pretty full, man,
but let me see if | can...
rearrange.
Nope. Can't do it.
| don't know if stomachs
work like that, dude.
Sometimes it helps.
Can't argue with that.
Eee, eee! Ahh.
Ahh.
Ahhh.
[ cellphone rings ]
Ohh.
Hello.
Lady, it's gonna be fine.
Mm-hmm.
All right, | love you, too.
Bye.
Lady Rainicorn again?
Yeah, man.
She's worried
about introducing me
to her parents
at lunch today.
She thinks they're gonna
"freak out."
Um... maybe give her parents
some treasure?
No way!
That's our treasure!
Wait.
I've got it, dude!
I'll invite them over early,
"smoove" them over using
my personality,
and we'll all be best friends
before Lady gets here
so she doesn't have
to feel nervous.
It's perfect.
I'll just send them
a quick prism-gram.
Mm-hmm.
What's it say?
Hold on.
Still converting the light waves
into brain waves.
A-EER
They're into it, dude!
Sweet!
Let's go powder our noses!
Why's Lady so nervous, anyway?
Well, she didn't really say,
but it might have
something to do
with the rainicorn/dog wars.
There were wars between
rainicorns and dogs?
Horrifying wars.
For thousands of years,
rainicorns battled dogs
over territory
in the crystal dimension.
But Lady and | are cool.
Dude! Her parents are probably
all full of dog hatred
from the war times!
They're gonna see
you're a dog
and forbid Lady from ever
hanging out with you again!
[ voice breaking ]
Nah. That could never happen.
You didn't think this
through enough.
It could happen!
WEEELL
I'm a moron!
Don't worry.
I've got a plan that's gonna
solve this biz.
Homeys help homeys.
Always.
I'm ready to hear
your plan, homey.
[ whispering ]
- Ketchup!
- Mustard!
BOTH:
Red and yellow!
> Lady's parents,
| say hello >
2 I'm the fellow
for your daughter )
> Please forget
the wartime slaughter
È Home improvement
decorations )
È Help me impress
her relations È
FINN:
È Sugar bears and rainbow jelly J
> Spread those colors on my belly )
2 On the floor and up the log È
> Please don't notice I'm a dog )
Ha ha! Yeah!
This plan is perfect.
You know, | thought
painting ourselves rainbow color
using condiments and stuff
from the fridge
so we could pretend
to be rainicorns
was a good idea
when you pitched it to me
five minutes ago,
but now I'm not so
sure, man.
Come on.
Trust me, homey!
No, no, no.
New plan.
First, we're gonna clean this
place up, and then --
[ doorbell buzzing ]
JAKE: [ gasps ]
WOMAN: Jake?
Aah!
Let's hide
and burn the house down!
[ buzzing continues ]
Hello?
Annyong.
Haseyo.
Jake, is that you?
- Uh-huh.
- Are you going to let us in?
- Yeah.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aah! | can explain!
| can explain!
Ohh!
He's so handsome!
Oh, Bob!
Our daughter's finally found
a handsome rainicorn to love.
You think
I'm a rainicorn?
| think we could spot a member
of our own species, Jake.
We're not blind.
Well, we are a little blind.
Yes, | guess
we are a little blind.
Uh... well, hey,
come on in!
It's awesome to finally
meet you both.
Your house is very colorful.
| like that.
Ha!
The plan is working, homey.
Jake, what is that thing
that's talking?
Uh... that's, um...
I'm Jake's rainicorn
roommate.
Everyone do the traditional
rainicorn rain dance.
2 [ singing gibberish ] È
Jake, please ask
your goblin butler
to stop insulting my heritage.
Uh... yes!
Get out of here, goblin!
Go fetch us
some rainicorn snacks!
- But --
- Come on, homey. Help me.
Ha!
You got it, homey.
Uh, please,
c-come upstairs.
My goblin will bring us snacks
in a moment.
Thank you, Jake.
I'm glad...
the wife and | made the trip
from the Crystal dimension.
Yes, we're eager
to know more
about the studly
young rainicorn
that's dating our daughter.
- Ethel.
Well, ask me whatever
you like, Ethel, Bob.
| am a little curious about
your goblin.
He looks a little odd.
Well, he's actually a human.
Oh, Bob! Our future son-in-law
must be filthy rich
to afford a human butler!
Shh.
Thank you, Jake, for being
interested in our daughter.
Uh... no problem, Bob.
Oh! Oh!
Let's play some traditional
rainicorn games!
Jake, do you know
Kabaladapawumba-pbht!
Uh...
S-Say it again?
Kabaladapawumba-pbht!
Oh!
[ laughing ]
Kabladapuwama-pbht!
| thought you said
Kobloderagut-pbht!
[ chuckles ]
But, aw, man, | love getting
down and dirty
with some
Klabladapuwama-pbht!
Ha! You all should go first, though.
Mm. Bold move letting your
opponent move first, Jake.
| respect that.
Very well.
Kabaladapawumba-pbht!
Oh, Bob!
Ha ha!
Your turn, Jake!
FINN:
Snacks! Get your snacks!
Finn!
Dude, | have
to show Lady's parents
that | have rainbow powers!
| need homey help.
Hmm. | got a plan, broham.
Just stretch your horn at me,
and I'll take care
of the rest.
- You're the best, homey.
- Homeys help homeys.
Ha ha!
[ inhales deeply ]
Kabladapuwama-pbht!
[ gasps ]
Very unusual color palette, Jake.
Yes. Subtle.
Whoo! Oh, yeah!
[ breathing heavily ]
Finn?
How about we play some more
traditional rainicorn games?
I, uh...
oh, um...
let's do it!
BOTH:
Let the games begin!
[ upbeat music plays ]
I'm sorry!
[ both laugh ]
JAKE:
Yo, my bad! I'll get him!
[ panting ]
Ooh. Hey, man.
How's it going?
It's going crud cow!
| know, | know.
I'm sorry.
But they really like me.
Your plan is working perfectly!
Being poked in the buns
and laughed at
was not in my plan!
Not in the plan!
Look, Finn, you know
| got your back "forevah,"
but right now, you're the only
one who can help me.
Come on, homey.
Homeys help homeys.
[ both laugh ]
Hey, guys! You ready to get
this game going again?
Oh, no.
We're pooped.
Yeah, we're about ready to
break out our picnic basket
and dig in.
Whoa, no.
You're my guests.
Let me take care of you.
Homey, help me cook something, please.
Okay.
Thanks, Finn.
Don't worry about a thing.
Finn'll make a great lunch.
He's a little raw,
but he's got great taste.
What? Wow!
So wealthy and so generous!
Oh, | was hoping,
but | was afraid to ask.
Whoa.
| can't wait.
- Oh, | can't wait.
What? Whoal!
Aah!
NELGY
| think they want to eat me!
Of course we do!
Jake said you'd make
a great lunch.
Jake, come on!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh, man! Oh, man! Oh, man!
Aaah!
Knock it off, Bob!
Don't you touch him!
JAKE:
Wait! Come on! Stop it, guys!
Come on, y'all!
| said stop!
REEEEEER]
Now, that's enough!
Nobody's eating Finn!
He's not my butler,
and he's not food!
Finn is my friend!
[ both gasp ]
I'm sorry | let the lies
get so far out of hand.
| just got so scared
of losing Lady.
But if they hate me,
so be it.
No more lies.
[ gasps ]
You're a dog?
Yeah, | just...
Oh, look.
I'm sorry about everything.
| was --
BOB:
Yay! Hey, hey! Hooray!
> Today is a happy day JÈ
2 Hip, hip, hooray È
> Today is the day )
> This dude is a super guy È
È Oh, me, oh, my
A super guy )
È We are the lucky ones È
> Son of a gun,
the lucky ones È
È The lucky, lucky ones )
Uh, uh...
[ gasps ]
Lady?
[ speaking Korean ]
What did she say?
She says she was worried that
they'd freak out...
Ôcause her parents are
bananas for dogs!
J.J. Flip!
What the zip?
JAKE:
Yeah.
She says a dog saved her dad
in the war.
Wow!
That's flippin' awesome.
[ all chomping ]
Finn.
Wha?
Listen, I just want you
to know
how sorry we are about
trying to eat you.
It's just we thought
we'd never get another chance.
We thought humans
were extinct.
Oh.
So this isn't human?
Oh, no.
This is soy people.
- Oh.
- Mmm!
I've never tasted
real human before,
but they say you can't
even tell the difference.
[ squish! ]
Ew. Soy?
[ chomping ]
Finn, you're delicious!
[ all chomping ]
Oh, man!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È