[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ both laughing ]
Don't forget
LSP's diet cola.
| won't.
| really do love
"Finn and Jake Movie Club."
Okay, everybody.
Apple juice for Tree Trunks...
diet soda for LSP...
Eh...
What did you order, PB?
Oh,
| brought my own.
[ pop! ]
Huh.
Iced lattŽ for M'lady.
Tomato juice
for Marceline.
MARCELINE:
Thanks, Finn.
Hot cocoa for Beemo.
This does compute.
And, finally, a thimble
of milk for Shelby,
the worm who lives
in Jake's viola.
You can just
call me "Shelby."
Jake?
We're so excited that you
could be here tonight for
"Finn and Jake's
Movie Club's"
feature presentation...
BOTH:
"Heat Signature 3."
Oh, with the submarine?
- Sounds great.
- [ speaking Korean ]
Get on with it!
[ whirring ]
[ beep!]
Princess Bubblegum's
in my seat.
We decided last time
no reserved seating --
First come, first served.
[ growls ]
[ slurps ]
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
What's that?
Just stuff that comes at the
beginning of the movies.
Yeah, it's on all
the movies we dig up.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
| don't know.
It seems pretty important, Finn.
All right.
Let's take a look.
Pause, Beemo.
BOTH:
"Warning -- federal law provides severe and criminal
penalties for
the unauthorized
exhibition of
copyrighted motion pictures."
All right, well, goodbye!
Sorry we had to cancel.
We've been showing
these films unauthorized!
But these movies are before
the Great Mushroom War.
We should still respect
authority, Mang.
[ indistinct shouting ]
Yeah?
Are we meeting next week
to watch a movie?
Uh...
Uh, yeah, maybe.
I-I think so.
Finn, don't
cancel movie club!
I've literally been having
the time of my life.
[ sighs ]
[ speaking Korean ]
Calm down, y'all.
We're gonna have
"Finn and Jake Movie Club"
next week for sure.
Jake and | just have to find
a movie without that warning.
Good! Okay.
All right, well,
we'll see you next time!
Bye-bye!
Dude, we've never found a
movie without that warning.
We're not gonna find a movie, Jake.
[ zap!]
Well, what are we gonna do?
[ gasps ]
We're gonna make one!
Wow-p!
BOTH:
Movie filming time!
Okay, Beemo.
Turn to your right
and start filming.
Start to truck in.
Keep going.
Keep trucking in, Beemo.
Huh?
That was awesome, Beemo!
Yeah. Fantastic. Super.
Don't lose her, Beemo.
Front shot! Front shot!
Film the clouds!
Don't forget the little one!
[ camera shutter clicking,
whirring ]
Beemo!
Beemo,
you're gonna miss it!
Over there,
to your right!
[ laughs ]
Oh, we're gonna miss it!
Hurry, Beemo!
Don't lose it!
Oh, looks like
it's gonna fall!
Follow it!
Look over there --
across the river!
Beemo, forget about the coin!
Film that over there!
FINN:
Zoom in.
[ camera whirs ]
Weird.
Let's get some more footage.
[ whistling ]
Whee!
[ laughs ]
[ clapping ]
Nom! Nom! Nom! Nom!
[ whack! ]
Like that?
BOTH:
Yeah! Perfect!
Are y-you sure?
BOTH:
Yeah! Looks great!
Wait, what about this?
BOTH:
That's even better!
Uh...
What do you think?
| don't get it.
It's just a bunch
of random junk.
Yeah,
I'm not engaged.
| need to see
something that
reflects life as it is,
but, you know,
entertaining.
Yeah,
like a romantic comedy.
Exactly --
an action adventure.
Wait,
that's not what | said.
Let's get to filming!
FINN:
Okay, Slime Princess!
In this scene, you're gonna
leap over to that vine...
swing over the crocodiles...
do a triple flip with a
full twist, and land clean!
Don't fall in the water,
or you'll get eaten alive!
Action!
[ growls ]
[ smooching ]
No!
No smooching!
Cutl!
JAKE:
| thought it was great.
No, we can't use any of it.
| think we should
use all of it.
No, not all.
We should throw
away the parts
where Slime Princess
was smooching.
That was dumb.
What?!
Du-u-u-u-u-u-u-mbah!
Okay, you're having a picnic.
You're in love,
but you can't admit it.
So you're having a
playful food fight.
And action!
[ splat! ]
Why did you do that?!
JAKE:
Cut, cut, cut!
[ clank! ]
Cutl!
That was not what | wanted!
FINN:
That was awesome!
We need to shoot
more stuff like that.
[ sighs ]
What's next?
FINN:
Okay, PB.
Move back a little.
Stop!
Finn?
- FINN: Yeah?
BUBBLEGUM:
How does this work?
Um...
Jake's gonna get
the frog to hop
toward him,
and when he does,
you're gonna
run alongside the chariot,
and it's gonna look like
you're driving it.
Okay.
Hey, Finn.
Yeah?
How about when the
chariot takes off,
she says something like,
"Mm, check, please!"
What?!
No, that's terrible.
And...action!
[ croaks ]
[ whack! crash! ]
Check, please?
Aw, Jake!
You -- you brought
the fly in too close!
I'm sorry.
Well, help me catch him.
[ croaking ]
Well, | thought it was funny.
This isn't a comedy!
Not the way
you're shooting it.
FINN:
Look, just help me catch this guy.
JAKE:
All right, but after this, we do my part.
Okay, everyone,
it's been a long day.
Lot of...
[ chuckles ]
...a lot of running around,
chasing frogs.
[ chuckles ]
But we are making a movie, and
this is the big wedding scene.
Mr. Cupcake, you're playing
Todd Johnson.
Yes.
And, Lady, you confess
that you never loved
Todd Johnson
and that you were
just trying to
win a bet with
your snooty
socialite friends.
[ speaking Korean ]
And then you both realize
you do love each other,
and you both say,
III dO_"
And then, Shelby,
you say...
"Check, please!"
[ chuckles ]
Yeah.
Don't forget to look right in
the camera and slap your cheeks
like this...
[ pop! ]
And...
One, two, three, action!
Do you, Todd Johnson,
take this Rainicorn
to be your lawfully
married wife?
Oh.
[ giggles ]
[ creak! ]
[ stretch! stretch! ]
Lady!
Cutl!
Cut, cut, cut!
| didn't tell
you to flex out!
[ speaking Korean ]
No!
| don't like the way
he's flexing at you!
| don't hear
her complaining.
Why, you --
[ screams ]
Check, please!
How much longer till
you finish editing, Beemo?
About 20 hours.
20 hours?!
Yeah.
You guys shot a lot of footage...
About 20 hours.
Jake, let's talk
about our movie.
Okay.
| think we shot a
lot of great stuff...
Uh-huh.
...but I'm thinking
only half of it is usable.
Me too.
Really?!
Yeah,
| was just thinking that.
That's great!
| know!
You actually agree it's
an action-adventure!
Yep, it -- wait!
No!
What?!
Romantic comedy!
What do you mean,
"What?!"
Who's right, Beemo?
Yeah!
Me or Finn?!
[ beeping ]
We'll ask him
when he wakes up.
Why wait?
"Dear Beemo...
please use only the best
footage when cutting the movie.
Love, Jake."
"And Finn."
See you at the
movie club, then!
Oh, I'll be there!
As will [.
As will |
...as well.
[ beeping ]
[ indistinct conversations |
Yes. Oh, yes.
Ugh! | can't wait! Oh!
| can't wait!
[ chuckles ]
All right.
Thanks again, everyone,
for coming to...
È Movie Night! È
| hope y'all are in
the mood to laugh!
| hope y'all are ready to
be on the edge of your seats
for tonight's
action-adventure film!
It's, uh, more of a romantic
comedy, right, Beemo?
Eeeee.
Well, | guess we'll see!
Yeah, | guess we will!
Start the movie, Beemo!
[ applause ]
[ both scoff ]
It's a little awkward.
[ sighs ]
[ beam!]
[ crowd gasps ]
[ zapping ]
Ooh!
Ahh!
[ warble! ]
[ music plays ]
Oh, my gosh!
> Finn, why are you
fighting with your friend?
> Jake, you know this
can't be the end È
È Romance or action
does not matter JÈ
2 Hurting your friend
will make you sadder )
È Guys, you know you're
much more than this )
2 You two, please stop,
or you'll undo >
JÈ All that you've
been through È
> Ooh È
2 Just hug,
and it's agreed )
D Your love
will not delete È
[ cheers and applause ]
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Beemo's right.
Fighting over this
movie junk is dumb.
I'm sorry, man.
Me too, dude.
Oh, my gosh, you guys.
| can't wait till
next week's movie club!
Check, please.
[ laughter and applause ]
That's a good one, Beemo!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È