[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog and Finn the Human )
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ up-tempo electronic music plays ]
Beemo, turn the music down.
Beemo, turn it down!
[ volume increases ]
[ groans ]
Come on, Beemo!
You're messing up my game!
Hey, dude, can | borrow
that paper?
Mm-hmm.
[ whistles ]
Bad computer! No! No!
Now go sit in the corner
and think about your life.
[ crash! ]
[ roars ]
BOTH:
Snail attack!
Aaaaaah!
Oofl
[ crying ]
[ both coughing, gagging ]
Oh, sick! Ugh!
Dude, how do you fight
a snail?!
Hold on! | got this!
[ grunts ]
Don't make me use this, man!
Salt?!
But | heard you guys
were heroes.
We are heroes.
We thought you were
trying to attack us.
Why'd you break in here
all mad,
squirting that juice
all over us?
It's not mad juice.
It's sad juice.
My name's Snorlock,
and I'm sa-a-a-a-d!
[ sobbing ]
Stop squirting slime!
Just tell us what's wrong!
| need a girlfriend.
| have no one to love.
Jake, hero huddle.
What do you think?
| think our house is
all jacked up.
Yeah, but he's just an innocent
goober looking for love.
Yeah.
Okay, let's help him.
But he's gotta lay off
the house.
Right!
All right, man. We'll help you
hook up as long as you --
Yay!
BOTH:
Whoa!
[ cre-e-e-e-ak! ]
Aaah!
Lay off the house, man!
[ sadly ]
You guys won't help me?
[ whimpers ]
All right! All right!
We'll help you, dude!
Just put our house back!
Okay! Right after | get
a girlfriend.
Aw!
All right, you big crazy.
It's a deal.
[ giggles ]
Jake, what time is it?
| don't know, but
you're probably gonna say...
BOTH:
Lady time!
[ wolf whistle ]
Okay, Snorlock,
if you want a lady,
you have to be yourself.
How do | be myself?
Uh, how does he be
himself, Jake?
Just do whatever you want, man,
as long as it comes
from the inside.
- Like sad juice?
- BOTH: No!
You keep that stuff
inside you, brother.
You just got to talk to 'em.
Oh. | never done that.
Finn, you see
any hot mamas?
FINN:
Um...
Bam!
Go talk to her!
Go talk
to her!
[ sighs ]
Okay.
Onh!
[inhales ]
Hello.
Mm.
You seem like
a reasonable male.
We should go to a movie sometime.
- He's got this.
- Yeah.
- Uh...
- | like old movies.
Uh, uh, uh...
Um, are you okay?
[ screaming ]
Aaaaaaaaah!
Girlfriend! Girlfriend!
BOTH:
Aaah!
SNORLOCK:
Girlfriend! Girlfriend!
Girlfriend!
Dude! Our house!
We got to do something!
Relax. | got it.
Snorlock! Hey, Snorlock.
You okay, buddy?
Went a little nuts there, guy.
You got to get that under control,
'Ôcause you're scaring ladies
and jacking up our house.
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna leave me?
Aw, who could leave you?
Come here,
you big hot mess.
Break it up, you two!
We have ladies to attend to!
Yeah, the ladies.
Talking to ladies is hard.
No, it's not.
Check it out, Snorlock.
Finn, you be the guy snail,
and I'll be...
the chick snail.
Ugh! Gross, Jake!
Come on, man.
We're just pretending.
Do it for love.
[ whimpering ]
Okay.
I'll do it for this guy.
[ gasps ]
[ clears throat ]
What's up, lady snail?
[ high-pitched voice ]
Well, I'm just sitting here
thinking about mating
with snails.
No! | can't do this, man!
| am out!
I'll mate with you.
We're just role playing, buddy.
Aww.
Here, Finn.
This time you be the chick
and I'll be the snail dude.
Hey, baby. What's up?
Uh -- wha?!
Mm-mmm!
[ sniffs ]
[ deep voice ]
Girl, you smell good.
Did you take a bath
in rainbows and cupcakes?
Say "yes"!
[ high-pitched ] Say "yes"!
[ deep voice ] Say "yes"!
Okay! Yes!
See, Snorlock?
Talking to ladies is easy.
Just act like me.
Uh...
girl, you smell good.
You can smell me?
May | smell you more?
Uh, okay.
[ sniffs ]
Cupcakes.
Uh, | have to go.
Did you take a bath?
Don't ever talk to me again.
Please don't go!
Don't go!
Aww.
Aw, it's okay, buddy.
Come here and give us a hug.
Man, | wish you guys were ladies.
Uh...
Stay focused, Snorlock.
You have any cool talents
that ladies might like?
- No.
-Um...
Hey, Finn, teach him
how to use swords.
The princesses always
love this one.
Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah!
Yaaaah! Hyah!
Do you think you can do
that, Snorlock?
| don't know.
Hmm.
Maybe you're musical.
Can you do this?
[ inhales deeply ]
[ beatboxing ]
Try doing all that.
Hmm.
[ grunts ]
[ shing! ]
[ beatboxing ]
BOTH:
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
My word, Eleanor!
What is that alluring sound?
| have no idea.
Yeah, Snorlock!
Show us that talent!
Whoo-hoo!
- Oh, my!
- What is that?
What is that wonderful sound?
Do | see swords?
Jake, these chicks look
pretty serious.
Let's just let Snorlock
do his thing.
Go to it, buddy!
[ beatboxing continues ]
ALL:
Ohh! Ooh! Ahh.
Look at him go!
Bringing in the ladies.
Uh, he's bringing in
a /ot of ladies.
Mm!
[ crashing ]
Beep!
[ crash! ]
[ both screaming ]
Snorlock! These ladies are
ruining our tree house!
Stop!
[ continues beatboxing ]
[ smooching ]
BOTH:
Whoa!
Wedge, dude!
[ grunting ]
It's no use, man.
It's stuck with snail slime.
Wha?!
[ grunting ]
Finn! Aah!
[ both grunt ]
How are we gonna get our house back?
Salt?!
Dude, I'm going in.
Wha?! Jake! No!
You'll get slimed
or grinded on!
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
Hmph!
[ gasps ]
Snorlock, I'm gonna give you
'til the count of
three, Mister!
One...
two...
three!
[ continues beatboxing ]
Fine. | didn't want to have
to do this.
[ inhales deeply ]
[ blows ]
[ beatboxing slows ]
[ beatboxing stops ]
[ sizzle! ]
Aaaaaah!
Ow! Ow!
Owwwwwww!
Oh, my gosh.
He's naked.
[ laughter ]
What? I'm naked?
But I've never had a shell.
Snorlock, you never
had a shell?
That means you're not naked.
You're a slug.
Me, a slug?
Yeah, man.
That's why you have
trouble with snail chicks.
You need s/ug chicks.
| don't know any
slug chicks.
LADY:
Actually, I-I'm not really a snail.
I'm a slug.
My shell's made
of peppermint.
[ laughs ]
[ smooching ]
That's gross!
JAKE:
| don't know why they have to make out
so close to our house.
FINN:
| don't know.
Come on.
Let's finish rebuilding it.
| got some ear plugs
you can borrow.
[ up-tempo electronic music plays ]
Where's that music coming from?
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Beemo!
Get over here and help us
rebuild the tree house.
Yeah. You live here, too!
[ volume increases ]
BOTH:
Oh, Beemo!
[ squirrrrrt! ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È