[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
> with Jake the dog
and Finn the human
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
You got that cooler, buddy?
Yep.
Good, 'cause we're
gonna need it for this...
roof party!
[ all cheering ]
Watch this, everybody.
Triple flip with chips
for the dip.
Watch this, everybody.
A cooler with stuff
for the thing.
[ chuckles ]
[ all cheering ]
Finn, you always focus
an endless amount of energy
on everything you do.
What about me?
What do | focus my energy on,
Cinnamon Bun?
Uh, Jake, you don't really
focus at all.
Huh?
| said, you don't
focus at all!
Hey, Finn, do another flip.
Hyah! Hyah!
Ha ha ha!
You're a dynamo, Finn!
Yeah, | never
slow down!
Never slow down?
Whoa, dude, can you,
like, get off of me?
Do you think your energy
could be used
to power a huge machine?
I-I guess so, man.
[ laughs ]
Hey, Jake,
your friend
is superweird, dude.
[ munching, laughs ]
| thought he was
your friend.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
It's starting, everyone -- the celestial alignment.
ALL:
Ooh!
Whoa!
Oh!
[ gasps ]
Ooh!
Mm!
[ crickets chirping ]
Jake, that party was superfun!
Man, I'm sleepy.
[ yawns ]
Then go to sleep, man.
Huh? Oh, yeah, right.
[ yawns ]
Good night, homey.
Hyah!
[ sighs ]
Good night, Hamlet.
[ snoring ]
[ grunts ]
[ rooster crows, birds chirping ]
Crang!
[ groans ]
What?
All right, all right,
you old gut.
Whoa, I'm sluggin' it today.
Wake up, Finn.
Got a busy day ahead of us.
Finn?
Hmm.
Hmmmm.
Where's Finn?
Where is Finn?
D Is he in the kitchen? )
È Does he have a pumpkin? J
JÈ Rima, tima, tin-tin JÈ
J Dooba, dooba,
dumplin' È
È Poopy, doopy, pie tin >
È Monkey watermelon )
[ both laugh ]
MAN:
Welcome, Finn.
Huh?
Untie me so | can beat you
with that sack!
[ laughs ]
[ gasps ]
You're that --
Yes, the charismatic stranger
from last night, also...
the grand master of the gnomes!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
And...
ruler of the beneathaverse!
It's pretty nice.
Hey, why don't you guys just
untie me,
and we can pretend
this whole thing didn't happen.
Oh, no.
I've been searching
all over Ooo
for the ultimate
power source --
a living dynamo, something that
never slows down.
Uh-oh.
And last night,
| finally found --
It's me.
Yes, it's you!
You will have the great honor
of powering
the upturn-over-drive!
That does what now?
It will flip over
the entire world.
Then we'll be the ones
on top, buddy.
That's bizonkers!
Yes, but the engineering is
very sound.
Huh?
Your energies
will be harnessed
by our most advanced
technology --
the cyclonic rodentarod!
Ha!
You may have captured me...
huh!
...but you can't make me run.
Ow!
Well, you can't make me run
very fast.
[ zapping ]
Ow!
Jake's on his way
to mess you guys --
Aaaah!
[ munching ]
Finn!
Finn?!
[ munching ]
Man, where is that kid?
I'm really starting to worry.
Take my sandwich, Beemo.
I'm gonna go find fi--
[ gasps ]
a dancing bug.
[ dance music plays ]
Hey, man, you're shakin' it
all wrong.
But shakin' it's all | know.
Shh.
Let me show you
how it's done.
[ music continues ]
Oh, yeah! Ha ha! Yeah!
Whoo!
Congratulations.
You fully charged
the alternator.
Now it's time to power up
the plasma ball...
with sexy, fun dancing.
No! Stop! No!
Whoa! Aah!
[ screaming ]
[ beep ]
[ dance music plays ]
[ zapping ]
[ screaming continues ]
[ beep ]
ALL:
[ chanting ] Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug!
Aah!
[ gulps ]
Whoo!
[ all cheering ]
Any more grass shakes, Simon?
All finished.
Finished, huh?
Ahh!
Finished. Finished.
Finn. Finn. Finn.
Oh, Finn!
Darn it!
My best friend's missing!
| got to get my head together,
get undistracted,
and use all of my skills
to track him down.
Smelling...
[ sniffs ]
...touching...
tasting...
looking.
[ gasps |
Little footprints.
Too small to be Finn's.
More like "a bunch of gnomes
carrying something" footprints.
[ girls laughing ]
Hey, I've got a joke.
What did the mermaid
sea -- a movie?
W-What?
Oh, I messed it up.
But it's still funny, right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No, it's not!
Y'all are horrible
at telling jokes.
Let me hit you with this.
Did you hear about the goblin
who got his left arm
and left leg cut off?
BOTH:
Um... No.
That's okay.
He's all righf now.
[ laughing ]
[ breathing heavily ]
What?
[ screams ]
Now for the final stage --
the brain machine.
No!
Yes!
This machine will suck
the energy from your thoughts
to start
our upturn-over-drive.
[ breathing heavily ]
Don't think, Finn.
Don't think anything.
Can't...let...them...win!
Hyah!
WHEE V1)
Raaa!
[ strains, shrieks ]
No more games.
No...more...
EIEIYERY
BOTH:
No!
[ explosion ]
Whoa!
NELCYY
[ both panting ]
[ both laugh ]
Jake! Whoa, man!
| didn't think | was ever gonna
see you again.
[ breathing heavily ]
I-I can't --
[ cries ]
[ laughs ]
It's working!
ALL:
[ chanting ] Jake! Jake! Jake!
Whoo! Yeah!
Ha ha ha!
[ laughs ]
Man, this party is nuts!
How'd | even get up here?
You blacked out after
laughing so hard
at your own jokes.
You were off the hook.
So we brought you
to the cloud kingdom
to party
with The Party God.
Whoa!
Who's The Party God?
| am The Party God!
Oh.
Jake, you have won my favor
for being a completely
off-the-hook party dog.
[ howls ]
[ laughs ]
And because your gut waves
please me so,
| will grant you
one wish.
What do you want
most in the world?
What do | want most?
[ laughs ]
What do | want most
in the world?
Well, | wish Finn would stop
leaving his dirty --
[ gasps ]
Finn!
| was on his trail,
and then | got distracted.
Aanh!
What's wrong with my brain?
Cinnamon Bun was right.
| can't focus on nothing!
Party God, | wish that
| could focus
on finding my friend Finn.
[ inhales sharply ]
Then your wish is my --
Wait, wait.
Is there some kind of catch?
Uh...y-y-yes.
Y-You got me.
To grant your wish,
I will have to fill you
with the energy
of a thousand partying demons.
You will become so overloaded
with party energy
that you'll demolish everything
in your path!
Must... find... Finn!
Must -- must...
party forever!
It's working!
[ laughs ]
Party!!
Partay!
Step back, everybody.
I'm gonna shake it.
Unh! Unh!
You feeling this?
Fire the shooty-gun-ray!
High five!
ALL:
Freeze!
Let's kick it!
Whoa!
Ha ha!
| bet | can lift this thing.
[ straining ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Jake?
NELGY
You defeated the gnomes.
-1 did?
- Yeah, man!
- And you're okay?
- Yeah, man, I'm fine!
Ha ha!
Then | did it.
| saved you by being
an unfocused, rowdy party dog.
Ha ha. Yeah, dog.
Ha ha ha! Yeah!
Let's go eat Cinnamon Bun.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!!