[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D Adventure time 2
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
FINN:
Jake?!
Beemo?!
Hey, man, what you doing?!
[ gasps ]
Dude!
Don't worry, Bro.
We won't tell anyone about the
"private time" you spend with
your wad of
Princess Bubblegum's hair.
You guys knew?
Finn, we're roommates,
which is why I'm gonna share my
beloved keepsake with you.
[ imitates fanfare ]
My old baby blanket.
[ electronic humming ]
Hmm-hmm!
Hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm!
Who are you?
Grr!
Hmm-hmm-hmm!
No!
Hmm-hmm!
FINN:
Come on!
[ imitates airplane engine
roaring, machine-gun fire ]
I'll get your kid back, Toy!
[ cries softly ]
Hmm. Hmm!
That guy must
do crazy squats.
Get back here,
you thieving Door Lord!
You butt!
Come on, Bubblegum!
Finn?
[ gasps ]
Aaahh! Aaahh!
[ electronic humming ]
[ hisses ]
Marceline!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
We'll get him.
[ electronic humming ]
No!
[ sighs ]
What?!
"This door shall
yield to no command,
save for a song
from a genuine band."
What is this grippa grap?
It's the door of
the Door Lord, Finn.
We used to lock them up,
but they kept breaking out,
'Ôcause they're Door Lords.
They broke out because
you let them live.
[ growls ]
Hmm.
The door said it'll
open for a genuine band.
Let's try to music this
door open as a quintet.
Can | be the jerk
in the band?
'ÔCause that's an important
part of a band's success.
Hmph!
I know how to get
through this door.
We're gonna lay down
a chill jam.
Hey! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Just keep it cool.
Got that, Princess?
Hmph!
Ohh! Oh!
My face!
[ music plays, Beemo laughing ]
Let's see if you hacks can
keep up with my raw talent.
Hyah!
[ violin playing melodiously,
Finn imitating beat box ]
D La-da-da da-da )
2 I'm gonna bury you
in the ground )
D La-da-da da-da )
2 I'm gonna bury you
with my sound È
2 I'm gonna drink the red
from your pretty pink face
2 I'mgonna -- 0
Marceline,
that's too distasteful.
Onh.
You don't like that?
Or do you just
not like me?!
> Sorry | don't treat
you like a goddess )
2 Is that what you
want me to do? È
> Sorry | don't treat
you like you're perfect È
2 Like all your little,
loyal subjects do È
> Sorry I'm not
made of sugar )
È Am | not sweet
enough for you? JÈ
2 Is that why you
always avoid me? >
D That must be such an
inconvenience to you )
È Well,
I'm just your problem JÈ
È I'm just your problem È
J It's like I'm not
even a person, am |? )
È I'm just your problem È
> Well, I-I-I B
2 Shouldn't have to
justify what | do
DI-I-1 D
È Shouldn't have to
prove anything to you J
2 I'msorry... È
It's working!
Look at the door!
J ...landed me on
your blacklist )
> But I-I-1 È
È Shouldn't have to be the
one that makes up with you È
È So why do | want to? >
È Why do | want to?
> To bury you in the ground È
2 And drink the blood
from your -- È
Ugh!
Stop staring at me!
Ugh! You threw me off!
FINN:
Come on, everybody!
Don't stop now!
The door was responding
to our music!
| wonder what it liked
or what was missing.
Well, | know what's missing --
talent.
I'm getting out of here,
you hacks --
Talentless hacks!
Yikes.
Maybe to be a genuine band,
we need to be nicer to each
other and hang out as buds.
Let's take a noodle break.
Come on! It'll help!
No! Wait! Don't go, too!
I'm just gonna get
stuff to cook that.
Cook?
That was sweet what you
said about being buds.
Mm-hmm. Thanks.
I'm back, yo.
Come here, baby.
Oh!
Pasta water...
getting hotter.
A song about noodles?
BOTH:
No!
Oh.
[ laughter ]
For our next attempt,
| want to be the lead.
Yeah.
Sounds cool, my bud.
Hmph!
Jake! You're back!
Shut your face.
| came back for the music.
Beemo,
execute song structure alpha.
[ electronic music plays ]
Marceline, begin begin
playing triplet quavers in the
mixolydian mode.
All right. Fine.
Wait. What's a quaver?
Now, Finn, vibrate
your uvula by dampening
and undampening your larynx.
What?!
Go like this, silly.
Oh.
[ vibrating ]
Waaaaa...
Okay. Okay.
Jake, are you gonna join in?
[ grunts ]
Grr!
Everyone,
just stick to my blueprints.
[ gasps ]
Oh!
[ sighs ]
One more time?
| may have, um,
miscalculated.
Ha!
Looks like you aren't
as perfect as you thought.
Guess you can't
judge me anymore.
| never said you
had to be perfect!
All right.
Time out, guys.
[ spits ]
[ gasping ]
Princess!
Princess, wait!
Whatever. Oh!
I'm out of here, too!
Marceline...
[ sobbing ]
You've all forgotten
about the music.
I quit the band!
I'm just pretending.
Jake! Everybody!
We can beat the
Door Lord --
together.
[ clapping rhythmically ]
> Everyone J
> Bubblegum )
> 1I'm so dumb
2 | should have just told you JÈ
D> What | lost .
È Was a piece of your hair )
È Now it's gone JÈ
D Gone forever )
È But | guess, what does
it matter when | just )
> Just had all of you there? )
È>0h 2D
2 | just had all of you
there with me, my friends )
2 If you're even my friends È
You like this?
This is what was missing.
The truth!
È What am | to you? È
È Am | a joke, your Knight,
or your brother? È
È What am | to you? È
> Do you look down on me
'Ôcause I'm younger? JÈ
2 Do you think that |
don't understand? È
2 | just wanted us together
and to play as a band
2 Last night was the most fun
I've ever had >
> Even liked it when the
two of you would get mad
at each other )
È>0h 2D
2 You a-a-a-are my
best friends in the world )
È That's ri-i-i-ight >
2 I'm talking 'bout
the two of you, girls È
È And you, Jake >
2 | wanna sing a song to you J
D> And | refuse
to make it fake È
È What am | to you? È
SJAmla..È
BOTH:
JÈ Joke, your Knight, or your brother? >
È What am | to you? È
> Do you look down on
me 'cause I'm younger? )
2 Do you think that
| don't understand? È
2 | just wanted us together
and to play as a band
2 I'll forget that | lost
a piece of your hair JÈ
2 I'll remember the
pasta that we shared È
D Over there
È Ah,ah b
BOTH:
D You a-a-a-are )
È My best friends
in the world &
D You a-a-a-are )
È My best friends
in the world &
BOTH:
È That's ri-i-i-ight >
2 I'm talking 'bout
the two of you, girls È
È And you, Jake >
2 I'm gonna sing
a song to you )
D> And | refuse
to make it fake È
BOTH:
> Ahh, ahh
> Make no mistake
2 I'm gonna sing a
song that feels so real È
D It'll make this
do-0-o-r break È
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
Hmm-hmm.
[ munches, spits ]
Hmm?
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
It's over, Drawer Lord.
So, hand over our stuff!
Hmm-hmm, hmm-hmm.
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
Hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm.
Hmm?
What's he trying to say?
| totally get it.
He may have stolen our
treasures...
But by doing so,
he showed us...
that the real treasure
is friendship.
Hmm-hmm-hmm!
Hmm-hmm! Hmm-hmm-hmm!
Hmm!
JAKE:
Okay.
Here's that lock of Bubblegum's
hair you love so much.
Oh, you!
Ah, yeesh.
And here's Jakey's Blanky.
Here's your controller, Beemo.
Yippie-ki-yi-yay!
Marceline,
here's your rock shirt.
Hey, that's not --
That's mine!
That's mine.
You kept the
shirt | gave you?
Yeah.
It, uh,
means a lot to me.
But you never wore it.
Dude, | wear it all the time --
as pajamas.
Wait.
If that's Bubblegum's shirt,
what are you missing, Marceline?
Wait a second.
Wait a second!
You don't have a thing.
You just wanted to
hang out with us.
No, I didn't!
No way. You're caught.
| figured you out.
[ laughing ]
[ growling ]
Uhhhh!
I'll kill you!
[ laughing ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!