[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ bells jingling ]
- Jake, you made this?
- Yeah.
And you buried
the treasure right here?
Uh-huh.
Jake, you're awesome!
[ grunts ]
This is so cool.
BOTH:
[ grunting ]
FINN:
A suitcase?
Oh, man!
| found it in the dump
and then buried it
without looking inside.
Whoa.
Wait a second, man.
| know this case.
One night, while you were
away at Lady's house,
| was dancing in the woods.
ICE KING:
Evil tapes. Evil!
Perchance, | saw the Ice King
doing something suspicious.
So | trailed him to the dump,
where he buried this case
in the ground.
You're evil tapes!
Full of evil secrets!
That's why I'm going
to bury you
where no one will ever
find you...
under all these boogers!
Whee!
[ laughs ]
Whee! [ laughs ]
FINN:
| waited for him to leave.
But he played in those boogers
for hours.
| decided to come back later
for the case.
But | lost track of it.
- Whoa! And | found it?
- Mm-hmm.
[ laughs ]
Let's have a secret
screening.
I'll make some fliers for it.
There, now nobody will
bother us.
FINN:
Jake! Jake, come on!
Okay, you can play this,
right, Beemo?
Yes, Finn.
It goes in my butt.
Oh.
This is so exciting!
Hello, dear diary.
Pretty good day so far.
Got up bright and early,
had a healthy and slimming
breakfast,
did 14 minutes of cardio.
Dude, what are
we watching?
| think it's
the Ice King's diary.
| mean, I'm not gonna win
carpenter of the year
or anything,
but it's a place
to hang up the old toothbrush.
Wenk.
Gunter.
Hey, Gunter.
Get -- get away
from the camera, sweetie.
Papa's recording
his innermost thoughts.
Remember, | explained this
to you?
Hey, Gunter.
Gunter!
- Wenk.
Well, anyway, as you can see,
I'm not wearing my --
Wenk.
I'm not wearing
my --
Wenk, wenk.
Sweetie, | raised my voice
because you were giving me
the silent treatment.
You understand?
- Wenk.
| love you.
Can we fast-forward?
N-No, man, we might
miss something.
[ sighs ]
There must be more to life
than this.
Wenk.
| know, you don't
like when I'm contemplative.
C-Contemplative? No.
Con-tem-plat--
C-- let's put on a play!
What?!
[ as Bubblegum ]
Oh, Ice King, you're so cool!
You take such good care
of yourself!
| want to be with youl!
Wenk, wenk, wenk!
[ normal voice ]
No, Gunter, beard stays on.
Wenk.
ICE KING:
Gunter, | need you to wear the beard!
- Wenk.
- Gunter!
Hey, pause it, Beemo.
There's got to be some
evil secrets in here.
| want to keep watching.
Okay.
Well, why don't | make us
some shacks?
So | don't have to
watch this.
Can we sit on the floor?
| feel so far away
from you guys.
Wenk.
[ knuckles crack ]
Aha!
Now hold still.
[ zap!]
[ dink! ]
You moved!
Ooh, what's this?
[ mumbling ]
Secret tapes?!
| wanna watch!
Catch you later, Gunter.
Wenk.
[ laughs ]
[ dance music plays ]
Gunter, no!
Gunter!
Dance p--
Dance party!
[ munching ]
Thanks, Gunter.
[ laughs ]
Mmm!
You're Gunter.
[ both laugh ]
Wenk, wenk, wenk, wenk.
Oh, fine,
who needs you?
More dance party for us.
Right, Gunter?
Oh! Uh...
[ chuckles nervously ]
May | have this dance?
[ chuckles ]
There's probably some
evil secrets coming up.
[ knock on door ]
Someone wants to see
the secret tapes!
What?!
Oh, but | was so clear
in my flier.
Let's peek through the window
and check who it is.
Maybe it's just a pizza.
Right!
- Hey, hey!
- BOTH: What?!
You guys are checking
too loud!
Oh, you're right.
More quietly.
[ clicking ]
I'm quieter now.
Cool.
[ knocking continues ]
Hey, guys, it's me.
Can | come in and watch
the secret tapes with you?
| brought some gifts.
BOTH:
Aah!
Okay, if we're quiet
long enough,
Ice King will think
no one's home and go away.
[ knocking continues ]
Ah, no one's home.
Guess I'll go away.
[ alarm blares ]
Aah! Aah! Ohh!
Huh?
[ blaring continues ]
Just turn your alarm
off!
Hmm, that sounds
like Beemo.
[ blaring continues ]
My alarm says it's time
for Finn's bath.
Finn, get naked.
No, just hit your
snooze button!
| cannot self-snooze.
It's against my programming.
Well, then, tell me
how to do it!
[ blaring continues ]
Press and hold, then press
the button on top of my head.
[ blaring stops ]
BOTH:
Phew!
I'm sorry.
We can still take a bath.
[ knocking continues ]
He must know
we're watching his tapes.
We need to find
his secrets faster.
[ crying ]
Oh, diary, thank you for
listening to me.
[ cries ]
Fast-forward, Beemo.
[ high-pitched ]
Sorry, been meaning to tell you
something insanely private.
But darest |?
| love to...
[ grunts ]
...fill my bathtub
full of milk
and sitin it
like I'm a magic angel.
There, | said it.
The white of the milk
is so dense,
And when | poke my little toes
out from under the milk,
they startle me
and | giggle.
| giggle, diary.
They're my own toes,
yet | giggle,
and then | fall asleep.
And the milk curdles and | get
all stinky and sticky.
Disgusting, diary.
| am disgusting.
I'm disgusting.
I'm disgusting and | smell
like curdled milk.
Anyway, back to
the Turtle Princess.
Play, Beemo.
So, there we are.
Turtle Princess is frozen
and in my little ice
wheelbarrow,
and there was magic
in the air.
We were both feeling it.
[ chuckles ]
But before | can leave
the library,
Finn and Jake show up!
You know how Jake is.
Stretch this, stretch that.
Bah!
He knocks off my crown,
and then Finn bonks me
on the nose!
Still hurts, too.
The worst part is,
Turtle Princess took away
my library card.
[ sighs ]
You know, dear diary,
I'm starting to worry
that all these entries sound
exactly the same,
and that my life is just me
running in place
on some giant hamster wheel.
Ugh, fast-forward,
Beemo.
[ high pitched ] 7his reminds me of the time
/ got stuck in my bathroom.
There was a squirrel.
Don't ask.
Anyway, long story short,
imagine me crouched down
on the kitchen floor
talking fo the toilet paper.
Ha ha! I'm like, "Who wants
to go on an adventure?
And the toilet paper's
like, "What?"
You're my best friend,
diary.
I'm gonna take a nap.
No!
These tapes are important.
We just don't know why yet.
Beemo, fast-forward
to triple speed.
Okay.
[ high piftched speaking indistinctly ]
FINN:
Beemo, play normal speed.
[ normal voice ]
Come on, baby, in the pocket!
[ breathing heavily ]
| can't doit. | can't do it.
Maybe he's talking in
secret code.
Telling evil secrets in
secret code...
He's brilliant!
Well, how do we decode
the secrets?
Why don't we call others
for help?
Beemo,
you're brilliant!
Well, who do we call?
Um... the smartest
person we know --
Princess Bubblegum.
She's brilliant.
[ dialing ]
[ laughs evilly]
- Hi, Princess Bubblegum.
- Hey, Finn.
Jake and | found
a bunch of secret tapes.
We were wondering if you'd
help us decode them.
- Codes?
- Yeah, they're really stupid,
but, you know, maybe
they're encoded or whatevah.
Oh, you called
the right person.
| know a lot about codes.
Let's start with --
[ static, dial tone ]
- Huh?
- Oh!
[ dialing ]
Hey, Princess, we got
disconnected.
[ as Bubblegum ]
Hello, Finny. [ giggles ]
BOTH:
You sound weird.
Must be a bad
connection.
That's why we were disconnected
earlier on the telephone.
Ice King is on the phone
outside.
So, how's the weather
in Candy Kingdom?
Oh, the usual.
There's ice everywhere,
and it smells like penguins.
The only thing that smells
like penguins is you, Ice King!
[gasps]
How did you --
What are you doing?!
| want to watch
secret tapes with you guys.
It'll be nice.
No, man.
But --
He doesn't know that
we're watching his tapes.
We gotta find these evil secrets
before he uses them
against us!
Ohhhh, fine!
No more nice!
Now you'll get ice!
Try watching those tapes
with frozen eyeballs!
[ laughs evilly ]
CEEEEEE L]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!