[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D the fun will never end È
D It's Adventure Time È
[ beeps, rhythmic beat plays ]
> We're
fuh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh È
D Finn and Jake >
> We'll
muh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh JÈ
> make-a you, make... )
BOTH:
È We'll make you cry JÈ
Q> Your mama lies >
> Jake likes pies È
2 I'm a guy who'll stick
my stick into your eye È
2 And you'll say why, why,
why, why, why? È
BOTH:
È Why, why, why, why, why? )
2 why, why, why, why, why? È
Pizza!
[ birds squawking ]
[ chuckles ]
MAN: Sir! My sir!
- Hmm?
A message from their majesties.
King and Queen Lumpy Space!
We can't find our baby girl!
Oh!
She's been missing for days!
[ both sobbing ]
Whoa! Stop your crying,
you two.
We'll help you find your
daughter.
We'll find her using Jake's
muscles.
Dude, show off your muscles.
Whoo!
No more tears, booblee bear.
Please, take her these
sandwiches we made.
She loves these sandwiches.
Thank you, boys!
Whoo!
Dude, | know where
Lumpy Space Princess is.
She's in the woods
eating beans.
Mm-hmm.
This is gonna be easy as...
uh...
Easy as childbirth.
Yeah, okay.
MAN:
Oh!
Aah! Oofl
Please! Please, help me.
A monster is terrorizing
our village
and has eaten up
all the crops!
Why were you up here
in this tree?
| thought | saw some food,
and | was hiding
from the monster.
[ groans ]
You must help.
Hmm. | guess we can
help this guy real quick
and then get back to L.S.P.
Where's your village?
Um...
| don't remember.
Howard remembers.
Hey!
It's Howard!
Howard!
You remember where
the village is?!
Yeah, | marked it on the map,
but, uh...
it's only half --
[ branch cracks ]
Well, we're all ready.
We can't leave yet.
[ branch cracks ]
ALL:
Awww.
All right, now we're ready.
What's in the basket?
Samiches!
ALL:
Food!
Food! Food!
Wait!
You can't eat this food!
It's not ours to give!
[all groan]
Now show us the way
to your town.
Too tired from hunger.
Carry me?
[ sighs ]
Okay.
[ all cheering ]
The monster lives
in that windmill.
We're too scared
to go near it.
BOTH:
Nothing scares us!
[ shing! ]
Be alert.
Anything could pop out
of there
and rip our faces off.
Whoo!
[ door creaks ]
[ breathing deeply ]
Be careful, Finn!
[ both scream ]
It's you!
Finn! What the junk?!
Oh! Sandwiches!
L.S.P., what the heck
are you doin' here?
Are you in here making out
with the monster?
[ munching ]
No.
...
am the monster.
WhHEEEEEEEEEEIYA
It's a long story.
It all started at my
lumpin' parents' house.
- Daughter.
- Yeah?
How are the sandwiches?
They're lumpin' delicious,
mom!
You know, you could enjoy your
mom's sandwiches
every day if you came back
more often.
No. You can have them
delivered to me at my apartment.
We want you to move back
home, sweetheart.
What?!
You invited me here
under false pretenses?!
Wait, sweetheart!
We're just worried
about you.
Ha! Y'all don't think | can
make it on my own?!
I'll show you!
I'm running away!
[ voice over ]
| stormed out and left Lumpy Space forever.
Oh.
And then you found this
windmill.
No.
Something else happened first.
Keep listening.
[ voice over ]
| was so cold,
and | was so very hungry.
[ moans ]
Uh, uh!
[ vomits ]
[ groans ]
[ thunder crashes ]
Oh, glob!
Maybe | can...
make a shelter out
of these nuts.
It's not fair!
[ voice over ]
| was rescued by a family of wolves.
The Mama Wolf was all like,
"We must take care of her
as if she were our own."
And Papa Wolf was all like,
"This is a special child who
needs special love
because she's going to be great
when she grows up."
So these were talking
wolves?
No, they were normal wolves.
| knew what
they were thinking
because of their
body language.
Stop interrupting, Finn!
| found a home where | could
act like myself.
They took care of me.
[ all howling ]
| knew that if my parents
could see me now,
they'd be jealous of
how lumpin' awesome | am.
Oh, my glob!
But then the drama started.
[ gasps ]
Stephanie, Sue, can you guys
keep a secret?
[ wolf panting ]
Okay, here's the secret.
| just saw Jessica
making out with Mark...
behind Tony's back.
[ wolf panting ]
Stephanie, are you even
listening?
'Cause I'm kind of freaking out
right now!
Tony's gonna come back
from hunting
any minute now and --
[ wolf howls ]
[ gasps ]
Hi, Tony!
Oh, my glob.
Guys, what are we gonna --
Oh.
[ munching, flies buzzing ]
So, should we say
something to Tony?
You guys!
Tony, Jessica's
cheating on you!
Oh, my glob! Oh, my glob!
Oh, my glob!
Look, I'm sorry.
| know it's none of my
business...
| know!
[ wolf howls ]
Because | think Tony has a right
to know, Stephanie!
[ wolf howls ]
Nuh-unh, Mirandal!
| do notlike Tony!
No, Jessical
Don't cheat on Tony with me!
[ wolves growling ]
Aah! Aah!
Uh! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh, glob!
Ah! Aah!
Oh, no!
Ah! Aaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaa! Aaaaaah!
Oh, glob.
[ voice over ]
| came upon a tribe of villagers.
[ groaning ]
Monster!
Oh, I'm so hungry!
[ munching ]
Monster!
Ah!
Anyway, then | found
this windmill,
and whenever | get hungry,
| dress up like the monster,
and | go eat all of the
villagers' crops.
L.S.P., you're
stealing!
Don't say that!
You're makin' me feel bad.
[ sobbing ]
Thanks, Finn.
L.S.P., if you want to feel better,
you should apologize to
the farmers and make amends.
- Really?
- Yeah. That'll work.
Monster!
Monster! Monster!
No! No, wait!
I'm not a monster!
| was just pretending
to be a monster.
ALL:
Huh?
And I'm sorry
that you're starving
because | ate
all of your crops,
even though you're all
still really fat
and | probably helped you
lose some weight.
Did she just call us fat?
Don't get all
bent out of shape!
I'm just being honest!
FINN:
L.S.P.!
What?
That apology was terrible!
VILLAGER:
Look!
The monster eats while it
apologizes!
Let's Kill it!
[ all shouting ]
Ohh!
[ panting ]
Please don't kill me!
We have to!
Well, you don't have to.
Yeah.
You can just let her go.
If we let her go, she'll keep
eating our crops,
and we'll starve!
Why don't you just get your parents
to buy you more crops?
We are parents!
Those crops were for
our children!
You guys are parents?
Just like my parents...
L.S.P., are you okay?
Yeah, Finn.
I'm great.
Here.
| want you to have these
sandwiches.
ALL:
Sandwiches?
Yeah, they're really good.
They're made
with a lot of love.
[ all munching ]
It's working!
| saved the village!
And that's how | saved
the village.
Well, we're just glad
you're home.
Whatever.
And thank you,
Finn and Jake.
No problem.
Yeah, we didn't really
do that much.
È Come along with me È
2 and the butterflies and bees È
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!