[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
5 With Cake the Cat
and Fionna the Human )
S The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Throw it, Cake!
Heh!
Hee-yah!
These Jelly Kinders aren't...
alive, are they?
What? No.
They can't even talk.
Bloo bloo-bloo bloop --
Kick it!
Thanks for helping
me out, guys.
What are these boogers for,
anyway?
Oh, they're decorations for
my Biennial Gumball Ball...
tonight!
Sounds like
it's gonna be large!
Yes! So very large.
I'd like you to be there
as my special guest.
You want me to...
go with you to the ball?
Heck yes.
As my pall!
Oh. Right.
It starts at 7:00,
so don't be late!
[ thunder rumbling ]
Fionna,
we got trouble!
My tail is totally
frizzin' out.
I'll check it out.
[ thunder crashes ]
[ laughs evilly ]
It's Ice Queen!
The Prince
shall be mine!
Back inside!
Out of my way,
tomboy!
Ice Queen, why you always
predatoring on dudes?
Ha! You should talk, keeping
all the babes to yourself,
totally ice-blocking
my game!
Wha?
Not... this time!
Gah! Slush beast!
Cakel!
Morningstar mode!
Hup!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
You saved me from
the Ice Queen!
Oh, uh, yeah, | guess.
Is she gone?
She must have fled.
Fionna, you're so strong...
and you look so
beautiful in the snow.
What are you
doing later?
| was just going
to go home...
Come with me.
Let's go out.
Go out?
Yeah.
Let's go somewhere.
- What?
- We'd love to!
Great!
Meet me in the castle
gardens in an hour.
Yes! We'll be there!
Oh, it's a date!
No, it's not.
I'm sure when he
said, "Go out,"
he meant "Go out,"
not "go out!"
Shut up!
He's into you!
Come on!
You heard what he said.
I'm like his guy friend.
Well, that could
change tonight!
If it's a date,
why are you coming?
I'm coming to help you.
Hold on.
I'm bringing
my dulcimer.
Aw, man!
It's a conversation starter.
[ grunts ]
Fine. I'll do this,
if only to prove you wrong.
Mm. Let's just bail.
| changed my mind.
No!
No retreat, girl.
GUMBALL:
Hello, Fionna.
And | see you brought Cake.
That's cool, right?
Only if it's cool
that | brought...
Lord Monochromicorn.
How are you, gorgeous?
Accept these tokens
of our esteem.
Hey, you didn't have to,
guy.
Nonsense.
For you, Cake...
A satchel of
Nepetalactone.
Mo-cro picked
it himself.
Catnip!
Sweet babies!
And for you, M'lady...
a bouquet of posies.
Oh, uh... they're...
There's a surprise
at the center.
Huh?
A crystal sword!
I'm all about swords!
How did you know?!
| pay attention to things
| see you being all about.
Thanks, dude.
It's just -- wow.
Come.
For the wowiness has
only just begun!
Psst! Fi.
Tell Gumball that
you think he's "Hawt."
What? No!
Guys like to hear
that they're hot!
Will you keep your
voice down?!
- Oh, Fionna!
- Hey! What's up?
| thought we might
have a little race --
a playful race --
to Marshmallowy Mweadows.
Okay. But I'm gonna
kick your butt.
Not that I'm thinking
of butts...
Excellent.
Hyah!
After him, Fionna!
After your man!
Whoooooo!
[ both panting ]
Good race, Fionna.
Why are y'all breathless
if we're the ones runnin'?
[ humming ]
Hup!
Gumball!
Sorry. | saw a pearl
Pygmy skull in there.
It reminded me of you --
the way your eyes... sparkle.
[ giggles ]
Fionna, there's something
| want to tell you.
| feel like
nothing was real >
2 Until | met you È
2 | feel like we connect
and | really get you
2 If | said "You're a beautiful girl,"
would it upset you? È
> Because the way
you look tonight J
2 Silhouetted,
I'll never forget it È
5 Oh, oh, Fionna È
È Your fist has
touched my heart >
5 Oh, oh, Fionna È
2 I won't let anything
in this world keep us apart È
BOTH: È | won't let anything
[ both laugh ]
Oh, my gosh, dude.
That was, like,
the stupidest thing ever.
See you back
at the treehouse!
[ding! ]
[ both laugh ]
Geez, | don't know.
I've thought about it, but...
| think you could wear
your pants as a shirt,
if you really needed to.
[ laughing ]
Okay, okay.
Now you ask me something.
Oh, uh...
is this a date?
[ chuckling ]
Fionna...
come to the ball with me.
As your... chum?
No.
As my girlfriend.
[ door closes ]
It was a date!
There was singing and junk!
| know! | was there
for that part!
Cake, he wants me to go to the
ball... as his girlfriend!
Oh, my goodness!
It's almost 7:00!
You need
something to wear!
Oh, hold on, honey.
I'm gonna make this happen!
How am | supposed to fit
my weapons in this?
It's a ball!
You don't need weapons!
I'll take my
retractable sword.
Okay!
Let's go, go, go!
[ indistinct conversations,
laughter ]
Lovely, lovely.
[ muttering ]
Yes,
| designed it myself.
[ gasps ]
I've been looking for you.
Well, here | am.
Ha ha!
Hey, | want to
show you something.
Okay.
Whoo!
Okay, girl!
See you later!
What?
Hey, is this your bedroom?
Fionna...
[ chuckles nervously ]
Whoa.
What?!
[ laughing ]
[ high-pitched laughing ]
This was so much easier than
| thought it would be!
This is really messed up,
Ice Queen!
What is your
problem with me?!
You're what stands
between me and my Gumball!
| can't believe | fell
for this trash!
You got me to show up
with that dress and a pur--
my purse!
My sword!
[ laughs evilly ]
[ shing! ]
[ laughs ]
Aah!
You like my ice sword?
[ grunting ]
- Get it off mel!
- Fionna?
[ laughing continues ]
[ grunting ]
N EEEEEEE L]
Oh, my goodness!
What's going on in he--
Aaaaah!
Don't you touch her!
Aaah!
Shh!
It's okay, it's okay!
It was the Ice Queen.
Paws off my Prince!
Aaaaaah!
[ laughs evilly ]
Donk! Unh!
[ moaning ]
My magic tiara!
My powers!
And this is for
yankin' my heart guts!
Ha ha!
I'm a Queen!
No.
You might catch
her crazy.
Wow, Fionna... you're...
you're just...
really incredible.
Maybe we should meet up...
for a date!
No way, man.
Not interested.
[ sighs ]
| think the reason | got all
these guy friends and no boyfriend
is because | don't
really want to date any of 'em.
| don't need to feel like
I'm waiting to be noticed.
| know who | am,
and I'll know what | want
if and when it
ever comes along.
But there is one guy I'd
do anything to date...
The Ice King!
- What?
Me, too. Ice King's
the rea/deal.
[ rumbling ]
Ice King is the hottest hottie,
and | can't wait to marry him!
ICE KING:
...said Fionna.
Then she turned to
Prince Gumball and said,
"l hope Ice King will
sweep me off my feet
and take me
to the farthest corner of Ooo,
where we will do nothing
but kiss and eat a whole bunch
until we get fat and die!"
The end.
So, what did you think
of the fan-fiction
| wrote about
you guys?
Uhh...
Tell me you
thought it was good!
Uh, it's good!
It's good!
It's -- it's really good, dude!
It was amazing!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
> And do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!