[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D the fun will never end È
D It's Adventure Time È
PRINCESS:
Finn! Finn!
Finn, where are you?
| need you to try this.
I'll be there in a sec.
[ telephone rings ]
What's the status?
- Good, man.
Nice.
Seal the deal, bro.
[ laughs nervously ]
Okay, man. Whatevs.
You can do it!
You hear me?
I'm playin' Beemo.
Call me later. Bye.
BEEMO:
How's Finn's date?
| think it's goin'
good.
Unlike your game, boy-eeee.
Where's the key
to the tower, Beemo?!
Tell me!
Aaaah!
Okay, Finn.
She's 13. You're 13.
Just have fun.
Be yourself.
Whoooooooooooooop!
What's that?
Are you trying to make yourself
18 again?
Nah.
This is an instant bath serum.
It makes you sweat
cleaning agents.
| don't bathe.
| want that.
[ screaming ]
Hot!
So spice! So spice!
[ laughs ]
You're so spice!
MANFRIED:
JÈ Bwaa bwaa bwaa bwaa È
Announcing the arrival
of the Earl of Lemongrab!
[ grunts ]
Aah!
Oooh!
[ groaning ]
This castle is in...
unacceptable...
condition!
Unacceptable!
[ crowd murmuring ]
30 days in the dungeon!
- For who?
- Everyone in this room.
Aah!
Wait! Wait!
You can't give orders
like that!
I'm in charge here,
Lemongrab!
Too young!
Too young to rule
the kingdom!
Watch your manners
with the princess!
Hoo0000000!
- What the huh?
- Mm...
| am nextin line
to the throne,
so | will be in charge
until Princess Bubblegum
turns 18 again!
That's bunk!
Right, Preebos?
No.
He is rightful ruler
under kingdom law.
It's complicated.
| created Lemongrab.
[ gasps ]
He was the first one of my
experiments gone wrong.
NYEEEEEEEEEEE])
[ screaming ]
[ gasps ]
And now that
I'm younger than him,
he inherits the right to
control the throne.
If anyone needs me,
I'll be taking a nap.
And clean this place up,
or dungeon!
Three hours dungeon!
Who are you talkin' to?
-[allgasp]
- Three hours dungeon!
Nooooo!
We'll see you
in a few hours.
Okay, Starchy?
- Yeah, right.
If Starchy survives
that long.
Finn, this is dirt balls!
We've got to do something
to make him leave!
Yeah!
Like pranking him
up his face!
Yeah!
And | have the perfect prank!
Come on, Finn.
[ laughs ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ clock rings, bird squawks ]
Huh?
"You...
really...
smell...
like...
dog buns"?
[ screams ]
Well, well, well.
This is everyone, then?
Yes. All the castle staff.
So which one of you was it?
Who did the thing?!
The thing?
[ groans loudly ]
The thing! The thing!
PEPPERMINT BUTLER:
Hey, man! Calm down.
It's just a prank, man.
For laughs.
Prank? For laughs?
Yes, of course.
Just a harmless prank...
for laughs.
[ laughing ]
12 years dungeon,
all of you -- dungeon.
Seven years, no trials.
- [ crowd groaning ]
Come on. Let's move it.
[ sighs ]
| don't think that worked out
too math, Finn.
What? No, no.
He just needs some more
prankings to finish the job.
He'll leave the kingdom.
Let's try it my way
this time, okay?
Okay.
[ both babbling spookily ]
Ooh!
[ coughing, groaning ]
Ha ha ha ha ha! Good one!
[ coughs ]
Keep 'em coming!
I'm not going anywhere!
Ho ha!
[ both panting ]
| got a new plan!
Oh, yeah? What?
We'll work together
and use that serum you made,
the one that was
"Ah! So spice!"
and spice-bomb him nonstop
til his butt falls out.
How's that sound?
- [ sighs ]
Thank you for releasing me
from the dungeon early,
Master Lemongrab.
| determine what is early
and what is late,
Mr. Peppermint.
Yes, your Earlness.
Also, | don't know where food
comes from.
My lord, food
comes from ma--
No! Da-da-da-da-da! No!
That is why | am royal
and you are servile!
You ready to pour
the stuff?
Yeah.
| made it super hot this time.
Wait 'til he opens
the lid.
Behold, a plate of mashed
carrots, flavor--
[ screaming ]
Shoot!
Shh.
Stop screaming!
Why are you screaming?!
Because I'm excited
by this meal | made!
Me, too.
I'm excited, too.
[ retches ]
[ screaming ]
BOTH:
Whoa!
He's eating the dirt.
Spice it now!
[ screaming ]
Apple!
Oh!
Ooh!
Mmm!
Oop.
[ sighs ]
Mmm!
[ laughs ]
One million years dungeon!
[ door slams ]
Hmm.
Maybe if we set his butt
on fire?
No, Finn.
There's only one way.
| just didn't want
to have to do it.
If | change myself back
to my real age,
| can reclaim
the throne.
What?! No!
| mean, uh,
you can do that?
Then why did you wait so long?
Because being 13 again is
bloobalooby!
Hmm?
Well, being 18 is
all plopdumps and waggle-sags.
| never really get to act
like a kid.
But it's okay, really.
My people need me,
and that comes first.
Yeah.
The first thing we need
is more candyflesh
to increase my biomass.
But | need my lab equipment
to engineer it.
PEPPERMINT BUTLER:
Not necessarily, m'lady.
[ gasps ]
Oh, thank youl!
Thank you all!
Okay, next we need
a bonding agent.
FINN:
Princess, | think | can help.
Finished!
There's one last
thing we need.
Only the heat from a whopping
love-hug
can catalyze
the re-agifying process.
Are you ready,
Princess?
Yes, Finn, but first,
| just want to say
how much fun I've had hanging
out with you.
Me too!
And I...
| wish | could stay
like this
with you, but...
l...
| know, Princess.
'Scuse me, Finn.
Yo, Earl!
EARL:
What?!
Hey! You're fired,
ya butt!
[ screams ]
[ muttering ]
I'm so glad
everything's back to normal.
Thanks for all your help, Finn.
Oh! You're welcome.
But, um...
What is it, Finn?
Well, do you, uh...
do you want to hug some more?
[ laughs ]
What? Finn, you silly.
That was like five years ago.
You really got to move on.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Sorry.
Such a silly boy.
[ sighs ]
[ telephone rings ]
Hello.
Hey, man.
What's the status?
Bad news, man.
l...
| got dumped.
Aw, I'm sorry, Finn.
But look, man, let me share
with you a little secret
on how to win the heart
of a princess.
It's not easy, but you have
to be persistent.
You might have
to defeat a demon lord
and warp through
several worlds,
but once you do, you
walk up the wizard stairs
and produce your magic key
you got in the water world
and unlock
the chamber door.
Then walk right up
to the princess
and you give her
a smooch.
[ beep ]
Yes!
Does that make sense?
Yeah, man.
| see what you're saying.
Thanks, Jake.
Mm-hmm.
[ beep ]
Go up the wizard
steps...
È Come along with me È
2 and the butterflies and bees È
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!