[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
FINN:
The tree of blight.
[ shrieks ]
Every hundred years,
it spews evil spores
across the land.
Then let's burn its butt
down to the root-rubbings!
Finn, | can feel
a bunch of
eyeballs peeping
us from the woods.
[ growls ]
[ gasps ]
Hugs!
What the...
is this an extra butt?
[ grunts ]
Quick, Jake,
burn the tree.
Grr, hugs.
[ grunts ]
Gonna catch you up,
boy.
I'm gonna sugar
you to pieces.
Dude!
The tree's about to 'splode
its evil juice all over.
No!
[ growls ]
[ gasps ]
[ howls ]
Ugh!
Jake! Hurry!
Is he crushing you,
man?
No, he's just
hugging me gently.
JAKE:
Oh.
[ deep voice ] When you see
the wicker devil in tree afterlife,
tell him Jake says "Hello."
[ shrieking ]
Aah! Aah-ha-ha!
[ coughing ]
Ugh.
Hey, buddy. You okay?
Didn't even tell
me its name.
What?
Oh, sweet.
[ laughs ]
BOTH:
Hot to the touch.
[ video game beeping ]
[ whistling ]
[ beeping stops ]
Hmm.
Dude, why are you so huggy?
| just feel affectionate,
| guess.
Hugging helps.
Mm.
You got a fever, man.
| feel hot.
Finn, you're hurting me.
| think you need a
good night's sleep.
[ shrieking ]
You feeling
better today?
Yeah.
| feel like a
million clams.
Good.
Hey, you think we
have enough candy litter?
Litter for lunch! Mmm.
Huh?
Huh? Not again.
What's the matter,
Cinnamon Bun?
Please, Finn.
If you're gonna hug me again,
don't make it as hard as you
hugged me last night.
Uh, I didn't hug
you last night.
Yes, you did.
My love handles still hurt.
You came into my room around
midnight and gave me a
squeeze --
a really strong one!
[ groaning ]
C.B. says | hugged him.
[ laughs ]
Cinnamon Bun,
you've got some crazy notions.
| tell you.
[ laughs ]
[ both laughing ]
[ groans ]
[ laughs ]
Oh, Cinnamon Bun.
What a crazy story, buddy.
Yeah, buddy.
But you were pretty
huggy last night, buddy.
Wait.
You don't think | actually snuck
into Cinnamon Bun's room and
hugged him, do you?
I'm just saying,
you were really clingy.
But -- no.
Why would 1?
And don't tell me it's because
| have repressed emotional
feelings for Cinnamon Bun.
No.
| have a theory,
but | don't like it.
Your questionable behavior
started about an hour or so
after you got hugged by
that wolf-man, right?
FINN:
So?
Well, I've been thinking
that maybe that wolf-man
wasn't what he seemed.
Maybe he was some
sort of "Hug Wolf."
Yeah, here it is.
Hug-Wolves --
"A subset of wolf-men
which roam the countryside
with a fervid hug-lust.
Every night, hug-wolves must go
out and hug people to satisfy
their insatiable
craving for hugs.
To become a hug wolf, one must
be hugged by an alpha hug wolf
on the night
of a full moon!
Like last night!
Yes.
So you must be a
beta hug wolf --
a lower-level creature.
Well, how can
| get un-cursed?
Let me, um, read the
book a little more.
It says there's
no known cure.
[ gasps ]
I'm scared, Jake.
No hugs!
I'm sorry.
[ grunting ]
| feel hot.
[ whimpering ]
What's wrong,
Beemo?
I'm terrified of Finn.
Hmm.
Well, that plant's
not gonna protect you.
You can get this
under control, buddy.
Are you ready to
overcome this thing?!
| think so.
| said, "Are you ready to
overcome this thing?!"
Yeah. | heard you.
| said, "l think so."
I'm trying to
get you to shout.
Oh. Okay.
Is this good?!
Never mind.
Now, | want you to think
about hugging a cactus.
How would that feel?
Prickly and painful.
Good. Good.
You're doing great.
Cool.
So, can | hug
the cactus now?
No, you can't
hug anything.
But that poor cactus.
It --
it needs me!
[ panting ]
[ growls ]
Ah, no.
The hug-lust has already
taken over your brain.
[ growling ]
| want to hug you, Jake.
[ breathing heavily ]
[ growling ]
Finn?
Say something
to reassure me.
[ growling ]
I'll hug your mom.
[ gasping ]
Jake, we need
the silver baseball.
[ growling ]
[ growls ]
Hugs. Hugs. Hugs.
Hugs for buddies!
[ howls ]
Oh, glob,
oh my glob, Jake.
W ETEL
[ breathing heavily ]
Bring it in, guys.
Scream-o!
Beemo!
Strobe-light mode!
[ techno music plays ]
[ growling ]
Not cool.
JAKE:
Back, beast.
[ howls ]
[ grunting ]
Surely this frosted drink will
soothe my fevered tempers.
[ breathing heavily ]
Hello?
Good heavens.
A lycanthrope!
Aah!
Hug you up, bro.
[ breathing heavily ]
[ roars ]
[ groaning ]
[ growling ]
[ sighs ]
Dracula?
Aah! Eeel!
[ growling ]
Hugs!
Get away from my daughter,
you hairy teenager!
[ imitates gun cocking ]
-[roars ]
- Eee!
[ imitating gun cocking, gunshots ]
[ grunting ]
She'll never marry!
[ imitates gunshot ]
[ fairy-tale music plays ]
JAKE:
Finn? Finn?
There he is.
Huh?
Huh?What --
what happened?
Jake, what happened
to me last night?
You hugged everyone.
No!
There he is!
[ crowd jeering ]
We're mad, but we're
not gonna go down there.
People of the Candy Kingdom,
all I've ever wanted was to
keep you all safe.
And because | can't undo
the hugs I've caused,
my sole wish is to be locked up
forever in the Candy dungeon.
Why is Finn in a cage,
mama?
Isn't hugs nice?
Oh, baby.
Candy people!
Let's make sure that alpha hug
wolf pays for what he's done.
Yeah!
| agree with the last guy.
Cinnamon Bun,
you watch over Finn.
Uh...
Let's go, boys.
Uhh...but -- but -- but --
[ crowd cheers ]
[ chanting ]
No more hugs!
Without consent.
[ groans ]
Huh?
[ gasps ]
[ grunting ]
Hugs!!
Finn?
[ grunting ]
Uh...
[ growling ]
Cinnamon Bun,
let me out.
| --
I'm not supposed to.
Don't you want a hug?
| can't, man.
Not even a little one?
[ groaning ]
You want a hug?
[ muttering ]
Yes! Hug me!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Which way does it turn?
[ growls ]
ow!
Ow, my sides.
Say "No" to hugs!
| smell someone being
hugged right now!
Uh, | have a wife.
That hug be your last,
demon.
[ yelps ]
[ growls ]
Still love you.
Raah! Come here, baby.
No huggies!
Raah.
[ indistinct talking ]
Eh. Finn?
I've failed you.
[ howls ]
[ grunting ]
I'm gonna hug you up.
You call that a hug?
[ both grunting ]
This is the biggest hug
that's ever existed.
[ grunts ]
Yeah.
[ howls ]
[ groans ]
Huh?
You --
you stopped hugging me.
Yeah. You stopped, too.
| just didn't feel like
| needed any more hugs.
Me neither.
The curse is broken!
Can | get a hug?
Jake!
Mm.
[ shrieking ]
Aah!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!