[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
J [ video-game music plays ] È
[ horse whinnies ]
Ha ha ha.
Take that, Master Chen.
FINN:
Jake?
JAKE:
What?
Jake, did you hide my sock?
JAKE:
No, man.
| told you -- | don't do that
kind of stuff anymore.
So, what?
It just magically disappeared?
| don't know.
Maybe.
Is that just a cute way
of saying you took it?
JAKE:
No!
FINN:
Why don't you just help me find my sock?
Oh, Finn lost his sock!
Everybody stop
what you're doing
and help Finn
find his precious sock!
[ hiss!]
BMO:
/t looked like a fough case to crack,
but.. | hate fo see
good friends fight.
So / decide to take the case.
2 [ film-noir music plays ] S
[ camera shutter clicks ]
Hmm.
[ gasps ]
Ronnie.
[ squeaks ]
It looked like | had
a guilty mouse.
> [ tempo quickens ] È
[ gasps ]
[ exhales sharply ]
[ music stops, sour notes play]
Hello, Ronnie.
[ BMO's voice, deep ]
What do you want, BMO?
[ squeaks ]
Where is Finn's sock?
| don't know what you're
talking about, BMO.
| didn't do nothing.
Leave me alone!
[ squeaks ]
| knew that lipstick anywhere.
How is Lorraine?
You stay away from her!
She's with me now.
Do you hear?
Calm down, big guy.
Me and Lorraine are...
dinosaur bones.
Good.
'Cause | would be so jealous.
[ squeaks ]
Just tell me where the sock is,
and | will let you go.
| don't know, man.
What if | put some knuckle
in your eyeballs?
Would that help you think?
[ squeaks ]
Okay! Okay!
Um...
it looks like a grape-juice
stain on his sock.
Check the pantry.
Of course,
[ didn't trust Ronnie.
But | had no other leads.
Maybe the grape juice had
some secrets to tell me.
Or maybe Ronnie was just
pulling my hair.
[ grunting ]
Ugh.
Just as | thought --
not even opened.
| fell right into his trap.
[ door creaks ]
[ gasps ]
BMO:
Let me out, you!
[ pounding on door ]
| will get you!
Piece of you, Ronnie!
Oofl
Oh. Officer Davis.
Thank goodness. I--
[ BMO's voice, deep ]
BMO, what are you doing here?
Looking for Finn's sock --
same as you.
We got this under control.
Stay out of police business,
or you will be the one
behind bars.
/ didn't listen fo that cop.
/ needed to find Ronnie.
And | knew just the lady
who could lead me to him.
J [ slow saxophone music plays ] È
She looked
as beautiful as ever.
[ clucks ]
Where is the sock,
Lorraine?
[ BMO's voice, high ]
What makes you think | know?
| saw your lipstick
on his fur,
so don't act so cute.
It sounds like somebody's
jealous, no?
Don't count on it, Lorraine.
Now, tell me
where Ronnie is.
Hal!
You think it was Ronnie?
Maybe if he was man enough
to steal a sock,
| wouldn't have
spent my nights with Bebe.
Bebe?!
So you are saying Bebe
/s man enough?
What? No.
You are putting words
in my mouth.
Bebe doesn't know anything
about Finn's sock.
[ gasps ]
Finn's sock?
How do you know
it was Finn's sock?
| never said whose sock was
stolen, Lorraine.
I, um, um...
| heard it on the TV news.
No dice, sweet beak.
Officer Davis has this case
under tight wraps.
Uh, uh... fine!
Bebe stole the sock!
Okay?
Oh, BMO.
Can't you just
forget about it?
Sorry, lady.
Forgetting ain't
in my job description.
[ chuckles smugly ]
Does this mean you still
remember... us?
Ha ha. Same old Lorraine.
Well, don't tell Ronnie
about me and Bebe.
You know how he gets
when he's jealous.
[ door creaks, closes ]
Bebe owned Bebe's,
a dance club downtown.
He yells at ladies.
Wake up, brainiac.
[ BMO's voice, deep ]
BMO? Aah! Aah!
Arrgh!
Where is the sock, Bebe?
Uh...
[ coughs ]
| don't know
nothin' 'bout socks!
Don't play dumb, Bebe.
Don't play dumb with me.
[ coughing, gagging ]
| talked to Lorraine, Bebe.
She sold you out, dum-dum.
No!
She -- she wouldn't do that!
It wasn't me! | swear!
It was Ronnie!
Ronnie? But why?
| don't know, man.
| don't know.
[ sobbing ]
Oh, Lorraine.
[ sobbing continues ]
I'm gonna go wash this
schmutz off my grabbers.
When | get back, you better
start talking sense.
It wasn't adding up.
Why would Ronnie
swipe the sock?
And why would Lorraine
finger Bebe?
Sure, he's a dirtbag born out
of a mother, but who's not?
| don't really get it.
Maybe it was time
fo cut my losses.
Come on, Bebe.
Let's get you cleaned up.
Bebe?
Bebe!
Dead!
This doesn't look good.
| better hightail it!
- [ meows ]
- Huh?! The cops!
It was a setup!
[ gasps ]
Oh. Oh, no.
Bang, bang!
Pyoo! Pyoo! Pyoo!
[ growls ]
[ panting ]
Whoa!
Ugh!
Ugh! Ugh!
Ohh...
ugh...
JAKE:
Hey, has anyone seen BMO?
BMO!
Where's BMO?
Hello?
With the ljpstick, she looked
as beautiful as ever.
I'm worried about BMO.
This is real.
BMO!
Who's BMO?
[ deeper voice ]
Hello?
[ echoing ]
Hello? Hello?
N.E.P.T.R.:
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hey, BMO.
Wake up, buddy.
Are you all right?
N.E.P.T.R.?
| feel like | got hit
with a Dracula by King Kong.
Whoa. Sorry, man.
You want some pie
or something?
Sorry. | gotta run.
The cops are after me.
Have you seen any down here?
Nah. No one's been
down here all day,
except me, you,
and Ronnie.
What?! What was Ronnie
doing down here?
| don't know.
But now my sensors indicate
that some treasure
is missing.
[ whirring ]
About a sock's worth.
[ gasps ]
That's it!
That's why Ronnie
took the sock --
to carry stolen treasure in
with!
He had to whack Bebe to keep him
from squealing.
Then, he pinned the rap
on me.
Bebe's dead?
Listen, N.E.P.T.R., you better
lay low for a while.
I'm gonna go find Ronnie.
I've got a score to settle.
N.E.P.T.R.:
Hey, BMO.
We should hang out more.
We're both robots.
No, N.E.P.T.R.
I am notlike you.
JÈ [ dramatic organ music plays ] È
- Ronnie?
- Evening, BMO.
[ gasps ]
Don't worry, buddy.
You're off the hook.
We know it was Ronnie
who killed Bebe
and snatched the treasure.
[ meows ]
We found this confession on him
after the shootout.
Hmm.
What about the sock?
Forget the sock, BMO.
The case is closed.
Let it go, buddy.
It's over.
Maybe he was right,
but | just couldnÕt shake
the feeling that, somehow,
this case had slipped
right through my fingers.
Lipstick?
[ gasps ]
o [ up-tempo music plays ] >
Ohh! Ohh!
J [ slow saxophone music plays ] È
Lorraine!
BMO?
Get back here with that
treasure, Lorraine!
Sorry, BMO.
| earned this loot.
Those chumps were not
framing themselves.
See you around, BMO.
Lorraine! Wait!
What about the sock,
Lorraine?
Oh. That old thing?
| hid that where no one would
ever find it --
in our secret
grown-up kissing spot.
Remember?
- [ giggles ]
It was good to see you again,
BMO.
'Til next time.
[ clucks ]
'Til next time, Lorraine.
You see, man?
That was really fun.
You don't need
two socks to have fun.
Yeah. | guess.
But maybe it would have been
more fun with two socks.
[ sighs ]
Finn! Finn!
| know where your socKk is.
Huh?
It was in your pillow
this whole time. See?
Whoa!
[ laughs ]
Right on, BMO!
Ronnie the Mouse stole it,
but Lorraine Chicken set him up
to kill Bebe.
But the flatfoots
busted Ronnie,
and Lorraine skedaddled
with the loot.
But BMO solved the case!
Yay, BMO!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yay!
Yay, BMO!
Our chicken's name
is Lorraine?
She's red-hot like
pizza supper.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!