[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D the fun will never end È
D It's Adventure Time È
Hmm?
[ laughs ]
Gleebull baybelgrapes!
You're just in time.
Baybel cuber spoon to watch
an incaldrible adventure
from days of old
on my holo-pyramid viewer.
Five stories, each relating to
one special theme.
See if you Graybels can guess
the theme
by the end
of the episode, okay?
Now sit back, relax,
and enjoy the show.
FINN: All right, Beemo.
We'll be back in an hour.
You sure you don't need anything
from the grocery kingdom?
No, | don't need anything.
Thank you.
Okay, goodbye, Finn and Jake.
Bye, Beemo.
Yeah, see you later,
Beemo.
[ door closes ]
[ grunting ]
Finn? Jake?
Well, hello there!
Oh, hello.
Who are you?
My name is Football.
What's yours?
- | am Beemo.
- Beemo, are you a robot?
[ gasps ]
Oh, no, Football.
| am a little living boy.
On!
That sounds wonderful, Beemo.
Will you teach me
about being alive?
Yes, Football.
Watch me.
Oh!
[ gasps ]
Pee-ing!
Oh, Beemo!
That's fantastic!
Oh, thank you, Football!
It's really nothing!
JAKE:
What the?
You see, man?
| told you.
This is nuts.
Plus he's using my toothbrush.
No, man -- that's my
toothbrush.
BOTH:
Ugh!
"Prove that Beemo does weird
junk when nobody is around.Ó
Check!
High five, buddy!
[ whoosh!]
[ smack! smack! ]
That was pretty weak.
Yeah, | was thinkin'
the same thing.
- Give it another go?
- Yeah.
That was better.
But we can do better.
You mean even better!
Let's back on up
and run at each other.
Okay.
Ready? Go!
Rrrrrr!
Uhhhhhh!
BOTH:
Yah!
Ohh, it kind of stings.
| like the pain.
Let's do another one!
Ready?
Yeah!
S £:EEEEEED
- Whoooooooo!
- Yaaaaaaaah!
- Whooooo0000!
[ smack!!!]
- Jake!
- Yeah?
| know how we can do the most
ultimate high five ever!
You've gone crazy mad
with power lust...
and I'm lovin' it!
You ready to do this,
dude?
JAKE: I've been ready this
whole time, dude!
Just waiting on you to
say when you're --
Super ultimate
high five, go!
JAKE: Gah!
[ grunts ]
Whooooo!
BOTH:
WEEEEEEEEEEELL
Ugh!
A glass of delicious
nourishing water for milady.
Ahh!
[ groans ]
[gasps]
Oh, yes!
Mwah!
Oh, man.
Uh...
oh, boy.
Oh...
oh...
oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Onh...
oh, whoa, oh, my glob...
ohh...oh.
Oh, glob.
Ch-e-e-e-eese.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
Ah.
[ squeaks ]
Ha ha!
Jingo jango!
Yeast on third,
flour on first,
swell the dough,
fit to burst!
Aw0000000000!
[ splat! ]
[ whoosh! bash! ]
Well, this is it,
Cinnamon Bun --
the most perfect sandwich that
has ever existed
or ever will exist
within the confines of
space-time.
Will you do the honors?
Okay.
But -- but you --
you didn't --
you didn't even
taste it!
[ belching ]
[ smacks lips ]
Thanks, Princess.
Peace out.
FINN:
WhEEEL
[ keyboard plays ]
[ Ice King humming ]
[ sniffs ]
Blegh!
Gunther, something stinks.
[ sniffs ]
Gunther, do you smell that?
Gunther, stop playing
the keyboard!
[ sniffs ]
Smells like
it's coming from...
[ sniffs ]
Gunther, are you blowing it up
in here?
You are nasty, Gunther.
You got a nasty booty, mister!
NEEY
Aw, don't be sad, stinky.
Come with daddy
and I'll make it all better.
Goodbye, Gunther!
Sorry, sweetie, but I'm never
gonna get any princesses
if you're stanking up
the place!
[ sniffs ]
Blegh!
It still stinks in here!
What the heck?!
Where's that smell
coming from?!
[ sniffs ]
Oh, it's me.
| smell horrible.
Scrub, penguins!
Scrub harder!
We are not stopping until
the stench is completely gone!
[ whistling ]
Clean, clean, clean,
cah-clean.
[ whistling ]
Gunther! Guess what.
It was me who was smelly,
not you.
Wenk.
Sorry, | thought you
had a stank booty, Gunther.
My bad.
Although | have no idea how
my armpits got so stinky.
[ farts ]
JAKE:
Wahhhhhhh!
Everyone's worthless
at this talent show.
I'm totally gonna win
when | sing...
È These lumps È
2 | know you wanna slump up
on these lumps È
> But you can't
'cause you're a chump! È
2 A chu-u-u-u-u-mp! È
You're totally gonna win,
LSP.
Thank you, Marc.
You made 2 out of 10 baskets.
[ unenthusiastic applause ]
Now it's time for me
to kill it!
Hold on, LSP.
You're not up next.
These girls are.
È These lumps! S
2 | know you wanna slump up
on these lumps! È
> But you can't
'cause you're a chump! È
È These lumps! S
È So go on back home,
back to your du-u-u-mp!
Wha?!
That's my song!
[ all cheering ]
CINNAMON BUN: That sounds good
in my eardrums!
WEEEEL]
È These lumps È
2 | know you wanna slump up
on these lumps È
Hey!
We just heard this song!
Quit ripping off our act!
[ crowd chanting "rip-off!" ]
No!
| was gonna do it first!
ALL:
Rip-off! Rip-off!
No!
- Rip-off!
| was gonna do the song first!
Aah!
Huh?
- CROWD: Whoa!
- That's amazing!
Huh?
[ grunts ]
[ gasps ]
Aah!
[ crowd chanting "LSP!" ]
That was the most amazing
thing ever!
LSP wins!
Really?!
Oh, my gosh, you guys!
| just want to thank y'all
so much!
It means so much to me,
and | just wanted to say
.. l...
[ Jake and Finn screaming
in distance ]
[ echoing smack ]
[all gasp ]
[ all cheer ]
Finn and Jake win
the talent show!
What?!
[ breathlessly ]
Awesome.
[ panting ]
That... was... awesome!
Oh-ho! Baybel!
That was easy, wasn't it?
Slimmin'?
I'm glad we all guessed
the theme so easily!
What? What's that?
You haven't guessed it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, pause your viewer now
to think about it
before | blable it
to you.
The theme was
"The Five Senses."
You see?
Look -- Beemo saw his
reflection.
Finn and Jake fouched their
hands together.
The Princess made a fasty
sandwich.
The blue guy smelled bad.
And the other thing
heard music.
Ha ha! What a treat!
Okay, well, I'll see you
crimpy glimmers
on triode
flimpin' the diode!
Ha ha!
È Come along with me È
2 and the butterflies and bees È
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
S and do so as we please >
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!