[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Jake, if | beat you,
you have to call me "sensei"
for a month.
Deal.
Hi, guys.
ALL:
'Sup, Turtle Princess?
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh! Argh!
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
Get your hands off me,
Steven!
Yah!
You too, Chad!
Hey, qirl.
Brought you some
little fruit pies.
Awesome.
How you doing out here?
Turtle Princess,
the men out here
will not leave me alone!
[ sighs ]
It must be nice.
Nah, it's horrible.
They just want me
for my lumps.
[ screeches, caws ]
These lumps aren't for sale,
Billy!
-[ caws ]
- Ugh!
Aren't you sick of men going
after your turtle lumps?
Actually, I've never been
able to work my T-Lumps.
| just know
what | read in books.
[ gasps ]
Hey, you should write a book
telling me how to do it.
Oh, my glob.
Turtle Princess,
| always wanted
to write trashy books
for ladies!
[ hisses ]
Hyah!
Back up off me, Ricky!
Yeah, everyone needs to know
that when | work these lumps,
no man is immune
to their influence.
Jake's ball landed over
here, Beemo!
[ gasps ]
LSP, Finn would be perfect
as the test subject
for your lump studies.
Yay! | win!
Bow to your sensei.
Aw!
[ laughs ]
You got to go undercover
and conduct your lump science
on him.
Prove to the world that even
a white knight like Finn
is no match for the power
of your lumps.
I'l do it --
for the world!
And for you, girl.
Oh, girl!
[ ting! ]
D
Day one -- on my way to Finn
and Jake's.
Side note --
| look fresh to death
with my new dress
and purse.
Mm. Mm. Mm.
Hello?
[ sexily ]
Hey, Jake.
Is Finn home?
Ohh!
'Sup, LSP?
[ normal voice ]
Oh, hey. I'm answering that ad you put out
for the "Adventure Secretary."
What?
Ugh! Hold on. I'll get it.
[ paper rustling ]
Hold on. It's down in there.
Okay, wait. | got it.
Here you go.
"Wanted --
Adventure Secretary."
[ sniffs ]
Smells like fruit pie.
It's nice of you to
want to be our secretary,
but we don't need one.
Dude, look at her.
Mmm. Oh, glob.
Yeah, it's sad.
Come on.
We got to help her.
Ah.
All right, LSP, come inside.
Awesome.
Totally nailed the interview.
[ slurp!]
I'm gonna need
a secretary desk.
Rah!
[ screech! ]
I'm starving!
What's for dinner?!
Oh. Uh...
we got some...
blueberries.
Jake has saltines.
Yuck.
Looks like I'll have to bust out
these cobras
to get a better dinner.
[ sexily ]
Hey, Finn.
You got anything better to eat?
Oh, cool --
old spaghetti.
I'm gonna go heat this up.
Chapter one -- "Gotcha."
Have a good night.
See you in the morning.
Good night, you guys!
Finn is even more overpowered
by my lumps than | thought.
| guess at the end of the day,
it's all about the lumps.
TURTLE PRINCESS RINGTONE:
Hey, girl. Hey --
[ cellphone beeps ]
Hey, girl.
Oh, Turtle Princess, this book
is coming out awesome!
Oh, good, girl.
[ can't wait fo read it.
Thanks, girl.
- Good night, girl.
[ click ]
[ snoring ]
[ crackle ]
[ groggily ]
Huh? What's that?
'Sup, LSP?
What are you guys doing?
We're carrying these
rocks on an adventure
up to the mystery mountains.
Oh, nuh-uh!
| am not gonna carry rocks!
That's okay.
Jake can carry them.
Yep.
Ugh! Fine.
You're welcome, Finn.
Ugh!
My arms weren't meant to carry
SO many rocks, you guys.
Come on, LSP.
You can make it.
Ugggggh!
[ rocks clatter ]
RINGTONE:
Hey, girl. Hey --
[ cellphone beeps ]
Turtle Princess,
you can't call me.
You're gonna blow my cover!
Good morning, girl.
Would you be mad at me
if | ask out Billy,
that vulture who was
hitting on you?
! think he's cute, and...
Hey, LSP, shake a leg.
Can't talk right now, girl.
[ cellphone beeps ]
The Loch of Phantoms.
Princess Bubblegum said
the rocks would show us
the safe path.
This is way too boring
for my book.
Oh! My shoulder strap!
Oh, my orange juice
is coming out!
Ha! Gotch--
huh?
[ splash ]
[ chuckles ]
Jake. "Kerploop!"
JAKE: [ chuckles ]
"Kerploop."
Not... gotcha?
Al right!
[ drip! splat! ]
Ughhh!
This place is plops, Finn!
We can meet you back
at the tree house later, if you want.
That weird light.
[ shimmer! ]
Hey, Finn!
Finn, my dress is slipping!
Huh?
Listen, LSP, we gotta
be careful.
Whooooo!
My dress!
- No, LSP! It's not safe!
- Aaah! Don't look!
He-e-e-e-e-y!
Oh.
Hey, Fi-i-i-nn.
[ knock on wall ]
She's stuck in there!
We gotta bust through
this wall!
[ shing! knock! knock! ]
[ clang! knock! ]
| knew you couldn't
resist me, Finn.
Oh, lump.
| took it too far.
[ whish! ]
[ gasps ]
My powerful lumps have turned
Finn into a grody monster!
Get away, Finn!
Aah! No!
I CEEEEEEEEEEEE L
Hyah!
Aah! I-l can't look!
[ whoosh!]
Aah!
[ both breathing heavily ]
That was so crazy!
What just happened?!
Oh.
Um, Bubblegum sent us
on a quest
to destroy these
cursed mirrors.
Evil stuff happens
when you look into them.
Oh, glob.
| had to look,
'cause | looked so good.
LSP, you don't need a mirror
to know you look good.
You're beautiful
on the /nside.
Like...
your brain and stuff.
Thanks for saying that stuff.
And for saving me
from those mirror-yous.
That was pretty nice.
Okay, time to write.
Gonna make this...
trashy.
Turtle Princess will be all...
[ as Turtle Princess ]
"Oh, my gosh!
Number-one best seller!"
[ normal voice ]
Heh heh. Yeah.
[ rustling in distance ]
What is he doing out there?
Sometimes,
after an adventure,
he likes to sit out there
and think.
RINGTONE:
Hey, girl. Hey --
[ cellphone beeps ]
- Hello?
- Hey, girl.
Are you almost done
with your book?
Oh!
I'm working on it.
I've been doing so much
research.
Did Finn fall victim
to your lumps?
Um... yeah.
Great! Bring in your manuscript
right away.
Click!
Yeah... a book
about how I'm hot
and Finn only wants --
he's so... hot.
[ gasps ]
[ laughs ]
Old spaghetti.
"Kerploop."
You're beautiful
on the /nside.
Finn has the hottest lumps,
but his lumps are
on the /nside.
Aaaargh!
He's great!
Uh... bye, LSP.
[ thunder crashes ]
This isn't what you said
it'd be about.
| know. | --
| love it!
Oh, my glob!
[ scribble! ]
[ caws ]
Finn, you've probably been
wondering
where I've been
for the last few hours.
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah, | have.
Finn, | was never really
your secretary, Finn.
| was writing a book
about how you were
a slave to my lumps
'cause I'm so hot, Finn!
Oh. Okay.
But you're the one
who's hot, Finn!
Wow. Uh... thanks!
No. Thank you.
LSP, you're wearing
garbage for clothes!
Gotcha.
Aah!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!