[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ laughter ]
Oh, man!
All right. What's next?
Let's see.
First, we visit Tree Trunks
for apple pie,
and then we go to Bubblegum's
science music thing.
Wait -- what about the
movie at the drive-in?
That's after we make
dream sandwiches.
Whoo! Let's go!
Apple pie!
Whoo!
[ humming ]
FINN:
Tree Trunks!
Huh?
-T.T.
- Tree Trunks!
Oh, my, look who's here.
Yoo-hoo!
Whoa!
Oh, yeah!
Howdy, Jake. Howdy, Finn.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
| never really left.
Mr. Pig's been so kind,
helping me [giggles]
tend to my rose garden.
[ both laugh ]
BOTH:
Hmm.
Cool.
Cool, cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
[ both laugh ]
Oh, you.
Where's the apple pie,
Tree Trunks?
Yeah, my stomach is
jonesin' for it bad.
[ stomach rumbles ]
Oh, you all are so early that
| haven't even started.
Ahh, ha.
| love her so much.
Whoa! You love her?
What? No!
You just said
you love her.
You're crazy.
Dude, come on.
We heard you.
[ sighs ]
| think | am in
love with her!
But | don't know
how to go about it.
Dude, you should just
tell her how you feel.
Whew.
TREE TRUNKS:
What are you boys chatting about?
Hmm?
Uh-huh. All right. Okay.
[ clears throat ]
Miss Tree Trunks, maÔam, today
| wish to speak my feelings.
Mr. Pig, what's going on?
[ inhales deeply ]
When | see you, my heart
beats like a choo-choo train.
When you stand near me, | get
SO nervous, | cannot move...
Ohhh.
[ sniffs ]
[ crunch!]
Mm, that's good.
TREE TRUNKS:
Shush.
| feel the same.
| have a feeling
that this feeling
is what others call "love."
What should we do, then?
We should hug.
Tree Trunks, you gonna
bring some apple pie to
Princess Bubblegum's thing?
Uh, yeah, Jake, yeah.
Well, okay.
See ya later, then.
BOTH:
Mmm.
[ instruments clanking ]
[ keyboard plays ]
Bonk, beep, woomp, wowoow,
bing-bong, shoo,
da-be-dop-dop, ooh.
[ stomach rumbles ]
Where is she?
[ keyboard plays ]
You givin' me a
back rub, Bro?
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmmmmmraa!
Is that...
[ gasps ]
It's Tree Trunks!
[ panting ]
Pie! Pie!
Lay it right here!
Oh, Jake, | tried
to bake an apple pie,
but this cutie kept
distracting me.
[ both giggle ]
[ smooching ]
No apple pie?!
This is making
me uncomfortable.
They are
snuggling too long.
What is happening?
| forgot my glasses.
[ crowd grumbles,
dissonant music plays ]
Huh? Oh, gross.
[ music stops ]
[ panting ]
Hyah!
Break it up! Break it up!
Okay, the love show is over.
Princess, please continue.
Hmm.
[ upbeat music plays ]
[ whimpering ]
This is too much!
[ gasping ]
Aaaaah! Aaaah!
It's driving me crazy!
Cinnamon Bun, do something!
Okay.
Hey, everyone!
The concert is over!
That's not what | --
The concert's over, Princess!
[ crowd grumbles,
dissonant music plays ]
Princess, how's about a slow
song so me and my man
can dance cheek-to-cheek?
[ both humming ]
Hmph!
Err!
Why is everybody givin'
me the hairy eyeball?
Y'all are too affectionate.
It makes people feel bothered
when you and the pig flaunt
your affection in public.
They don't want us to
flaunt what we have?
You two need to hide your love,
or else you'll end up making
the whole world throw up.
BOTH: We promise to keep
our affection hidden.
Thank you.
Have you seen my other shoe?
| think | saw
it in the closet.
[ smooching ]
Aah! Under my shoe?!
Outta here!
[ baby crying ]
[ gasps ]
[ smooching ]
This carriage is for babies!
For babies!
[ smooching ]
Nice stacks of sandwiches.
You shouldn't have
bought so many flavors.
| had to make a sandwich for
each flavor and for each flavor
combination.
I'm making a cheese sandwich.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch!
Mwah!
Ugh.
Tree Trunks! Pig! Come on!
We're trying to hide our love,
but it's so difficult.
[ munching ]
Try harder!
Doesn't look like Tree Trunks
and Pig are around.
Yeah, looks like
the coast is clear.
[ projector whirs ]
Look at this cup!
Now look at #A/s cup!
Look at this one!
[ smooching ]
Oh, man!
[ sighs ]
Just try to ignore it
and watch the movie.
| can't ignore that!
[ crowd groaning, shouting ]
[ smooching ]
Stop!
Tree Trunks, this has
gone on long enough.
No more spending time with
the Pig unless you do it...
inside your own home.
But, Finn,
an unmarried couple
living together
under one roof --
that's indecent!
Then why don't you
two just get married?
We don't want to rush things.
- Marriage is a big step.
- We need time to get
to know each other.
Then | guess we
only have one option.
All right.
You can't do this.
Wait.
No! Stop!
[ crowd cheers ]
Take them away!
Sweet meat!
Little dove!
Sorry, Tree Trunks.
[ crying ]
So, where do you live?
I'm homeless.
Oh.
[ sighs ]
I guess I'll just go
back to eating criminals.
[ glug! glug! glug! ]
Ugh!
Guh! | miss her!
TREE TRUNKS:
[ sighs ]
| don't know what I'm
gonna do without him, Finn.
Why don't you make apple pie
to take your mind off of it?
[ squish! ]
[ squish! squish! squish! ]
D> Dream of love
J Is it really over? È
JÈ Can | overcome
these tears? )
> | close my eyes )
D Feel that he's
still with me È
2 Still standing
with me here
D> Dream of love
> Are we truly parted? )
È Must this pig
forever walk alone? )
2 In my dreams,
our love is just a dream to me )
> But in my heart, it lives
and breathes and grows )
2 And even though we ain't
allowed to be together )
> | cross my heart
and promise to be true )
È Well, I'm still loving you, girl S
È From halfway 'cross
this great big world!
2 And in my dreams, I'm holdin'
hands with yo-0-0-0-0-0-u J
BOTH:
D> Dream of love
2 It's only a dream of love È
S Dream of lo-0-0-0-0-0-0-ve )
2 It's only a dream
D> Of love È
> | close my eyes and
feel his arms around me È
2 In my dreams,
he's not so far away JÈ
Go to him.
Go.
[ gasps ]
[ smooching ]
I'm freaking out!
[ crowd groaning |
You know what?
I like it.
It's nice.
Yeah.
[ smooching continues ]
Mmm.
Apple pie, I've been
waitin' to kiss you all day.
Mwah!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!