[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Yo, Beemo, you done
charging up that phone, or what?
[ grunting ]
Almost... finished.
[ grunts ]
JAKE:
Thanks, Beemo.
All right, man,
we're gonna figure this out
right... now.
[ cellphone beeping ]
Yo, yo, yo, yo, check it!
This is Jake
on my camera phone!
Wh-o-o0-0-0-0-0-0-0a!
Whoa, whoa!
Yo, Finn! Say hi
to my new camera phone.
What up, camera phone?
BOTH:
[ ululating ]
[ whoosh! whoosh! whoosh! |
BOTH:
Marceline!
You guys want to come party in
The Nightosphere with me?
I'm visiting with my dad,
and it's crazy boring.
Whoa!
Wait a minute, Marceline.
Last time | saw your dad,
/ sliced open his soul sack.
Oh, no, he's ftotally chill now.
Okay, but I'm keeping
an eye out for your old man
in case he pulls any...
[ raspy voice ]
sneak afttacks.
[ chuckles |
Don't be a wiener dog.
Jake, you coming?
Whoo! Yeah, baby!
[ cellphone beeping ]
All right, so...
this is
The Nightosphere, | guess.
/t looks banaynays.
Marceline says they got fons
of crazy ways out here.
[ guitar strumming,
tambourine rattling |
Right, Marceline?
Marceline!
Marcy!
[ imitates duck quacking ]
[ chuckles mischievously |
ABADEER: There you are, Marceline.
[ music stops ]
- Hmm?
- Rrragh!
V- CEEEEEEEEEEEL
Oh. Hello, dog.
Hello, Finn.
Stay away from me,
old man!
[ tambourine rattles ]
[ chuckles ]
Nice one.
Now, Finn.
Come on, there's no
bad blood here.
Come here.
Let's bury the hatchet.
See how I'm not killing you?
[groans ]
Dad, stop.
All right.
/ don't want to embarrass
my little girl.
So, young lady, have you
thought about my offer?
Ugh!
JAKE:
What offer, Marceline's dad?
[ chuckles ]
! want Marceline to take over
The Nightosphere --
finally join
the family business.
Business?
Dad, what do you even do?
Oh! Ha! Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Check it out sweetie.
See how chaotic it is
out there?
[ fwoosh! ]
How everyone's confused
and frustrated?
The Nightosphere
/s sustained by chaos.
Eh, I just don't see myself
doing this biz.
Okay, but | know
you'll come around eventually.
Or maybe you won't.
/ don't know.
You're an independent woman.
[ yawns ]
- Aaah!
Well, I'm gonna take
a nappy.
Oh! | almost forgot.
[rip!]
- Dad!
- Whoops!
[laughs ]
You should put this amulet on.
Itll grant you wishes for,
like, ponies --
or whatever kids like.
Dad, I'm 1,000 years old.
Hal! Yes, you are, sweetie.
Daddy'Õs little monster.
[ footsteps depart |
Look, letÕs just play
something, okay?
Okay.
/| know you just wanna give
your little girl the world .>
S but, Daddy, I'm not just
your little girl >
S I've got my own life,
/ got my own plans .
/| hope you understand
and like the way that | am
S 'Cause | want your respect,
and | want to be here .>
S but | don't want fo rule
The Nightosphere .
[sighs ]
Pffft! Whatever, dad.
Ooh--
CEEEEEEG
[grunting ]
[ laughs evilly ]
- Jake, grab the amulet!
Oof?!
- JAKE: Ow! My hippocampus!
[ laughing evilly ]
[ cellphone beeping ]
Well, that explains
how we got amnesia'ed.
But what about banana?
Hey, man, there's
another video.
[ cellphone beeping ]
[ grunts ]
We got mad prison-overcrowding
down here, fellas.
So, | got to put you
in the cage with the stuff.
Sorry about that.
But, you know, not really.
[ gate slams,
belches ]
Oh, my stomach!
[ grunting ]
[ pb
ft! pbft! ]
[ sighs ]
Yeeeee!
That amulet's
controlling Marceline!
We have to go back
and help her!
We're gonna get back using
that one portal spell we know.
Hah!
Maloso vobiscum
et cum spiritum!
Whoa, dude.
She told us never
to come back.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Jake, can you
turn into a gross demon?
Mm-hmm.
Grosser!
REEEEEER]
[ deep voice ]
What's your disguise?
- Paper-plate mask, yo!
- Nice!
[ panting ]
Let's go! Hyah!
Who's next? Who's next?
Uh... me,
my lord Aberdeer.
What do you desire,
cowering speck --
pain, pleasure,
or weird punishment?
Uh... pleasure?
No! Weird punishment!
[ zap! zap! zap! ]
[ vomiting ]
And what do you desire --
p.," "p,"
or "w.p."?
... pain?
Okay.
Aw.
Come on! Come on! Next!
I'm just gonna go.
You sure, dude?
Don't you want abs?
Yeah, give me abs.
[ laughs ]
| think we can
charge up there
and rip the amulet
off her neck.
[ panting ]
[ gasps |
Hey! What are you guys doing?!
You can't run up to the front
of the line!
These good people have been
waiting forever!
Shame on you both!
Everybody, shame them!
[ crowd booing ]
Boo, sir!
| boo what you're doing!
Step back -- back!
You will not
cut the line again!
You stay back here
and wait your turn
like the rest of us!
Understand?!
- Yeah, okay! Okay!
I'll be watching you.
Sorry, dude.
You got out of line.
Dang it!
BOTH:
[ groaning ]
[ gasps ]
Who are you?!
Waah!
Don't kill us, Marceline!
It's us --
Finn and Jake!
Your friends,
remember?!
- Eh.
- FINN: Oh, grob!
[ growling ]
Aaaaaah!
Run!
Marceline.
What are you doing?
Just grabbing a midnight
snack.
It's Marceline.
That's her out there!
| know.
Isn't it fantastic?
No!
We have to save her!
- Save her?
- From the amulet!
But this is what
I've always wanted --
my girl following
in her daddy's footsteps.
But that's
not what she wants!
That's balderdash, baby.
The wearer of the amulet is
filled with chaotic evil,
which is how | grew up,
SO...
[ chomping ]
Maybe we can get these
dudes to help us.
[ all murmuring ]
[ sighs ]
[ normal voice ]
These guys won't help you.
They're all complacent
sheeple.
[ beatboxes ]
Wait. That's it!
We're gonna freestyle
a political rap
to get these guys to rise
out of their systemized
demon apathy!
Okay.
[ beatboxing ]
[ rapping ]
Yeah. Unh.
Political rap!
Yo, yo!
Demon apathy!
Yo, zappity!
Get ready!
Government!
Where you went!
Yo! Farmer's market!
Ride bikes! Get on it!
Geodesic domes!
Sciencel!
You heard?
[ all cheering ]
| never thought of it
that way before.
This system is
broke, yo!
[ crowd chanting "freedom!" ]
Marceline.
[ grunts ]
[ all chomping ]
Ugh. Sick.
- Jake! The tree house!
- Aaaah!
I'm too freaked out to move,
Finn!
These demons
are nibbling my legs!
NEVCRELCE
No, Finn!
You'll be filled
with chaotic evil!
Aaaaah!
[ gulping ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
[ roaring ]
[ moans ]
FINN: [ deep voice ]
Marceline.
No one leaves
The Nightosphere!
[ roars ]
[ normal voice ]
Wh-0-0-0-0a!
Oh!
ABADEER:
Marceline!
Uh, | wonder
what happened to him.
Kids these days.
Am | right?
Dude. Seriously.
Dad, you tricked me.
Dad, that sucks!
| know. I'm sorry.
But | thought
you'd want to --
want to make
your old man proud
and, you know, take over
The Nightosphere.
Yeah, | want you
to be proud!
| want you to be proud
of me!
No, | didn't mean --
baby, of course
I'm proud of you.
Dad.
And your friends,
they're all right!
That political rap?
Pretty great!
Okay, okay.
| got to go now, dad.
Woof! What a nightmare.
Man, Finn, my dad
actually likes you.
[ chuckles ]
[ whimpers ]
| don't want to hang out
with you anymore.
- [ moans ]
- Finn?
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!