[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
You gonna do the thing again?
Yeah, man.
[ whoosh!]
[ grunting ]
[ snap! snap!]
What?
Nice.
Hey, Princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody.
[ cheering ]
Finn's herel
Yay!
[ dance music playing ]
[ indistinct talking ]
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
[ panting ]
Man, dancing is rough.
Yeah.
I'm having some
sweat issues here.
Il go get us
some snack-ity juice.
Hey, man. I'm Jake.
I'm Jake.
Hmm.
FINN:
Check it out, Jake.
| got us some peanuts...
and punch!
[ growling ]
[ laughs ]
[gulps]
[ choking ]
Pbht! Choking!
Don't give up on me, man.
[all gasp ]
[ choking ]
Hyah!
[ burps ]
[ gasping ]
[ cheering ]
Yay!
Whoa, Finn. Nice book!
Yeah. It's pretty cool.
It's the Enchiridion --
The Hero's Handbook.
[ gasping ]
Hey, guy.
Are you all right?
[ growls softly ]
[ laughs ]
He's all good.
Everybody get back
to your dancing.
[ cheers ]
[ owl hooting ]
Uh, Finn?
| think that bear
is following us home.
Whoa.
[ chuckles ]
| think you're right.
Hey, bear.
You gonna come
hang out with us?
What do you say, bear?
[ growls ]
[gulps]
[ chuckles ]
Awesome.
| don't know, Finn.
This guy seems
kind of weird.
Yeah.
He's totally weird.
[ laughs ]
[ growls ]
Hmm.
FINN:
Jake. Hey, Jake.
FINN: Jake?
- What?
FINN: Come here.
You got to check this out.
Yeah, okay.
Check this out, man.
This bear is tops blooby!
[ sighs ]
Watch this.
-Ah...
-ah...
- ...choo!
[ laughs ]
You got to try this, Jake.
He does everything | do.
[ slurp!]
[ grunting softly ]
[ giggles ]
Oh, stop.
[ laughs ]
Come on, Jake. Try it.
It's awesome!
[ chuckles ]
Um, yeah, okay.
Sweepy, sweepy, sweepy!
Sweep, sweep, sweep!
Sweeping.
[ growls ]
[ laughs ]
He's got me down pat.
Sweeping's weak.
Mm.
Sweeping weak.
Whoa!
This guy's all right.
This guy just busted
me in my chops, Finn.
Hey, come on.
He's just a bear.
He don't know nothing.
Mm. Yeah, | guess.
Well, anyway,
it's getting pretty late.
Probably time for everyone to go
back home to their own houses.
Yeah, | guess you're right,
NELGH
It is pretty late.
He should probably
stay here tonight.
You can sleep in the bathtub.
Brathtrub.
[ laughs ]
Sleep in.
"Brathtrub!"
[ laughs ]
This guy's tops blooby.
[ snoring ]
[ snapping ]
Finn?
[ snoring ]
[ snapping ]
[ fingers snapping ]
What?
Hey, Princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody.
What? Hey.
Hey, Princess Bubblegum.
Hey, everybody.
What? Hey.
[ chomp! ]
Aah! What are you doing?
Shh. Come with me.
You got to see something.
This bear's wiggy, Finn.
He's wearing your clothes and
dancing around all crazy.
That sounds rad, man.
What?!
No. Just --
[ groans ]
[ snoring ]
Aw, man!
[ sighs ]
Oh, you got to
believe me, Finn.
| swear.
He was, like, all wigged out.
He was dancing.
[ groans ]
| do believe you.
Oh.
It's just, you know,
who cares?
Dancing, wearing clothes --
he ain't hurting nobody.
He's just doing it up,
you know?
He's just cool,
and he likes my style.
That ain't a crime.
(\[o}
[ chuckles ]
| guess not.
Okay, great.
I'm going back to bed.
You coming, smart guy?
Yeah, okay.
[ chuckles ]
[ snoring ]
[ grunts ]
[ slurps ]
Ahh!
You're not even a
little weirded out by this?
No, man.
He's just doing
his instincts.
He's just doing his instincts.
He's like a parrot
or chameleon or something.
...like a parrot or
chameleon or something.
He's funny.
Anyway, | got to go
pick up Beemo from soccer.
I'll be back soon.
And remember --
don't eat my special Finn cakes.
Finn only.
Yeah, | get it.
You don't need to tell me that
every time you make Finn cakes.
Bah!
Hey, what are you doing?
[ gasps ]
Why, you little...
Trying to set me up, eh?
You think you're so smart,
but this time, I'm ready.
[ laughing ]
[ humming ]
Oh, my Glob! What?!
Jake!
You ate all my Finn cakes.
What the stink?!
Uh, nope.
The bear did it,
and I've got proof.
| taped the whole thing!
The bear ate all my cakes,
and you just sat there
and watched him do it?!
What's wrong with you!?
Uh, what? No, man.
He was trying to
frame me, Finn!
He's trying to
steal your identity!
Why can't you grok that!?
[ sighs ]
FINN:
He's a bear, Jake. He's a wild animal.
He doesn't know things.
He just does stuff.
He's cool.
JAKE:
Oh, fine.
Well, that's just great.
Then you and M.C. Cool friend
can go stink it up together at
your stupid, cool Finn
party all by yourselves,
'Ôcause I'm not going!
Wait -- what?
What party?
What? Your party, man.
Tonight?
In the woods?
But | didn't make this flyer.
Huh?
Well, who did, then?
[ gasps ]
BOTH:
The bear.
| knew it.
[ cheering ]
See, dude?
He's not just
jacking your style,
he's jacking your whole you!
Jacking yo' you up.
What the what?
He got in close
and used you.
Now he's feeding nuts
to your ex-girlfriend.
Sure, I'll have another
[muffled] nut.
She's not my --
we never went steady.
Bleh.
[ laughs ]
He's trying to replace you,
and he's already got everyone
convinced he's you!
He didn't really like you.
He used you.
Troops brooby!
Troops...
[ snap! ]
Ow! Not cool, man.
[ gasps ]
You're not me.
You're just a bear
acting like me.
[ crying ]
It's okay, everyone.
The imposter is gone.
Finn, nobody really
thought the bear was you.
Wait. What?
We just thought it was one
of your jokey-joke jokes.
Hey! Hey, bear!
Wait up, guy.
[ whimpering ]
Hey, | -- |
didn't mean to make you feel
so bad about yourself.
I'm really sorry about that.
Me, too.
But you're a super-rad bear,
so why not just be you?
| want be hero like you!
Aww.
| guess he's got a
heart of gold after all.
Hold on, bear.
| got something for you.
It's the Enchiridion --
The Hero's Handbook.
Everything you need to
know about being a hero
is in this book.
Take it and learn.
Finn, are you nuts?
We can't give that book away.
It's, like, crazy important.
Whatever, man.
We never use it except for,
like, sitting on it when the
grass is wet and stuff.
Drink your fill of knowledge.
Someday, you'll be a great hero.
Thank you, Finn.
Thank you.
[ panting ]
Ooooh!
EVIL VOICE:
Did you bring the book?
Yes. One step closer.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!