[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ all cheering ]
> [ dance music plays ] È
[ laughs ]
Dancing is cool.
Check it out, y'all.
Ah!
[ laughs ]
This one is called
"The Worm."
[ grunting ]
Aaaaaaah!
[ birds chirping ]
Ack! Ack! Ack!
Aaaaah!
[gulps]
[ gasps ]
[ yawns ]
Oh, no.
It's crazy-far.
[ muttering ]
Okay.
Now easy does it.
Easy...
CER
Hey, man!
It's safe in here!
- Eeeee....
- You can hide in here!
Oh. Shoot, man.
Uh-oh.
Eeeeeeeeeceeeceeee!
Ee-ee-ee-ee!
Eeeeeeeeeceeeceeeeceeeee!
Ugh!
[ crack ]
Ugh.
Oh, no! My face!
Finn! Jake!
[ echoing ]
Kiss my face!
[ sighing ]
Ohh.
So, this is the pits.
| hear that, friend.
Do you mind if | wallow
with you a bit?
I'm a bubble.
Okay.
Nothing stopping a bubble.
[ sighs ]
That's what they say.
Looks like you've given up
on things.
I'm thinking about giving up
on things myself.
I've been lost in this
wilderness a long time.
Maybe you and me can wait here...
to get eaten by a carnivore.
No, Bubble.
| know two heroes
who can help you.
- You do?
-Yes.
Help me get to my home and...
and we will help you
find yourhome.
Your friends sound great!
They are! They are huge!
Well, then, what are we
waiting for?
Nothi-i-i-i-ng!
Hey, so, tell me
about your home, BMO.
| live in a tree house.
Unh!
It's really funny.
- Cool.
Yeah. Oofl!
What about yourhome?
My home?
| think that my home is very
large and very beautiful,
but | can't pin down
these memories.
It...
haunts me.
Oops!
| wasn't listening
to your story.
[ clunk ]
What was that?
[ metal rumbles ]
It's a carnivore
waiting to eat us!
- No!l
- Don't worry, Bubble.
I've got everything
under control.
Ugh! Ehh.
[ gasps ]
It's a baby!
[ coos ]
What's a baby doing
in the wilderness?
He must be lost --
like us!
We should take him with us.
Maybe we can help him
find his home, too.
What a handsome baby.
Handsome baby.
Bubble, what do you think
our baby's name is?
How about...
Sparkle?
No, | think he looks
like a Ricky.
Hmm.
Oh! Bubble! Ricky! Look!
[ wind howls ]
| have bad news.
The bridge doesn't have
guardrails.
| don't think we should
cross it, then.
[ creature howls,
birds cawing ]
| don't think we have
any choice!
I'm sure that really /s
a carnivore this time!
Ricky, you should go first!
[ coos ]
You are so beautiful, and...
| love you.
Go, Ricky!
[ coos ]
Okay, Ricky,
slow and steady!
[ coos ]
Ricky? Ricky!
Ricky!!
- Sparkle!!
[ inhales deeply ]
Bravery!
Oh, n-0-0-0-0-0-0-0!
[ coos ]
One second, sweetie!
Hmm.
A deadly waterfall!
BMO!
Bubble!
You have to save our lives!
Ohh...
maybe | can hold out
this leaf.
[ grunting ]
[ bird chirps ]
[ grunts ]
[ coos ]
Thank you, Bubble!
| think my batteries
are wet.
[ electricity crackles ]
Goodbye.
[ coos ]
[ grunts ]
[ yawns ]
Good morning, everyone.
| didn't have any dreams.
[ fussing ]
He looks fussy.
Maybe he's hungry.
My hungry baby.
What am | going to do
with you?
[ smooches ]
Potato.
[ crying ]
Eat your potato, Ricky.
[ slurping ]
[ creature howls ]
[ gasps ]
It's the carnivore!
Everybody! Hide!
Psst! Ricky! Please! Hide!
Ugh! Ungh!
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
Oh, Ricky!
Ungh!
Help me out here!
[ wailing ]
[ grunting ]
[ playing call ]
[ gasps ]
My baby!
[ playing call ]
| was so worried about you,
Sparkle.
- No!
- Hey!
Ricky, no!
No, no, no!
[ grunts ]
No! No!
BMO, that's his mom!
Let go!
Ehh...
[ sobs ]
My beautiful baby.
[ coos ]
You should be ashamed
of yourself!
Vro-o0-o0-0-om!
Zo-0-0-om!
Sho-0-0-om!
Hey!
The path ahead
looks pretty clear.
And there were these --
uh, there...
BMO? Are you okay?
| am sad, Bubble.
I miss baby Ricky.
I miss him so much already.
And | miss Finn,
and | miss Jake.
And | got dirt all in my
butt circuits.
And, Bubble...
- Yes, BMO?
I-I don't think I'm ever
gonna get home again!
[ sobs ]
Don't cry.
Sparkle is safe now,
and we did that.
Thanks to us,
he's gonna grow up
and be anything
he wants to be --
a strapping horse whisperer
or a sexy hit man
or whatever.
And things are looking up
for us, too.
| saw some bugs up ahead
who look pretty with it.
[ gasps ]
Maybe they can give us
directions or something.
Oh! Oh, my gosh!
Oh! Oh! Oh, Bubble!
- What?
- | know those guys, Bubble!
Those are my homeboys --
my homeboys!
Those are my homeboys!
We are close to my home!
[ gasps ]
Yay!
Come on, BMO!
[ laughs ]
Yay! Oof!
Yay!
[ both laughing ]
It's been so long!
| can't wait to have some
bread and butter!
[ both laugh ]
FINN:
Jake? Is that you at the door?
JAKE:
No, man.
I'm in the kitchen,
making us breakfast.
| call
not-answer-the-door, then.
Oh, all right!
Hang on out there.
I'm coming.
Whoop!
Whoa!
[ crashing ]
Argh! Agh!
Whoa!
N EEEEEEEE]
Might be a minute.
[ crashing continues ]
Um, hey, so, BMO,
since we have a little time,
there's something I've been
wanting to say.
Huh?
| know | might never find
my real/home.
[ gasps ] No, Bubble!
That's not true!
Itis.
| know it is.
But it's -- it's okay.
Because | realized something.
All this time we've been
together, BMO,
| haven't fe/tlost.
I've felt at home.
N R EEEEEEEE]L
[ crash ]
And it's you, BMO,
| feel at home with.
[ gasps ]
So, | thought -- | mean,
if you feel the same way --
| thought we could...
get married.
I-I mean, I'm not even sure what
that means exactly, but --
| do!
Oh, I do! | do!
Oh!
[ laughs ]
- Whoooooo!
- JAKE: Hey, a Bubble!
Pop!
-[gasps ]
- [ laughing ]
- Bubble? Bubble?!
No! No, no, no!
My Bubble! No!
- What's so funny?
- Oh, it's just BMO.
He's pretending to be
all messed up
'cause his bubble got popped.
[ chuckles ]
- [ sobbing ]
Ohhh.
[ chuckles ]
That /s pretty funny!
Oh, Bubble, I'm so sorry
| brought you here.
[ sobbing ]
BUBBLE'S VOICE:
There, there, BMO. If's okay.
Bubble? Is that you?
| hear you in my head,
but | don't see you.
- [ both stifling laughter ]
- Oh, no. Have | gone bananas?
No, BMO. It's okay.
You see, I'm finally free.
| don't understand, Bubble.
No, not Bubble.
Alr.
BMO, I'm Air!
1'd been trapped in that bubble
for so long,
/'d forgotten who | am.
But now I'm finally home.
Yay!
Oh. B-But wait.
Now you don't need me...
to feel...
at home.
No.
See, that's what's so great.
Now we can be together forever,
BMO --
every minute
of every day.
No more privacy.
No more quiet.
No more alone.
Every room you ever go in,
I'll already be there...
waiting...
forever and ever...
until the end of time.
Yayyyyyyy!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!