[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ laughs evilly ]
[ glass shatters |
[ tink! ]
[ laughs ]
Your butt is mine, Joshua!
What? My butt?
Weird.
Where are we?
This is my yoga room.
And this is your new home.
Downward, dog!
Ouch!
Welcome to revenge, Joshua.
You'll never see your
loved ones again.
Everything you need for
survival is booby-trapped.
[ energy crackles ]
Huh.
Now I'm gonna gank your blood
the way you ganked mine!
[ inhales deeply ]
Boo-yah!
How does it feel, dog?
How does it feel that
I've juiced your body
and turned your blood
into Man-dazzle?!
Mm. Not that great.
| feel weird in my skin.
[ laughs ]
Wait. Is that it?
Yeah, but | could
get used to this.
What?! No!
You have to suffer!
Okay.
No "Okay"!
When | say something,
you're supposed
to disagree, okay?
Okay.
[ grumbles ]
You're causing tension
in my neck and shoulders.
I'm gonna go stretch it out.
You stay here and suffer.
Okay.
NELCYS
Drat.
Hmm.
Ah!
[ telephone dialing ]
[ telephone ringing ]
[ speaking Korean ]
Hey, Lady.
Listen, your husband got
abducted by Kee Oth the demon.
[ speaking Korean ]
Jake?
Yeah, your hubby or...
boyfriend or whatever.
[ speaking Korean ]
Yo, my Korean is
not that good.
Can you just
get over here?
We need to find a way to Kee
Oth's dimension, Shipshiyo.
[ speaking Korean ]
All right,
that sounds affirmative.
See you soon. Bye.
[ humming ]
[ snapping fingers ]
> Broke-up dimension,
you're breaking my heart J
2 I'm looking for a broke-up
girl to break me apart È
Just kidding.
| got a girl!
[ snap! creak! ]
Lady Rainicorn!
Yeah!
Mm.
That don't look right.
[ creak! ]
That's better.
[ smooches ]
HIGH PITCHED VOICE:
Excuse me.
Hmm?
Down here.
Hil
Oh, my fun!
| thought you was a rock!
I'm not a rock.
I'm a little buddy!
Can you get off me, please?
Whoops! Sorry.
It's okay.
Cool.
You want to be friends?
I'd like that!
I've never had a friend.
Whoa, seriously?
My species spends its
first 12 years sleeping.
| just woke up today!
[ zap!]
Hello?
I'm just gonna pretend
you're sleeping.
Whoop! She's here.
| thought my body was
hopping up and down,
but | was sitting still.
[ speaking Korean ]
What is it, Lady?
What?
[ speaking Korean ]
Uh...something "skip."
| don't know.
Just play it, BMO.
[ static ]
Jake? Finn? Jermaine?
Whoever is watching this?
Dad!
/ just opened up an
unexplored cavern deep in the
underground-grasslands complex.
Please refer to my
chart system, okay?
I'm in Cave 73-H.
In case | am
overtaken by an enemy,
/ need you fo
retrieve my corpse.
[ static]
Hey, Laady.
You asked me fo
make you a video...
[ speaking Korean ]
BMO, skip! Skip!
...saying JTD won't
change his doggie ways...
[ tape rewinding ]
That should be good.
Okay, I love you, girl.
! hope you liked it.
Bye!
[ smooches |
...over here, you see?
The second half of
the tablet, | believe.
Now, if | put this
together with mine,
/ should be able to create
a portal to the demon
Kee Oth's dimension
and trap him in a
circle of holy wafter.
Okay, here we go.
Perfect!
Okay, lets see...
"Kee Oth zaple myrups pama--"
[ static]
[ both gasp ]
JAKE: Okay, this is scene one,
take one of "Heat Signature 2."
Ready?
Action/
Father, it's been a year
since [ was on the submarine,
but I still hear the screams.
/ was forced fo choose --
the lives of my men
or the entire planet!
What would you do?!
Tell me, father!
I'm a mess, man!
Oh!
Wait, what do | say?
Mm, check, please!
JAKE:
No!
[ static]
Hold on, BMO.
| feel like we need to watch
more of this video for clues,
but you got to
promise me that
I'm not gonna see any
more weird Jake stuff.
[ speaking Korean ]
Okay, high five.
Play it, BMO.
Mm, guess what, Lady.
This dirty dog
needs a bath.
Whoo!
Aaaah!
This stinks!
What do you mean?
Come on, Joshua!
Back in the old days,
you would've been up here
trying to take me apart!
Uh, what?
That's my Dad, Joshua,
back in the old days.
I'm his son, dude.
Shoot.
Where is he?
He's dead, dude.
Don't make me get
emotional about it.
Then why are you being
such a wimp then?
Come on up here and beat
on me like your Dad would.
Okay, that's weird.
What's weird?
You want to get beat up?
That's weird.
I'm not doing
your weird biz.
You won't fight?!
Nope.
[ groans ]
Heh-heh.
What the...
CEEEEEEEEEEE
Oh, my gosh!
[ both grunting ]
Hi. I'm Samantha.
I'm Jay T. T-The dog!
I'm -- I'm Jake.
Only one can
survive my pit!
This bozo tried
stealing my blood, too!
So youse better duke it out
and see who gets to live!
But | haven't seen
a man-dog in years!
And now the universe has
dropped one into my arms.
Whoa, Lady.
No way.
This boy is got.
But fate has brought
us together!
The stars have paired
you with a goddess!
| like the way you talk,
but you are crazy.
Kill or be killed,
you two!
Yes, if I'm so crazy,
then let's fight!
No, girl, we can bounce
out of here.
My friend Finn will
save us any second now.
| don't wait for rescue.
| conquer till
| am conquered...
by love or by the hand
of an adversary.
Well, | guess we're gonna
have to fight then.
Yaah!
[ crunch!]
[ laughs ]
[ splat! ]
[ smash! ]
Okay, take your time.
| got to do my daily
sun salutations.
[ grunting ]
Release me, Joshua!
[ growling ]
I'll show you!
WILEICERCE A
[ gags]
[ coughing ]
Blech/
Dude, your blood is harsh!
[ gulping ]
That's Ôcause | been
drinking so much holy water.
/t's in my blood, sucker!
And naturally, | got to go
to the bathroom like crazy.
Be right back!
If I can't suck you,
I'll suck myself's blood.
WILEICERCE A
[ laughs ]
Taste it, scrub!
[ splash!/]
V- CEEEEEEEEEEEL
[ groaning |
Man, | can't believe it
/ got fo wee-wee again.
[ static ]
[ tape rewinding ]
Would you like to
rate this video?
No time, BMO.
Let's go find the
cave from the video.
Maybe we'll find
more clues there.
[ speaking Korean ]
"Kee Oth zaple myrups
pama mancakes."
[ cracks ]
Whoa.
[ glass shatters |
NELCYS
Yeesh.
Eh?
[ grunting ]
NELCYS
Finn, yes!
Help me!
Jake!
[ speaking Korean ]
This is not hugging!
It's fighting!
Fighting!
Jake, what do | do?
Should I kill him?
With what?!
With this!
Demon blood!
That's right!
Demon blood beats demon!
Uh, that is not correct.
[ laughs evilly ]
Oh, yeah!
Give me that
blood, stupid!
[ inhales deeply ]
W EEEEEEEL
Lady, don't break
the circle of protection!
[ speaking Korean ]
Aw, geez.
He's sucking my
sword off its hilt!
Yeah!
[ laughs ]
Your circle can't
stop my sucking!
Now | have yourdemon blood,
as well!
Exceptit's not
demon blood.
It's a frozen grape juice that
was blessed by the priest.
Cold.
Bless this sword, Fodder!
Mm. Check, please!
[ slurping ]
Mmm. Grapy.
Wait.
Aaaaaaaaaah!
My blood!
Whoo!
Coward!
Whoop!
Hey, hey!
Lady!
Let's go, bros!
Samantha, you can come,
too, | guess.
Very well.
[ glass shatters |
You've returned
me to my world,
so | recant my
oath to destroy you.
You made an oath?
Okay.
Let's fight
again sometime.
Nah, I'll just
stretch into a tree.
Hmm.
Took long enough for you to
stretch out of that pit.
[ speaking Korean ]
Psh! Please. Not even.
Uh, because Kee Oth
was right there!
A-and there were traps.
| didn't have no blood
this whole time,
so I'm totally
out of it.
[ grunts ]
[ both gasp ]
BOTH:
Jake?!
Whew! Sorry.
| got a little
light-headed.
[ speaking Korean ]
| love you, too, Lady.
Yo, guys.
| still love
Flame Princess.
Okay, big hug.
ALL:
Hug!
[ wind gusts ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!