[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's adventure time È
[ snoring ]
[ smacks lips ]
[ footsteps approach ]
Finn! Jake!
| invited some bikini babes
over to dance to this song.
[ slow music plays ]
J ...feel a thousand petals >
2 I'm walking by
cherry blossoms in the sky
It's my favorite song!
It makes me so happy!
[ music continues ]
Uh, why are you not talking?
D> There's so
much to take in È
What?
> Today È
2 I'm humming like washing
machines through the window JÈ
È And feeling glad...
Why are you not talking?!
What happened to
Finn and Jake?!
You have taken
over their bodies!
[ screams ]
[ whimpering ]
[ creak! ]
[ knocking ]
[ pounding ]
[ whimpering, gasping ]
Oh, what should | do?
Oh! Oh!
JÈ Feel so friendly
when you say... È
[ knocking ]
BMO?
[ music continues ]
2 I'm looking
forward to... È
[ clatter! ]
[ dramatic music plays ]
[ music stops ]
[ clonk! clonk! clonk! ]
[ creak! ]
[ pop! ]
[ clonk! clonk! ]
[ pitter! ]
[ twang! ]
[ dramatic music plays ]
[ music stops ]
[ clink! ]
[ all snoring ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ alarm ringing ]
[ soothing music plays ]
[ typewriter keys clacking ]
[ creak! ]
[ slow music plays ]
[ volume increases ]
[ music stops ]
Aah!
Go away!
Where is the real Jake?!
You're a doppelganger, you!
Body taker!
Aaah!
[ growls ]
> Suddenly, I'm... È
BMO?
BMO, are you at home?
BMO, we're here
to dance with you!
[ music continues ]
[ creak! ]
[ tap! tap! tap! ]
[ sniffing ]
[ inhales deeply ]
[ thud! ]
[ clank! ]
Aah!
[ thud! ]
[ click ]
[ slow music plays ]
[ indistinct conversations |
Yeah.
[ flutter! ]
[ chuckles ]
[ music continues ]
2 I'm looking forward to
the chance to meet again È
JÈ But, then again,
it all depends È
[ creak! ]
[ pounding ]
BMO:
No way, fake boys!
| am never coming out!
[ all screaming ]
[ clatter! ]
BMO:
Bikini babes!
They are not Finn and Jake!
Get them!
[ mid-tempo music plays ]
[ thud! ]
[ smack! smack! smack! smack! ]
[ smack! ]
[ creak! ]
Ow! Ow! Okay, fine!
Uncle! Uncle!
Please stop pinching me,
bikini babe!
Oh, | win!
[ sighs ]
You're so disappointed.
[ chuckles ]
Finn? Jake?
For real?
We were just playing
a game, BMO.
It all started this morning when
Jake made a sign that said --
Oh, | don't care.
Let's just party!
[ mid-tempo music plays ]
Party, party, party!
[ howls ]
[ grunting ]
Oh, yeah.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!