[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
FINN:
Hey, Jake.
Do you think you should date
someone just like you
or someone who's, like,
your opposite?
| don't know.
I'm the first come,
first serve kind of guy.
Getin line, ladies.
This Rainicorn thing
can't last forever.
[ laughs ]
| didn't mean that.
Don't spread that around.
- So it's not good...
to weigh somebody's qualities
against your own?
Well, no.
| mean, if you feel something,
you fee/ something.
It's not about personality
matrixels and charts,
it's all about the b-bumps
in your heart.
You can't stop
the pumps and bumps.
Pumps and bumps!
[ Finn laughs ]
[ laughs ]
All right, well, what
about BMO and Ice King?
What about them?
Would they make
a good couple?
Whoa! Wait!
Did BMO say something to you?
No, no, no.
Oh, | see.
You're being weird.
It's not fthat weird.
Come on.
Do what thou swill be
the whole piece of log.
JAKE:
BMO and Ice King?
Yeah!
I'm not coming back.
You're creeping me out.
I'm just thinking out loud.
What, can't think out loud?
Oh, is that what
you're doing?
Yeah, man. [ scoffs ]
Geez, don't be judgy.
- I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
How can you know that?
| can hear it
in your tone.
[ sarcastically ]
You can?
Yeah, wise guy.
Hey, what's that on
your pants?
What?! Not again!
Oh. | don't know.
Whoa, look.
- Crazy.
Careful, dude.
What the --
What the heck?!
Are they alive?
Hey, are you guys
alive?
| don't know, man.
| think they're some kind of
magic toy.
Maybe it's black magic.
Maybe we shouldn't
mess with them.
No, man, look.
That's you!
You're totally shredding
on the viola!
[ laughs ]
Yeah, that's good.
How many more thingies
are in there?
Dude, like, a lot.
Come on, let's check this out
at the house.
JAKE: I'll make a special
sp-got with a new sauce.
Sheesh, so many.
PB, you hang out with Lady.
C-listers, go back in the bag.
Who's a C-list?
Uhh, Tiffany, Donny --
He's okay -- Xergiok,
a bunch of these guys.
That's not very nice.
Don't worry, man.
They'll get involved eventually.
Involved with what?
| don't know.
Involved.
Check out Lady
and Princess Bubblegum.
LITTLE BUBBLEGUM:
Wa-wa-wah, wa-wa-wah.
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wah wa-wa-wah
wa-wah.
What are they talking
about?
Wa-wa-wa-wah.
It's hard to say, but |
think it's got something to do
with Lady being preggos.
Whoa, what kind of narrative
are you trying to create here?
That's your narrative,
buddy.
All right, well,
what else you got going on?
Mm... not much, really.
| got Ice King over here.
Ice King?
He's not C-list?
Yeah, well, | saw his
drum kit in here.
Here we go. Okay.
Jam out, little Ice King.
S [drums play ] S
JAKE:
No, don't play with that hack.
Aw, man. Hmm.
They've got good chemistry.
Who would've guessed?
Chemistry...
2 [ drums and viola play ] È
Hey, Finn, eat the food
before it gets cold.
[ grunts ]
| made a new sauce.
Um... Earth to Finn.
Are you okay?
[flatly ] Yes.
[ snoring ]
È [ ominous music plays ] >
[ both speaking gibberish ]
[ chuckles ]
Ah-ha-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wah.
[ grunts ]
[ blink! blink! blink! ]
[ both speaking gibberish ]
[ smooch! ]
Hmm? Whoa.
[ both smooching ]
Mwah. Wha?
[ snoring ]
Wa-wah! Wa-wah!
Wahhhhhhhh!
Wa-wah.
Whoa-wah!
[ laughs ]
Weah.
Wee-wee-wee-wee.
[ both smooching ]
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wah!
Ohh!
Wa-wa-wa-wa-whoa.
Wa-wa-wa-wah.
Wa-wa-wah wa-wa-wah.
Whoa! Whoa-whoal!
[ all arguing in gibberish ]
[ yawns ]
You're up early.
- | didn't sleep.
[ liquid pours ]
You stay up all night
reading trash books?
- Mm.
- Told you, man.
Those dating books...
[ slurp!]
That stuff is mess you up.
I'm not reading.
I'm playing
with the little we's.
Oh, let me see
little me.
Me look so lonely.
Hey, Finn,
pass me little Lady!
- Uh, you guys broke up.
- What?
- She's with someone else now.
- Who?
He's a cool guy.
Don't worry about it.
Wahh. Wahh.
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wah!
[ gasps ]
[ smooch! smooch! smooch! ]
Aaaaaaaahhhh!!
What the ball, man?
[ laughs ] What?
"What"?
What do you think "what"?!
Come on. They're not real.
They're like toys.
These guys here,
they're going out.
It's pretty serious.
And look at Choose Goose
and Lollipop Girl.
They're still testing
the waters.
But | think things
are gonna work out.
Check out Xergiok
and Turtle P.
[ both speaking gibberish ]
[ laughs ]
Weird, but cool, right, Jake?
| don't like where
you're going with this.
It ain't wholesome.
I'm gonna go to Lady's
for a few days --
clear my head.
Okay, whateva whatevs.
[ both smooching ]
[ laughs ]
Weird.
Huh.
[ yawns ]
Wha?
[ giggles ]
Ulp.
Wah-wah-wah num-num.
Wah-wah num-num-num.
[ chuckles ]
Wha?
Wahhhhhhhh!
Wahhhhh!
Wahhhhhhh!
Mm.
- Wah-wah -- hmm?
- Wah.
[ whistles ]
Hmm. Mm.
- Mm.
- Wa-wa-wah wa-wa-wah?
LITTLE FINN:
Wa-wa-wa wa-wah.
LITTLE BUBBLEGUM:
[ laughs]
- Wah?
- Wa-wa-wah wah?
[ smooch! smooch! smooch! ]
Wah-wah!
Wa-wa-wah wah-wah!
Wa-wa-wah wah!
Wah? Wa-wah wah?
Aaaaaaaaaahhhh!
Wa-wah! Wha!
[ fire roars ]
Wah -- unh!
W-Waahhhhh!
WEEEEEEEE)]alalal!
[ whimpers ]
WELL
A-EEEEEElalal
[ both grunting ]
I'm back.
| got over all that...
messed-up stuff you did.
Yeesh.
You okay, man?
| don't know.
What's Little Finn
doin'?
He's thinking.
He looks sad.
What's he thinking about?
| don't know.
Probably lots of stuff.
- Where's little Rainicorn?
- Probably still crying.
What?!
She's... not handling
the breakup very well.
- [ sobbing ]
- Aww.
PB's good, though.
After Little Finn dumped her,
she started working out.
[ grunting ]
Looks like she's
really into it.
This is messed up,
dude.
You've crossed the line
from weird curiosity
into some dark,
messed-up stuff.
- | know!
- The destruction!
The depravity!
The wrongness of it all!
I'm taking that bag back to
the cliff where we found it.
No, man!
| gotta fix this mess!
Look at me, man!
I'm staring into the shadow of
my darkest mind hole!
| got to help him.
[ straining ]
You can't.
Just let them
do their own biz, man!
| junked them up
too hard, though.
| got to step in!
- How would you do that?
- I'm gonna talk to him.
- But he can't hear you.
Yeah. Why is that?
Hmm.
Maybe we're on different
dimensional planes
and the border between
our planes is like a two-way mirror.
So we can see him,
but he can't see us.
Eh, let me try this.
Finn! Can you hear me?!
We are connected!
Finn!
Wa-wa-wah, wa-wa-wah,
wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wah.
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wah,
WERTERVER
- Try shaking him.
- Why?
Maybe we're vibrating
on different intervals.
Try shaking him
at different speeds
and see if he responds.
- Okay.
Finn! Finn!
- Now go faster.
- Finn!
[ wind howling ]
JAKE: Faster!
Wa-wah wa-wa-wa-wah,
wa-wa-wa-wa-wah.
Finn!
Wah wah?!
- Go slower! He saw you!
- Okay!
WELRYEN
wa-wa-wa-wah, wah!
Finn! Can you hear me?!
WELR
Wah wah wah?
Whoa, neat!
| made you do those
crummy things!
I'm why yous guys is fighting!
I'm the big youl!
| came to apologize!
| will never interfere
with your lives again!
Wah, wa-wa-wah
wa-wa-wah wah wah!
Don't worry!
I will...
[ wind howls ]
Take care of it.
Sorry, my arm got tired.
- Wah?
- Never mind! It'll be fine!
Goodbye, little Finn!
I'm not coming back!
Wah-wah!
Now what?
[ wind howls ]
Hey, ladies!
This is big Finn!
| caused all the problems!
It wasn't anyone's fault!
Don't be mad at each other!
Have a dance party!
Okay, goodbye!
I'm not coming back!
> [ dance music plays ] È
Is that gonna do it?
Get the C-listers out.
Good party.
Oh, flip!
Look who's hittin' it off
with the Ice King!
[ chuckles ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!