[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ hiss!]
[ hiss! ][ hiss!]
Huh.
Is this like eating for you?
| don't know about eating,
but it feels nice.
Hmm.
Mm.
ICE KING:
Hey.
You two should get a room.
You and that /og,
not you and Finn.
'ÔCause you're hugging
a log, you weirdo.
[ laughs ]
Grrrr!
Finn.
Huh?
Let me.
Huh?!
[ laughs ]
Huh?
Hey, now.
Stay away from me.
Shoo! Shoo! Oh!
[ fwoosh! ]
Oh, so you want to
get real, do you?
Well, check this.
You seeing this?
Huh?
Oh!
[ whump! ]
Whoa.
Aah! Oh! Ugh!
Why don't you get a room?
Oofl
[ fwoosh! ]
Aah! My hams!
Beat it,
you freaky old trump!
[ grunts ]
[ whistle! ]
[ whoof! ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ groaning ]
[ hiss!]
Huh?
What's cooking?
Smells good.
Wha?
WhEEEL
Oh! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Breath mint!
Aah! Aaaah!
Huh?
Gah!
[ chuckles lightly ]
My body is
engulfed in flames!
[ laughs ]
Oh, so good!
- [ in distance ] Hey!
- What?
[ in distance ]
Blew it. Blew it.
Huh?
- You blew it.
JAKE: Eh-eh-eh-eh-eggs!
Wha!
JAKE:
Ninja kick!
Eh-eh-eh-eh-eh eh-eh-eggs!
File folder!
Eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eggs!
Gorilla!
Eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eggs.
Jake. Jake.
| had an awesome dream.
Flame Princess was there.
My body was on fire.
| think it was inspired
by Flame Princess
battling Ice King yesterday.
Hmm. That's weird.
| had a dream, too.
I'll tell you about it.
So, then paintings were found,
and everyone's eyes lit up.
Cinnamon Bun smiled and said,
"l saw it from miles away."
[ thinking ] Man, I need to
have that dream again.
/ have to get Flame Princess
to beat down Ice King again.
Why'd you pick this spot?
Why does anyone do anything?
Hmm.
Why do they?
[ bag shakes ]
Mm?
No, thanks.
[ garbled ]
Suit yourself.
[ whistling ]
Mm?
Hey! L-I-look!
[gulp!]
[ normal voice ]
Hey, look.
There's that big jerk you
hate so much, remember?
[ whistles ]
Hmm?
Oh, hey, kids.
Fine day for a picnic.
Oh, dang.
Did you hear that?
[ inhales sharply ]
| think he's, like,
making fun of you.
What?
Yeah.
It's in the tone
of his voice.
What did you say to me?
Uh, uh -- w-what?
W-what did | say?
[ gasps ]
It /sin the tone
of your voice.
L-look.
Just take whatever
you want, okay?
Take it all.
It's all just prunes --
prunes and liver --
Frozen, of course.
[ hiss!]
Ugh!
[ growls ]
[ whap!]
[ fwoosh! ]
Bah!
You might have what it takes
to slap these old jowls,
but do you have what
it takes to face my...
just a sec.
...Legion of Snow Warriors?!
Go, fight! Protect me!
Oh, boy.
| don't like being
made fun of, Ice King.
| don't like it at all!
Whoa!
[ whimpering ]
[ splish! ]
[ clank! ]
[ zap!]
[ thump! ]
Oh!
Oh, man.
Times! | call times!
[ whimpers ]
It's only okay if the person
who's making the fun is someone
that I'm cool with.
We're totes cool.
I-I-I'm Ice King.
And they doitin a
respectful and knowing way.
Respect?
| got all kinds
of respect.
Oh, yeah?
Then what's with that
stupid, smirky face?
Smirk?
Oh, I-l smirk
when I'm nervous.
Ugh, bear hug!
WhEEEL
[ gasps ]
And also when I'm
about to win!
[ laughs ]
Boo-yah!
And | didn't even get to test
out my new fireproof grundies.
Put it away, man.
You didn't win nothing.
[ laughs ]
Are you okay?
You feel lukewarm.
I-I just need to burn
a couple of forests or
something and get
a good night's sleep.
Yeah...sleep.
Milk.
[ gulp! gulp! gulp!
gulp! gulp!]
Milk.
[ gulp! gulp! gulp!
gulp! gulp!]
Play the sleep jam, BMO.
[ static plays ]
Mm.
What's cooking? Smells good.
Wha?
Hi-yah!
What? Oh, no!
[ laughs ]
Aah! Aah!
[ groans ]
Huh?
[ panting ]
Jake!
| had another dream!
My body was being blasted.
[ inhales sharply ]
But this time, Ice King was
blasting me with ice cubes.
Oh! It was awful!
And someone else was there.
He was just laughing
and laughing.
He was in the first dream,
too, but he was whispering.
| couldn't make out
what he was saying.
Oh, yeah.
It was the Cosmic Owl.
Pbht!
What?! You didn't tell me the
Cosmic Owl was there!
| couldn't see
him last time.
Dude, that means it
was a prophetic dream.
You have to finish
the original dream.
Cosmic Owl could be whispering
something wildly significant!
You have to get Flame Princess
and Ice King to fight again
SO you can see
the end of the dream.
Make them fight!
Aah! Do it now!
Aaaah!
Dear Ice King,
you smell like stink.
You're unpleasant, you're
not funny, you're old --
blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah.
Sincerely, love,
Flame Princess.
P.S.
Let us fight.
Aaaah!
Dear Flame Princess,
you're just the worst.
Your hair is bad, your feet
smell like face cheeks --
blah, blah, blah, blah.
Let us meet up and
fight, dummy.
Sincerely, Ice King.
Hmm.
Flame Princess
fight Ice King.
FINN:
Ice King.
What?
Ooh! Beard mail!
"Dear Ice King,
you're not funny,
you're old, and no Princess
will ever marry you ever,
Simple Simon."
Oh, fight.
Flame Princess!
Huh?
"Dear Flame Princess, your
feet smell like face cheeks,
your stupid candles
smell heinous,
and you can't even kiss Finn
without totes freakin' out!"
Aaah!
[ roars ]
[ gasps ]
Not my beard.
Ohh!
Pbht!
Oow!
Aaah!
[ chuckles ]
What is all that noise?
Ach, mein gloob!
Infern-0-0-0-0-0-0 shot!
I-I-1-Ice...
uh, King!
Aah! Whoa! Ow!
[ hiss!]
[ grunting ]
[ whimpering ]
[ zap! zap! ]
[ laughs ]
Ergh! Stop that!
[ chuckles ]
Hows about some of this?!
Yee -- aah!
[ hiss!]
Oh, beans!
Oh, beans! Oh, beans!
[ penguins wenking ]
I maybe went too
far with this jazz.
FLAME PRINCESS:
[ roars ]
Flame Princess.
[ moans ]
Too hot.
[ groans ]
[ fwoosh! ]
Aah!
[ laughs ]
[ hissing ]
Mm.
Huh?
Uh.
[ fwoosh! ]
[ groaning ]
Wha. Wha-wha wha-wha?
[ gasps ]
Wha-wha?
Wha wh-wh-wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-
wha-wha-wha?
Wha wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-wha?
Wha wha-wha-wha-wha-
wha-wha-wha- wha-wha!
You blew it.
Huh?
[ snarling ]
[ breathes deeply ]
Okay. | can fix this.
| can make it right.
Ice King!
RVECELOA!
Finn.
I'm so sorry, man.
Help, Gunter.
Please.
I- meant after
you save me.
[ blows ]
Wenk!
Oh.
Wenk, wenk.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Oh! That's right.
Carry me like a Princess.
GUNTER:
Wenk, wenk.
Eh?
Ice King!
You can't escape me!
Wha?
[ gasps ]
Finn.
Aaah!
Ice, uh, whatever.
I'm so, so sorry, Finn.
Are you all right?
No, Princess.
[ sighs ]
/'m the one who's sorry.
Ice King hasn't been
picking fights with you.
It's --
it's been me all along.
What?
So, you wrote that letter?
Yes.
But, ook, it's just like...
| had this dream and --
and it was because
of that fight you had.
It was weird, but
| also liked it, but it --
but it was important because the
Cosmic Owl was wh-wh-wha-wha.
Whadda-wha-wha-wha.
Wha-wha-wha, wha-wha-wha-wha.
Wh-wha.
Wh-wh-wh-wha.
And so | had to get you
to beat up Ice King be--
Shilll
| should have known.
That letter said things in it
that only you would know,
personal things, Finn,
and you used them against me.
| thought you were the
one person | could --
|-l need some
time alone.
Princess.
But...
I-1-1 said |
was sorry.
[rip!]
[ splash! ]
[ inhales deeply ]
You blew it, man.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!