[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ squawks ]
[ chuckles ]
Loot, bro!
Gear dumped, bro!
How about this room, bro?
Looks like a brolicious
room to relax in and
play video games ...bro.
Home sweet home, bro.
ICE KING:
Yeah, you said it.
I've been home
this whole time.
[ groans ]
| keep forgetting that
he lives here now.
Just until Gunther finishes
rebuilding the Ice Kingdom.
What y'all whispering about?
Hee-hee! Ex-squeeze me.
Ice King, we've told
you a thousand times.
This couch
ain't for cuddling.
Sure it is.
It isn't!
Mm, it's cozy.
It's not that bad, Jake.
See?
[ groans ]
Finn, can | speak to
you in the kitchen?
Oh, hey, Jake.
Can you bring
me a sandwich?
[ whistles ]
Sandwich?
It's time to kick
Ice King out!
Huh!
Don't forget the bread!
Ha ha!
Look, | hear you, but
we can't kick him out because,
well, | still feel guilty
about junking up his crib.
Hey, what if we check
him into a hotel room?
Hmm.
What's that?
Checking into a hotel room.
Ooh, sandwich time!
[ munching ]
Hey, Simon, how would you like
to stay in the coolest hotel?
Lumpy Space Princess
stays there.
That's how cool it is.
We'll even put you up for a few
weeks until your place is ready.
Oh, but that
sounds lonely.
I'd just like to
stay here with you guys.
Having roommates is nice.
Keeps me out of my head.
Gunther only says "Wenk."
What's up with that?
[ chuckles nervously ]
Yeah.
Finn, I'm ready
to murder the Ice King.
No.
Uh, | have another idea.
[ ticking ]
[ munches ]
[ scratching ]
[ munching ]
[ plate clatters ]
Oop.
[ door bell rings ]
Oh, my gosh!
Someone's at the door.
We have a doorbell now.
We'll get it!
BOTH:
Abracadaniel?
What are you doing here?
What?
You kept calling and ca--
[ laughs ]
Shut the hupbububup,
Abracadeez!
Yeah, man.
You don't even need
a reason to stop by.
A sexy wizard like
you goes where he wants.
Whoa.
| see what's going on.
Wha-- you do?
Yeah.
This wizard donk is trying to
jack my tree house styles just
'cause he beat me that
one time at wizard battle,
and if he takes
one step closer,
I'll bust him up
one real good!
| never asked to be...
[ sobbing ]
Aah! Aah! Aaaaah!
Come on, dude.
We got cookies and the cocoa.
FINN:
[ laughs ]
Dang, but you're funny,
Abracadaniel!
| didn't say anything.
[ laughs ]
Fantastic.
JAKE:
Hey, Abadabs.
Why don't you show us that
trick you're working on?
[ slink! ]
Oh, uh...
Yeah,
I-I suppose | could.
Shraa-molah-ra
cantata florianaaa.
[ grunting ]
[ panting ]
So good!
Whoo!
You're a good wizard!
| don't know. It's dumb.
I'm still working on it.
It's --
it's nothing.
Oh, you're right
that ain't nothing!
Check out this schwizal!
[ warble! ]
[ ice creaking ]
Hwah!
What?
Oo-oh!
You're the greatest
wizard ever!
Well, maybe
not everever.
Am | the greatest wizard
of our generation?
Yes.
Pew! Pew!
[ crash! ]
[ slurping ]
This was a
great idea, man.
It's like he's
forgotten all about us.
Mm-hmm.
And pretty soon he'll
be out of here for good.
For good.
Yeah. Mm.
ICE KING:
Finn!
Jake!
JAKE:
[ grumbles ]
ICE KING:
Come quick!
It's an emergency!
Hurry!
[ both giggle ]
Ice King, what's up?
Huh? What the flip?
Ta-da!
How'd they get the
other couch down here?
There you are, sir.
And there you are.
Right this way.
You made it!
[ drumming rhythmically ]
Caw!
Ta-da!
[ laughs ]
A bird! He's a bird!
I've always been into
interpretive dance...
but I've never been able to find
a musician who could match my
energy until now!
[ drumming rhythmically ]
Huh, he's
actually not bad.
> Bum-bum-bum
SÈ Budum bum bum bum-bum-bum
SÈ Bum-bum-bum bum bum )
Dance party!
È Boom chica bow wow
JÈ Boom chica chica chica boom È
No!
CEEEEEE L]
> Doopa doopa doom doom J
È Doopa doopa doom doom doom
> Doopa È
> Doopa doopa doom doom J
È Doopa doopa doom doom doom
No!
Oow!
Ow! Why are you doing this?!
BMO:
You pushed my whole body!
Um...whoo!
That was great, guys!
Yeah? You guys liked it?
Well, then, the second
and third acts are gonna
knock your socks off!
Uh, actually,
Jake and | got to --
got some stuff
to take care of.
Yeah,
it's getting pretty late.
Uh...oh, glob.
Sup, ABD?
| just remembered that I'm,
uh, allergic, uh, to --
to the night sky!
You're afraid
of the dark?
Yes, if | ever had to walk, uh,
outside at night,
I might die of ...of...
of fright.
...of fright!
Gee, well, | guess you can
crash here for the night.
BOTH:
Al right!
Sleepover!
Wait.
Are you really
afraid of the dark?
Maybe?
Okay, well,
you can sleep on the couch.
We're gonna go.
Uh, good night.
[ both giggle ]
Whoa!
See?
| told you.
Isn't it awesome?
Since I'm pretty
much in charge here,
we could totally take all this
treasure if we wanted to.
Ha! Totally.
Wow! Cool!
Oh, that's just a binklemyer.
Oh.
Want to see something
really cool?
Yeah.
Okay, but you got to
promise not to freak out.
This is Joshua the dog's
demon-blood sword.
ABRACADANIEL:
[ gasps ]
Yeah, it's a real
demon-blood sword.
Whaaaaaaat?
And you see these words?
If you say them out loud,
you can actually see a vision
of the demon whose blood was
used to make the sword.
No way!
That sounds awesome.
Too bad neither of us
can read demon runes.
Ooh, | know how!
"Booty rum lac soo ree
po Kee Oth prandium."
Like that.
[ roars ]
Oops.
Wow!
It looks so real!
| amreall
BOTH:
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Bring me the true bearer of my
blood sword or | will destroy
you both!
[ growling ]
Come on, best friend!
Let us not betray Finn.
Let's fight
Kee Oth ourselves!
Nobody can defeat us
if we work together.
Super wizard team up!
Hwah!
Floriana!
Raaa!
You're wasting your
powers on me!
Ha ha!
Oh! No!
Oh, no!
He's too powerful!
[ growling ]
BOTH:
Kee Oth!
Joshual
BOTH:
Kee Oth rama pan...
Don't say another word, Joshua.
Or their throats
are going to get it!
If you speak the
words to banish me,
I'll reduce your
friends to ash.
Kee Oth rama--
Dude!
Thought he was bluffing.
I'm not bluffing, Joshua!
If you do not willingly
return my stolen blood,
| will destroy
him and him!
Ah! The sword!
Scary!
[ shink! ]
| just can't do it, Jake.
This is Dad's sword!
You don't have
any other choice.
Do it!
Do it! Do it!
[ grunts ]
Whoa, bro.
You got your blood.
Now get out of here!
All right, I'll go.
Psych!
Got you now, Joshua!
Ah!
[ laughs evilly ]
Uh, hey.
So, |-l should
be getting home.
Uh, yeah. Me too.
Hey, Abracadaniel, you want
to hang out at my place?
| thought your
house broke.
Psh.
Ice Kingdom's been
rebuilt for weeks.
NELCYS
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!