[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ squeaking ]
Aw, yes!
The storm has passed!
Jake!
Hoo! Hoo.
Jake.
Nachos.
| love nachos.
| love nachos even more while
looking out the window.
[ wind howling ]
Hmm. Does that box have
a face on it?
A face...
gotta make sure.
[ gasps ]
There's a box outside
with a face on it!
It might be a box man.
He's all soggy and dirty.
Want to check it out?
NEVA
'Chos!
[ munching ]
I'm gonna check it out.
- Yeah, whatever.
Hmm.
Where'd your face go?
Whoa!
Okay. Shh.
Are you lost,
little cardboard dude?
[ cat meows ]
Jake! There seems to be
a lost cat
bumping around in a box!
JAKE: Yeah, that's great.
Get it out of here!
Getting no help
from him, | guess.
Do you know where
your home is?
[ cat meows ]
Okay. I'll follow you.
Whoa.
Is this your kingdom?
- [ cat meows ]
It's wonderful!
[ cats meowing ]
[ cat meows ]
[ laughing ]
[ trumpets blaring ]
That must be your prince.
Huh?
A prince wouldn't steal
from his subjects.
Aww!
[ cat meows ]
Switched?
[ gasps ]
Of course!
You must be the real prince,
and
that thief took your place!
Is that right, little prince?
[ cat meows ]
[ breathes deeply ]
Don't worry, your majesty.
I'll help you reclaim
your kingdom.
[ cat meows ]
[ cat purring ]
[ mid-tempo music plays, stops ]
Why do you hate cats, Jake?
Move your face.
You're messing up the game.
Anyway, | don't want to talk
about it.
It's personal.
Cats know what they did.
Aah! Aah!
Is Jake okay?
[ groaning ]
No!
I'm pretty dang far from okay!
There's a little shard
of tortilla chip
caught between
my teeth.
[ groans ]
First, we have to expose
the traitor's deception.
Hmm. Aha.
That's a counterfeit crown,
hewn from the liar's own
boxflesh.
Hmm.
It looks like your crown was
torn off by some -- ah!
[ cat meows ]
Your crown was lost, you say?
During the storm?
[ cat meows ]
The same storm that sent you
hurtling through the woods?
[ cat meows ]
Until you were delivered
unto my doorstep?
[ cat meows ]
Right.
So it's definitely
in the woods somewhere.
All we have to do is
find your crown
to prove to the people
that you're the real prince.
[ sniffs ]
Mm. Um...
I'm gonna wait over by the
gates, your highness.
Mm-nah, mm-nah,
mm-nah.
Get big and the chip will
fall out of your teeth.
Ha! You think | can
stretch out of everything?
You're so naive.
To live life,
you need problems.
That's stupid!
If you get everything you want
the minute you want it,
what's the point of living?
[ grunting ]
[ sips ]
[ sighs ]
FINN: Come on, dude.
It's time for your vitamins.
[ grumbles ]
Okay. So let's
retrace your steps.
Do you remember which path
you took?
[ cat meows ]
Prince?
Whoa!
You found it already!
Good work, team!
Ow! Quit that!
Come on.
You're a prince.
Come, your majesty.
It's time.
[ cat meows ]
People of the Box Kingdom!
| have found...
your true prince!
J'accuse!
[ cats meow ]
what?
They -- they don't believe us.
Mm.
The rain lumped up your
complexion all hobo-like.
They're not looking past
the surface grunk.
[ cat meows ]
Hmm?
Oh, no. He's challenging you
to a joust!
We better find you a lance.
[ spits ]
Did it come out?
You've forgotten
the most important part,
my impatient little friend --
a thorough rinsing.
Well?
[ spits ]
Bleh.
Nothing.
| need, like, a toothpick
or something.
| told you to buy floss.
Floss is for losers.
Oh, one of these
will do nicely.
You put cards in your mouth?
Just the edge, kid.
And then | work it
like a pro.
Now to find the card
that best suits
my devil-may-care
personality.
[ trumpets blaring ]
[ cats meowing ]
[ cat meows ]
Trial by combat shall
prove which prince is true!
[ both meow ]
[ cat meows ]
[ gasps ]
[ both yowling ]
[ cats yowl ]
This town's gone nuts!
[ humming ]
JAKE:
Hey, Beemo!
Ta-da!
[ gasps ]
You did it, Jake!
Congratulations!
How did you get that piece of
tortilla chip out of your teeth?
Oh, | didn't.
It's still there.
It'll be like a constant
reminder
of what life's all
about.
This is unsatisfying.
Zip it!
[ cats yowling ]
Hyah!
Bad!
Bad princes!
[ cats meow ]
Which is which?
Aww!
This is the one!
This is your prince!
Um...
or maybe this is the one!
[ cats meow ]
Hmm.
[ cat meows ]
Is this...
is this even a kingdom?
[ cat purring ]
[ cats meowing ]
[ chuckles ]
Aww!
Aww. Hey, hey!
Oh, you guys!
Aww, cut it out!
[ meowing, purring continues ]
Aww! Oh!
Ah!
[ chuckles ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!