[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ Jake snoring ]
[ clattering ]
Wha?
[ screams ]
Huh?
Finn?
I'm coming!
[ screaming ]
She's got me!
[ sighs ]
Yo, bro, you're sleepwalking again.
Wake up!
Whoa. Jake?
Was I...?
Yes, Finn.
Again.
Every time youse is
screaming about,
"she's got me!"
and all that.
She's got what?
Wait.
You don't remember?
You just woke up, man.
Recall it, baby.
Come on.
[ grunting ]
That's too much.
Don't punch yourself.
[ sighs ]
It's gone. | don't know.
You're repressing
the memory, dude.
I'm what?
You're hiding whatever
she is in a mental vault.
Oh, yeah. The vault.
That's where the stuff
| can't handle goes.
Kerplunk!
Okay, so you even know
you're doing it.
Yeah.
[ chuckles ]
Listen, we got to find out
who this lady is.
Got to open the vault
a little.
No, sir.
It's just gonna keep
happening, man.
It's all right.
I'm not hurting anybody.
Finn, for reals.
3\ [o}]
All right.
Chill. Chill.
Don't sweat it, man.
It's not even a thing.
Cool.
Why don't you clean up
the kitchen now?
Okay.
I'm sorry | did that.
It's all right.
It's only, like,
the fifth room you've
train-wrecked this month.
[ cricket chirping ]
Wow. That was fast.
- Yep.
While you were doing that,
| downloaded a new game
on Beemo.
There's a cricket
in here.
- Huh?
- What is it?
| don't know.
Lady said it's good.
Mm, she likes those
games where you're,
like, collecting materials
to make stationery?
Nah, this is different.
It's different.
All right.
Let's peep it.
Regression simulator?
Uh... okay.
Start.
VIDEO GAME NARRATOR:
Welcome, adventurer.
Whoa.
/ am the hypno priest.
[ will be your guide
deep into
your subconscious mind.
Follow me now,
adventurer.
[ gasps ]
The vault.
JAKE:
Go in there, man.
Don't be scurd.
What do you see?
| see my past lives.
| was a comet.
A butterfly.
A thing.
| don't know what that is --
some kind of shape or a doo-doo
in another dimension.
Do you remember anything
about the scary lady?
Scary lady.
Yeah. | was her.
Except she was
a chubby tiger.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
She was riding a tiger,
and she wasn't scary.
MAN:
Hey, qirl.
Sniffing around for
that chedda?
You know it.
Got at any work for me?
I might could, but it's
a top-shelf shakedown.
Know what I'm sayin'?
| can step to that.
There's a rival camp
down river.
The leader's got some magic
omelet, you know?
Mmm.
The kind you wear
around your neck.
| think it's pronounced
amulet.
Oh, don't get fresh with me,
girleen.
| talk good.
Anyway, when | get my hands
on that omelet -- whoo-hoo!
Forget about everything,
baby.
I'll be the biggest cheese
in creation.
Sounds cool.
I'll take the job.
Shake on it.
You pull this off,
and I'll let you join my gang.
Uh, that's okay.
I'll just work for coin.
And, on the other hand,
so to speak,
if you screw up or
chicken out,
you're out of the game...
permanently.
Pretend my finger's a knife.
[ grunts ]
Play dead.
Deader.
[ screams ]
[ crack!]
[ thud! ]
Ah! Another attack!
[ inhales deeply ]
[ horn blows ]
My leader!
Another attack!
Bring them inside.
Hey. You're up.
| thought you might be hungry.
So, who knocked you out?
Bath Boy gang.
Oh!
| hate those boys!
Yeah.
They stole everything | had.
But that's okay.
My parents always told me
that simple possessions
aren't the most important
things in life.
Word 'em up.
They told me all you really
need is a good computer.
Amen.
Wait. What?
Then they traded my arm
to some tranch for a computer.
- They what?!
- What?
Parents should
protect their children.
What?!
Really?
Do you have any kids?
BUBBLEGUM:
All the candy people are like my children.
Except
young Mr. Creampuff.
He's like my boyfriend.
Anyway, protecting my people is
the most important thing to me.
That's why I've got to take down
the Bath Boy gang.
You think you can do that?
| got a plan --
a secret, awesome plan.
In the meantime,
I've got to cover
this radioactive river
with candy.
Want to help?
Thanks for
pitching in, Shoko.
You can stay here
as long as you want.
Psst.
Psst. Psst.
Shoko.
- What are you doing here?
I'm spying on you.
Wait 'til | tell boss
that you quit the life
for a cruddy day job.
I'm gaining their trust,
you momo.
Say, you can help me.
Huh?
Stay away from me,
you gang boy!
[ screams ]
[ gasps |
A Bath Boy!
- What are you doing?
- Be cool.
Oow!
[ grunting ]
That was
bananamas.
Where did you learn to fight
CRGE
My parents took me to a dojo
when | was little.
They never came back.
Wow.
Your parents are the worst.
Hey, come with me.
| want to show you something.
My secret project is
in here.
Whoa.
What are they?
The Gumball Guardians.
Want to help me finish them?
Yeah!
BUBBLEGUM:
That's it.
There's just one last step.
Hello.
GUARDIANS:
Hello, mother.
Y'all go guard now.
And don't let nobody mess
with my stuff.
Hey, guess what.
Thanks for helping me
make those guys.
| like feeling handy.
| want to repay you
for your help.
Oh, yeah?
You gonna give me
that amulet, maybe?
[ laughs ]
[ chuckles ]
No.
No, dude.
| made you a thing.
That's it.
You can do it.
You made me a manservant?
No. In the box.
[ gasps ]
Oh, no.
What do you mean,
"Oh, no"?
| made you an arm.
It's a dang plug 'n' play,
girl.
No, it's awesome.
| can't believe it.
That's right.
I'm a technical wonder child.
Yeah, | know.
I'm sorry.
| got to go to my room
for no reason.
Okay. | thought we could do
some two-arm stuff,
but, uh,
it's cool!
Pretend my finger's a knife.
I'm sorry,
Princess Bubblegum.
Are you okay, Princess?
Ah, geez!
You're so loud!
[ thud!]
Are you in danger?
No!
Don't just guard me.
You need to protect
everyone.
Okay.
[ thudding ]
[ yawns ]
[ distantly ]
Are you in danger?
[ snores ]
- GUARDIAN: | knew it.
- [ gasps ]
Princess, you are
getting jacked.
What? Huh?
Whoa! Hey!
Halt!
[ screams ]
Get her out
of there, quick!
BOTH:
Yes, mom.
[ thudding ]
Uh...
All right.
Take a break for the night.
[ thudding ]
[ beeping ]
[ snoring ]
[ gasps ]
How you doing, buddy?
The past must
be reckoned with.
That's cool.
Whatcha gonna do about it?
[ German accent ]
Hello. Bubblegum here.
[ normal voice ]
Atonement?
All right, Finn.
I'm on my way.
[ screams ]
Ugh. Blech.
[ groans ]
Look at that.
| got a new arm.
That would be cool
if | weren't
about to hit
my reset button.
[ groans ]
Hey! Hey.
This way.
[ grunts ]
What was that?!
Oh, no!
Donk drangit, Finn!
Hyah! Hyah!
Uh...
[ grunts ]
Okay. Here you go.
Whoa! What?!
My amulet?!
Wait a second.
[ gasps ]
Is that...?
- It's me, Shoko.
And, PB, you are
like a bazillion years old.
You're not freakin' 19.
What the heck?!
- [ chuckles ]
- Weirdo.
Huh.
My vault feels lighter.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!