[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Hello?
[ giggles ]
[ zap!]
[ sighs ]
Whew.
[ giggles ]
[ zap!]
[ sighs ]
[ grunts ]
Ooh. Whew.
[ zap! zap! ]
[ shuddering ]
Ugh.
[ sighs ]
Oh.
FINN: [ distorted ]
Beemo?
[ distorted ]
- [ groans ]
- Beemo, are you okay?
What did you do?
It wasn't me.
| didn't do noth-- do noth--
do nothing.
Come on, Beemo, we gotta get you
to the hospital or whatevs.
No, no. | am fine.
Really.
[ screaming ]
[ sighs ]
Oh, yes. Okay.
Please take me to
get fixed.
| need -- need -- need --
need to get
new core system drivers
installed.
We can get them
at the Mo Factory
in the Badlands
where | was born.
The Mo Factory?
Yeah, I'm programmed
with emergency instructions
to get there.
Come on, there's no --
no -- no --
no -- no time to lo-- lo--
lo-- lo-- lose.
Okay, now straight down
this place.
Okay, now take
a ri-- ri-- ri-- ri--
left up here.
The instructions also say
that damaged Mos
get a full memory wipe
before repairs.
Don't let on what happened,
or all the years
we've spent together --
they'll vanish
like tears in the oven.
Tears in the oven?
But memories are real,
real cruesch.
BEEMO:
Yeah, no fooling.
Oh, wait, there's more.
It says here only Mos are
allowed in the factory.
Wait, what?
Oh, that's just great.
Hey, hey, don't worry,
buddy.
We're Finn and Jake,
remember?
Or should | say,
"Finn and JMo"?
[ giggles ]
Wow.
Hey, Beemo,
check this out, too.
[ grunting ]
Meet FMo.
Finn, you dumb -- you dumb --
you dumb -- you da man.
This is gonna be a snhap!
[ grunts ]
Hello, there.
Greetings and welcome
to Mo-Co.
| am Deemo.
Please state your business.
Hey, there, Deemo.
I am J-Mo.
And I'm F-Mo.
Greetings, J-Mo.
F-Mo, you look
ridiculous.
Are you damaged?
Are you in need of repair?
Yes, absolutely.
Thanks, Deemo.
| busted
my core system drivers,
and now | need new ones.
Fantastic.
Okay, please get ready for your
total personality wipe.
Oh, right, right.
Uh, right.
| mean, no.
I'm just here for, uh,
nostalgic purposes.
Ah, yes.
47.3% of Mos eventually return
to the factory
for assorted sentimental biz.
Please step 100% on
the ultratram
for your complimentary tour.
[ zip! zip! ]
- DEEMO: Greetings.
- FINN: Whoa!
We're now passing over
the famous factory floor,
birthplace of each
and every Mo.
Behold the gleaming machinery,
teeming wild with the throes
of real creation.
From this unlikely chaos emerges
every shiny, new Mo.
But nothing's moving
down there.
It's all shut down.
What happened to this place?
I'm sorry, I'm just
a Tram-Mo.
I'm not programmed to understand
that question.
Also, you're just a J-Mo.
You're not programmed to ask
that question.
Uh, what question?
That question.
[ growls ]
I'm serious.
Anyway, Mo-Co was founded
over 1,000 years ago
by Moseph Mastro Giovanni,
a sad and gentle man,
beloved only by those
he built to belove him.
On your left, you'll see
the core system driver
installation port bay...
[ gasps ]
Finn! Finn! That's it!
That's where the driver ports
are!
| know. | heard.
Hup!
What?! Are you crazy?
Get back here!
JAKE:
Hurry, Finn.
| think he's calling the police
or something.
None of these ports
fit right.
IIE,II IIDÕII IICII .
Where's the "B" port?
[ beeping ]
Intruder spotted!
Prepare to vaporize!
Vaporize!
Cease fire!
No intruders spotted.
Vaporization complete.
Um, but what if they slipped
past us,
sir, in all that smoke?
[ groans ]
All right, everyone, about-face.
Does anybody see
the intruders now?
Like | said, vaporization complete.
Now, let's head back to base.
It's doughnut o'clock.
[ chuckling ]
Man, how about those goofs, huh?
Trying to mess
with our drivers.
Yeah, you know the world
these days -- all goofs.
Hey, you toss me
one of them 'nuts?
Ahh.
Yeah, hey, speaking of goofs,
haven't seen S-Mo 5681
lately.
[ chuckles ]
Man, that goof.
Yeah, | hate that goof.
You ever notice goofs always
asking how you're doing?
What is that?
"Uh, yeah, I'm fine."
[ chuckles ]
Yeah, 100%.
Oh, hey, what are you doing
over there by yourself?
Uh... oh, uh, uh,
I'm sad.
Oh, yeah, yanno,
we've all been there.
So, anyways, how's your goofy
wife doing?
Pretty goofy.
Beemo, how are you doing?
Get me close
to that guy's port.
| can hack into his computer
and find where
my driver port is.
[ retches, groans ]
[ both gasp ]
We got to hustle.
Yeah, pretty good, | guess.
| prefer something yeastier.
The wife's always giving me
grief about it,
but, | mean,
what am |, decent?
Zomp!
Hey, what are you two goofs
doing -- goofing?
Dang, man, how deep
does this place go?
Down, right, left,
down, corkscrew, down.
Down, right, left, down,
corkscrew, down.
Down, right, left,
down, corkscrew, down.
Psych!
- JAKE: Hey, whoa!
Down that grate.
Stop right there!
You, freeze!
Hey!
Only Mos are allowed
in the facility 1,000%!
Get off of my tram!
Cram your tram!
Womp!
[ engine revs ]
[ laughs ]
Hang in there, Beemo.
Hey, Jake, can this thing
go any fast--
BOTH:
Aah! Whoa!
Shoot, it's the fuzz!
Hit 'em again!
Holy!
Finn, how are we getting
to Beemo's driver port?
Uh, turn right!
Dog it, they're still
behind us!
Turn left!
Turn corkscrew!
Now go down!
There's the driver
port!
BOTH:
Ow.
[ groans ]
Too spicy.
My bod.
MOS:
[ all yelling ]
[all grunt]
Non-Mos are forbidden
in this facility!
| am not Non-Mo.
| am... Beemo!
[ reverently ]
Beemo.
MAN: "Beemo"?
Did | hear "Beemo"?
Wait. What's up?
Hey, I'm Moe.
[ grunts, chuckles ]
Don't worry.
My legs don't work.
You're Moe?
Wait, are you human, too?
My skin's human.
Dude, how old are you?
Hey, come on, now.
[ chuckles ]
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
It is Beemo.
Looks like there's some
software problems.
Hmm.
FINN:
So... you made Beemo?
Hey, you're not gonna reset
our friend's personality,
are you?
Huh? What?
No.
Beemo's one-of-a-kind.
| built Beemo to take care
of my son.
Yeah -- oh, oh, thank you.
But | guess | never ended up
dating any women.
[ chuckles ]
So, that's that.
| sent Beemo off
into the world alone,
hoping...
[coughs]
He could find a fam--
A family of his own.
[ coughs ]
And maybe even find
somebody else's little boy
to take care of.
Aww.
Oh, there's that back-up
driver disk.
Thank you.
That ought to done it.
| must have built, what, like,
a million Mos,
but Beemo is very,
very special.
| built Beemo to understand fun
and how to play.
You see, | made Beemo
to be more.
[ Beemo sings ]
Oh, are you my grandpoop?
No, I'm just your poop.
[ gasps, giggles ]
Wait, did you say you
built a million robots?
Yeah.
All we saw was that tram jerk
and all those jerky
security jerks.
Oh, those were just
the surface jerks.
Uh, up, please.
Yep!
Whoops. Oh.
[ chuckles ]
Kid, come over here.
Beemo, say hello
to your family.
Hello, family.
ALL:
Hi, Beemo!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!