[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D Adventure time JÈ
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
D> With Cake the cat
and Fionna the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Oh, no. Oh, no.
[ panting ]
Hup!
[ wenking ]
Fire the laser cannon!
[ wenks ]
Aah!
Good job, girl!
Have some spaghetti!
Thanks.
Oh, no! Ha!
Too bad I'm a
really strong guy
and | took my doctor
pills this morning!
Lasers don't hurt me!
[ grunts ]
[ both gasp ]
Next time.
Hmph!
BOTH:
Give us the Enchiridion!
[ mimics monkey ]
Thanks.
That's not a book!
It's a bomb!
[ ticking ]
[ gasps ]
Yah!
Hyah!
You've been acting like a
real knucklehead, Dr. Prince!
Go on! Get out of here!
And don't ever do
wrong things again!
You're right.
| see your side of things.
You saved the day,
mega-rad-cool-guy.
What's your name?
Oh, Ice King.
I'm such a great guy!
This book is yours.
The Enchiridion!
| want to be your best
and closest friend.
Let's have a best and
closest friend lunch!
It's mac and cheezles.
BOTH:
Aww.
- What a sweetie.
- What a good guy.
I'm just so glad you
guys are real.
[ voice breaking ]
You're really, really real.
[ sniffles ]
| want to remember
this day forever.
Don't be sad, Ice King.
We're going on a
space adventure!
Hop on, baby.
[ chuckling ]
Wee!
Here we go!
PRINCESS:
Ice King, stop! Please!
This story is terrible!
Huh? What?
| can't follow anything.
| mean, where are we going?
[ all talking at once ]
| don't even understand.
Maybe the story is a
new form of torture!
Oh, come on!
It's a first draft!
Don't hate.
And besides, that story
had everything --
Action, adventure,
a hotter older guy.
Wild Berry, don't pretend.
I know you like the
silver foxes.
What if it were a little
more like real life?
Real?
It's based on the real
Fionna and Cake!
Yeah, but what if there was a
little more romance in the story?
Romance is a great idea!
Y'all are just
hatin' on my steez!
I'm not listening to haters!
Haters!
Whoa! What the --
[ trembling ]
Whoa.
ALL:
We're free!
I'm sorry | didn't
think you were real, Gob!
But now I've
seen your power,
and I've got some things | did
that | have to say sorry for.
Boo.
[ gasps ]
Marceline!
How long have
you been in here?
Oh, a couple hours?
Oh, you heard
my story, then.
Awesome, right?
It's good, but maybe it's
time to let someone else try.
Listen up, y'all.
I've got a
story of my own.
FIONNA:
Yah! Yah!
Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Yah!
[ grunts ]
Woo! Nice throw!
Thanks.
I've got to do
something today.
What about Gumball's mission
we went on this morning?
Delivering daisy chains
to the Fluffy people
not enough for you?
Uh, sometimes Gumball's
missions can be so...
lame.
Rah!
Hello, every --
[ gasps ]
[ both gasp ]
Oh, my.
Looks like you almost
skronked up my dome-piece.
Boy, have | got a
treat for you two!
The fluffy people and | baked
these in appreciation for the
mission you've completed.
They're cream puffs.
Try one.
Uh, I'd love to,
but maybe later.
[ footsteps ]
What was that?
[ gasps ]
Uh! Aww.
[ loud footsteps ]
Something's on the roof!
Come on!
I'm not going out there.
It's wet.
Uh, it is wet.
[ grumbles ]
[ guitar playing ]
[ gasps ]
Oh, it's just him.
Oh. Hey, Fionna.
Marshall Leel!
Ahem.
[ gasps ]
Oh, forgive me!
Hello, your Majesty!
[ slurps ]
Fionna, take me back inside.
What? Is he kidding?
[ grunts ]
Hey! Oh, honestly!
I'm going in.
Come join me when you
want more polite company.
Be careful!
GUMBALL:
Whoa!
You got it!
[ thud ]
[ scoffs ]
What a wad.
Uh, a gum wad?
[ gasps ]
Fionnal!
[ chuckles ]
Let's ditch him.
[ guitar plays ]
Uhh...
Lumpy Space Prince is
throwing a party in the woods.
It's gonna be
freaky nasty.
Uhh...
| know you're going to say
"Yes" to me, so let's just go.
Whooaaaaaal!
[ mid-tempo music plays ]
Oh, yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, my God!
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Oh, you're bumping into me!
[ indistinct conversations |
[ both grunting ]
This looks fun.
Bunch.
Come on.
You guys!
Marshall Lee is gonna
play a song, you guys!
[ cheers and applause ]
[ chanting "Marshall!" ]
[ feedback, guitar strums ]
[ guitar plays ]
Follow my lead.
[ gasps ]
Hey!
È Good little girl È
È Ahh-ahh
> Always picking a
fight with me J
È You know that I'm bad È
È Ahh-ahh
JÈ But you're spending
the night with me
È What do you want
from my world?
2 You're a good
little girl È
È Ahh-ahh
> Bad little boy È
[ cheers and applause ]
È That's what
you're acting like JÈ
2 | really don't buy JÈ
È Ahh-ahh
> That you're that
kind of guy È
2 And if you are È
È Ahh È
È Why do you want to
hang out with me? È
È Ahh-ahh
[ hisses ]
[ chuckles evilly ]
Don't you know I'm a villain?
Every night I'm out killin',
sending everyone
runnin' like children.
| know why you're mad at me.
I've got demon eyes,
and they're looking right
through your anatomy
into your deepest fears.
Baby, I'm not from here.
I'm from the Nightosphere.
To me, you're clear,
transparent.
You've got a thing
for me, girl.
It's apparent.
Oh! Oh!
2 | got a hot potatah J
2 And | got two
hot tomatahs
È Well, they'll make
a good sauce, maybe )
You're not so bad,
you know?
[ chuckling ]
Not so bad?
I'm the son of a demon
and the Vampire King.
It's not something
| have to try at.
You, on the other hand...
È The table, for as
long as | am able )
I'm not trying to be bad.
I'm hanging out with
you because you're my friend.
What, like him?
[ exhales sharply ]
Pbht! Pbht!
No, different!
[ grunts ]
Hey! Hyah!
[ sarcastically ]
Oh, no!
[ laughs ]
Hyah!
- [ groans ]
[ laughs ]
- Whoa!
J Dah, dah, dah, dah, dah J
Whoo!
[ chuckles ]
Hey, break it up, you two!
- Meow!
- MARSHALL: Outta my way, Kitty.
[ gasps ]
Hey!
Oh, come on!
That was funny!
Cake! You okay?
Yeah.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Hey!
Come on. Where you goin'?
What's the deal?
[ stammers ]
You're missin' the party.
Fionna, lighten up!
Look, | don't care if
you're being a jerk to me,
but nobody messes with Cake.
Oh, really?!
Well, what if | just take
her right now, you know?
Meep!
What?!
Unexpected!
[ laughing evilly ]
W ETERE
Cake!
You want your Cake back?
Come...and...get her!
[ gasps ]
[ skeletons roaring ]
[ beat-boxing ]
Did you think | was lying?
| said I'm evil without even
trying, already dead,
so I'm not scared of dying.
Drinking the red from
your heart in one sitting.
You think you've got me pegged,
you must be kidding.
| raise the dead up,
and they do my bidding.
Girl, I'm a thousand years old,
I'm a riddle.
"Bad little boy."
Yes, I'm bad,
but not little.
Unh-unh, boy.
What are you thinking?
[ grunting ]
[ laughs evilly ]
Fionnal!
Cake!
Grab on to my little paws!
[ all grunting ]
[ roaring ]
- Oof!
- Aah!
[ groans ]
Marshall?
[ groaning ]
Oh, this is bad, guys.
This is really bad.
W ETERE
[ sizzling ]
Ah!
Come on.
You gotta be okay.
[ chuckling ]
| think this is it for me,
Fionna.
So, why don't you
just admit it?
You're in love with me.
[ gasps ]
| -- | get that you flirt
with me all the time,
and it's funny
and whatever,
but you're doing
that now?/
What are you trying
to do to my head?!
You think I've got
some little crush on you?!
Well, for however long
we've got left...
For once drop it,
you freak!
[ gasps ]
Faking it. Faking it.
Okay, my shirt is, like,
filled with cream puffs.
Oh, goodness.
Glob, Fionna.
You're like the realest
person I've ever met.
[ smack ]
Ow! Oh, my cheek meat!
[ chuckling ]
MARSHALL.:
Quit clowning, Fionna.
[ chuckling ]
Fionna?
Fionna!
[ smack ]
The end.
Oh, I love that one.
Oh, come on!
You guys got mad at
me for a bad story?!
| mean, it's cute,
but that's not how they'd be.
[ grunts ]
Well, look, it might not be too
late to polish this piece of --
Let's spitball some ideas.
Like, if Marshall Lee
gets sick and dies.
But he's got a brother
we didn't know about.
His name's Marshall Lee...Roy.
Boom!
Shocker!
Ah-ha, | feel goose bumps.
- | like how it is.
- We like how it is.
- Yeah, don't change it.
- Yeah. It's good.
Everyone get out.
Maybe we could start a
writing group or whatever.
[ sighs ]
| know you're out
there somewhere.
| just haven't figured
out how to get to you,
but, believe me, | will.
[ will.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!