[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ birds chirping ]
Oh, hello!
Ha ha!
Here for more graybles,
| presume?
Well, you've come to the right
computer-fable.
Feast your eyes-mabel
on my holo-pyramid viewer
and -- huh?
What's that?
Not in the mood for graybles,
you say?
Oh, dear.
Are you okay?
Did something fatlabel
happen to you?
Oh, | see.
You'd rather watch me buh-blabel
a birdhouse together
in my workshop.
Hmm.
More of a grayble man
by trade.
But okay! Come on!
[ hammering ]
Oh, hello again.
As you can see, the birdhouse
is nearly complete.
All that's left is
a "where the door hole goes,"
but | can't remember.
Hmm.
Door hole...
Wait!
| just remembered.
My door-hole solution lies
in one
of tonight's scheduled
graybles!
Would you mind if | look
through them to find it?
Okay! Ha ha!
Whee!
Here we go.
[ sighs ]
Hey, Jake, Jr.
You havin' fun at daddy's?
Hmm?
Oh. Sure, dad.
Okay.
You seem kind of dump trucks.
What?
Heh. You know,
"in the dumps.Ó
Oh, sorry. It's cool.
I'm just thinking about
the future, | guess.
We're on, like, the bleeding
edge of history.
Everything ahead of us is
totally unknown,
and there's no guarantee
that things are going to be
all right.
It's exciting, but it's also
pretty scary.
You know?
Heh heh... heh.
Sounds like my little baby girl
want to build a time machine!
Oooo000000h!
- Guys, | don't --
- No, no, no.
Leave it up to your daddy
and Uncle Finn.
Hup!
Okay.
You guys have fun.
I'm gonna get
some more juice.
Mom has some weird taste
in men.
FINN: Psst!
She's comin' back!
Ding-ding!
Skreeee!
[ whistling ]
[ fart noise ]
Hello-0-0-0-0?
Ooh!
Is that the-time machine
part that | ordered?
Mm-hmm!
You just got to sign for it to
prove you accepted delivery.
Ac-cept-tance.
Guys, I'm basically 30.
I'm not a little kid
anymore.
You're not
a little kid anymore!
[ sobbing ]
Cinnamon Bun, you can't sleep
with a night light anymore.
You're basically 30.
It's starting to bum
everyone out.
| can't handle this denial
Yeah, well...
[ door creaks ]
N0o0000000000000000!
Too dark!
No! It's too bright!
[ glass shatters |
Now it's too dark!
Oh.
Okay.
This is nice.
Wee-00, wee-00, wee-00!
CINNAMON BUN:
Aah! Too dark!
Hey, Cinnabun!
l... need...
soft... light!
Yeeaargh!
How long has this been
in here?
Don't even remember
buying this.
Oh, well.
Easy come, easy go.
[ whistling ]
Goodbye.
Well, that wasn't so bad.
[ humming ]
Hmm.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Nothing like a hard day's work
to get them spirits a-lifted!
[ laughing ]
Great news, fellas --
| finished all my chores,
SO we can start movie night early.
Take your seats, and | will
review the nominees.
We've got "Baby Ballet,"
"Blimby: Who Gots Da ABC's,"
"Airplanes Taking Off" --
[ gasps ]
Oh, wait!
What's this one?
"Basic Mortality: Season 1"?
Isn't this that show that
everyone's talking about?
| heard that this show is, like,
really good for penguins.
Wow. That's really lucky
for you guys.
I'm a little jealous.
Well, anyway, good luck to all
our nominees.
Okay!
All in favor of
"Blimby: Who Gots Da ABC's,"
raise your hands.
Okay!
All in favor of "Baby Ballet,"
raise your hands.
Okay!
All in favor of "Airpl--"
What?!
"Baby Ballet"?!
Come on! Ugh!
| never should've given you
penguins the right to vote.
Well, you may have numbers on
your side,
but I've still got
one trick up my sleeve --
bargaining!
Whereby, you let me watch
"Basic Mortality,"
and |, in return, will do
anything you want
in the whole world.
How about it?
[ penguins chattering ]
Ha ha!
Algebraic!
[ giggling ]
Look, | know he was
your partner.
Enough!
Alan is not
the super-murderer!
| don't know
about this show though.
This, Captain, is the most
lamentable super-murder
I've ever seen,
and I've seen plenty.
Might be a touch
too dark.
Too dark!
Too bright!
Eat on it!
Hmm! Hmm.
Oh, little lemonsweets,
our son...
SO precious.
You've enjoyed sitting
in your chair?
What would you like to do now?
"Go to bed."
- No, he wants to dance!
- [ grunts ]
[ humming ]
Ehn! Dearest brother,
| really think
Lemonsweets would rather
go to bed!
[ both grunting ]
Mnh!
Hunh!
I'll fetch our son
a sleeping bonnet.
Beautiful.
[ gasps ]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Brother, stop that!!
We hate you.
CEEEEEE L]
Only 0-0-0-0-0-0-0-0-ne!!
[ both grunting ]
The end!
My end!
My end... table.
My love seat, yeah.
Gee, but it's great to be
back home.
It's always a blast visiting
my cousin, City Fox,
at his future palace.
But you just can't beat that
old country steez.
City Fox's digs be
mad sterile.
Look at this.
This was my grandpa's rug.
Some bums let him have it
'cause it was so ugly.
[ clattering ]
And check out these classic
stylings!
They don't make 'em
like this anymore!
Whoa! Ha ha ha!
Almost got me right
in my both eyes!
[ clattering continues ]
[ bugs buzzing ]
Look at my bugs.
Man, | always did have
the ugliest bugs.
[ chuckles ]
What are they doing?
Selling each other houses?
Yes, sirree, there's some things
money can't buy.
You see that depression?
You can't buy that.
You gotta earn it.
Boy, it's like | can almost see
myself sleeping in there...
Yah!
Wh-What?
"Dear conscious self...
| know where some
buried treasure is.
I'll draw you a map.
Love, subconscious self."
Oh, my gosh!
I'm gonna be rich!
Ha ha!
[ pounding on door ]
What the --
- Whoop!
Oh, no!
My riches!
[ grunting ]
Let... me... in!
It's too bright!
[ gasps ]
Too dark!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Cinnamon Bun!
You... did a...
great job on this wall.
It's very... rustic.
[ sighs ]
Mmm... what a jerk.
What? A jerk?
Yeah, just give it
a little jerk.
Now that's
a time machine.
Hey, sweetie!
Sweetie, look -- your
time machine's all ready.
Oh, yeah.
You having fun, dad?
Aw, anything for my
baby pup.
Okay.
As long as you're having fun.
[ laughs ]
Time machine!
Shpiow!
[ both screaming ]
[ shouting in Korean ]
Ha ha!
There it is.
You see?
The birdhouse door --
it's right
above the peg thingy.
Why didn't | think of that?
Ha ha!
Well, | guess that's it
for this week.
I'll see you crimpy glimmers
on the --
What? What's that?
You want to finish
the grayble?
You want to see if you can
still guess the theme?
You just want to see
how it ends.
Well, let's get right
to it then.
Ha ha!
Stranger! Stranger!
Stranger! Stranger! Stranger!
Shh-shh-shh!
Stranger! Strang--
Excuse me.
Hey! Why're you trying
to steal my dad's stuff?!
Hey! | need a night light
because I'm so scared!
Man, you can't steal, dummy.
[ sobbing ]
Fine!
[ sobbing continues ]
Here.
Now get lost!
[ gasps ]
[ laughing ]
Ye-e-e-e-s!
Take that, Princess Bubblegum!
Jake Jr., I'm sorry for
messing up your time travel.
Ah, that's okay.
It was just make-believe
anyways.
FINN:
Oh. Was it?
Then how do you explain...
tomorrow's newspaper?
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!