[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
| think the swimming hole is
right around the corner!
Yes! Whoo! Whoo!
First one in
the water is
...um, first one
in the water!
[ grunts ]
No fair.
| have to take
off my stuff.
[ laughs ]
Aah!
[ grunting ]
[ giggles ]
BOTH:
Whoo-hoo!
[ both laugh ]
[ sparkle! ]
[ grunting ]
Faster!
We're getting a swirl!
You ready to get out?
Yeah, dude.
Let's get BMO
to make us some "Sassages,"
maybe with
that one mustard.
I'll use the
"Sassage" flare.
[ whistle! ]
Hopefully,
BMO sees that.
Didn't lady tell you not
to use the "Sassage" flare.
Yeah.
Well,
don't abuse it, man.
'ÔCause you're getting...
I'm getting what?
'Cause you're
getting fat.
[ whoosh!]
Nyang.
Aah!
Whoa.
Nyang.
Nyang, Nyang!
Ooh! Aah!
Nyang! Nyang! Nyang!
Hiya!
Nyang.
FINN:
Hey. Relax.
Grob, dude!
Your hat's alive!
[ laughs ]
[ giggles ]
This is crazy!
Gah Nyang.
He likes me!
[ sweetly ]
Nyang, Nyang, Nyang.
Nyang -- mm.
It's not my hat.
It's, like,
this other thing now.
Yeah, man.
Hat's can be anything --
pants, other people.
It's fine.
Yeah, but it's, like...
living now.
Yeah, it's a miracle.
Now he can listen to our
rad jokes and hang out.
Right.
Maybe it's
good he's alive.
You were a rad hat, and now
you're a rad... Little Dude.
Nyang.
Yo, bro!
Our eyes are down here.
Nyang!
Come on, Little Dude!
Let's go live life!
Nyang.
[ laughs ]
Yeah! Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
[ rumbling ]
Rah! Rah!
Ooh-mwah! Rah!
Ooh-aah!
[ gasps ]
[ screams ]
Aw, yeah! Aw, yeah!
BMO, Jakey likes!
Look at that spread!
| did it up
big time for you.
Hope you're hungry!
Ha ha!
You know it!
BMO,
this is Little Dude.
Hello.
Nyang?
Nyang!
[ chomp! ]
Cribes!
[ gasps ]
What?!
Aah! There's hot
grease next to us!
Don't fool around!
Nyang! Nyang!
Ooh! Ooh! Aah!
[ gasps ]
Oh, no!
Get off of me!
Little Dude, no!
You don't jump on heads!
That junk is rude,
Little Dude!
You okay, BMO?
| am fine, Finn.
| just thought you
kept better company.
Sorry, BMO.
He's just excited.
Nyang! Nyang! Nyang! Nyang!
N-nyang-yang-yang!
Nyang! N-n-nyang! N-n--
Sorry, Little Dude.
But | got to eat.
Don't touch anything!
I'm still frying
up garnish!
Okay.
Yeah. Okay.
[ both munching ]
Your head looks weird
with short hair, man.
It feels like a peach.
[ grunting ]
Hey! Little Dude!
Y'all can get in on this
if you promise to be good.
[ growls ]
Only good babies [chomping]
get "sassages."
[ grunting ]
Nyang!
Hey, don't eat the --
the -- the food?
[ sniffs, gags |
Dude, he turned
it into poo!
This is poo now!
Smell it!
[ sniffs ]
Yep.
BOTH:
Little Dude!
Quit it!
Gotchal
Oh, little deezy.
What am | gonna
do with you?
You guys should
get ready for bed.
Yeah. Okay.
Hmm!
Oow!
BMO hit you on the butt.
[ chuckles ]
[ breathing heavily ]
N-Nyang. Nyang.
Shilll
Little Dude, you got to chill.
Nyar. Nyar. Nyar.
Night-night.
Nyar-r-r-r-r.
R-r-r-r-r-nyang!
Nyang.
Nyang?
[ panting ]
[ fearfully ]
Nyuuuur.
[ footsteps ]
Jake! Wake up!
Someone's on the house!
It's probably
Ice King again, dude.
Man, we should tell him
we know he sleeps
on the top of
our house.
[ glass shatters |
Oh.
[ wheezing ]
[ gasps ]
[ grunts ]
No, no, no!
[ gasps ]
No! Not on my head!
Pooh buns!
Pooh buns on my head!
[ screams ]
[ grunting ]
Gross.
[ wheezing ]
[ gasps ]
[ stretch! ]
[ wheezing ]
Ninja.
Eh?
[ grunts ]
Oh, uh, nyah.
Aah! Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho! Ha.
What are you doing
in our house, homey?
Please, don't hurt me!
You're in grave danger,
and it's all my fault!
Wha?
What are you talking about?
Your hat accidentally
touched my head flower.
See?
[ shing! ]
My magic imbues anything it
touches with an evil spirit --
One that craves
destruction and chaos!
Yuck.
[ groaning ]
| buried myself so that nothing
would touch my body ever again!
But then this bloom
grew out of my head.
C'est la vie.
Evil magic donks,
homey.
I'm sorry.
That's just the
way my magic works.
Papa always said
| was a bad wizard.
Right, Papa?!
"Baby's a bad wizard."
"A bad wizard," huh?!
You're a bad wizard!
[ sobbing ]
I'm a bad wizard!
Whoa. Cool it, man.
Let's just fix Little Dude.
[ sniffling ]
Uh, yeah.
[ sniffles ]
Okay.
BMO:
Guys!
Your stanky friend
jumped out the window
and ran toward the
Candy Kingdom!
[ whistling ]
Oh, hello.
Aren't you a cutie?
Hey, are you lost,
tiny gentleman?
Nyang.
[ muffled screaming ]
[ whir! ]
[rip!]
Nyang, Nyang.
[ both breathing heavily ]
Where is he?
Little Dude?
Little Dude?!
[ slurring ]
Nyang!
Pbht!
Nyang?
[ neighs ]
Pbht!
[ imitates gun cocking ]
Nyang.
Blisterin' beef!
[ Whoosh! Crash! ]
[ Clang! Clang! ]
[ Boom! ]
N-n-nyang.
N-n-n-yang-yang-yang.
- No, Little Dude!
- Nyang?
That's a bad
Little Dude!
Nyang!
[ neighs ]
Aah! The horsey!
[ Whoosh! Splat! ]
[ laughing ]
Na-na-yang-yang.
[ both breathing heavily ]
Hiya! Little Dude!
Nyang!
You were supposed
to be my buddy!
[ grunts ]
[ boink! ]
All my fault.
All my fault!
You're a --
N-n-n-n-nyang!
Wha!
Oh, gleeble snoots.
How is he so strong?
Whomever the hat possesses gains
the proportional strength of a hat.
Look out!
He's got the horse again!
[ roars ]
[ boink! ]
[ crackle! ]
Evil presence detected.
[ imitates siren ]
[ clunk! ]
[ grunting ]
Sorry, fellas.
| don't thrive in
conflict situations!
[ grunting ]
Evil.
Nyang?
[ twinkle! twinkle! ]
Nyang.
[ whir! ]
[ laughing ]
Nyang.
No!
Not the Gumball Guardian!
Evil.
[ laughing ]
Nyang.
Na-yang.
[ whoosh!]
Dude! Use your powers!
| can't!
All | can do is think about my
papa and how much
| disappoint him!
[ whir! ]
[ zap!]
[ shing! ]
Just think of
something positive!
Something comforting!
Like... my mommy?
When | came home with bad grades
from Wizard School,
my mommy used to
hug me and hug me.
[ giggles ]
Oh, mommy!
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
Uh, yeah.
Just think about your
mom and use your magic.
Uh, okay, let's try this.
... love my mommy.
[ whir! ]
Hugs. Aww. I'll hug you.
I'l hug you. Hug me.
Ooh! It worked!
| love my mommy!
[ whir! ]
[ warble! ]
Hi, fellas.
| love being alive.
[ whir! ]
Mommy!
I'm a window,
and I'll hug you!
Mommy!
[ warble! ]
Ha ha!
| feel like
hugging everybody!
Hi, mommy!
[ whir! ]
2 I'm going to hug you JÈ
Mommy.
[ whir! ]
[ laughs ]
Ha! Somebody get this
guy some clothes.
[ chuckles ]
Now -- Now rise up, love buddies,
and hug your gross
brother into submission!
Gonna squeeze the
heck out of him!
I love that guy!
Nya-a-a-ng!
We love you.
I'm loving youl!
Hug his face!
| love youl!
Hey, pal,
we're working together!
[ giggles ]
Come on!
Let's be Pal-jamsas.
P-pal-jamas. Pajamas.
[ straining ]
Nyang! Nyang!
[ zap! zap! ]
[ whoosh!]
Nyang. Nyang.
Thank you,
my newly conscious bros.
Now return your
life-forces to me.
- | loved every minute!
- Yay!
Not living!
Nyang. Nyang!
Ymmom!
[ warble! ]
Duh?
Yes!
Poor Little Dude.
He was just doing it up
the only way he knew how.
It's not his fault
he was created evil.
Yeah.
He deserves to
come back good.
Wizard, mommy-magic
this dude back to life.
Okay.
Mommy.
N-n-n-n-nyal!
Oh, my goodness!
What is this lovely place?
Life, man!
| see.
And this dude
is your pops.
[ chuckles ]
No, I-I --
Oh, | guess | am. Huh.
Be good to this dude.
I will -- way better
than my papa was to me!
Yep. That's the idea.
Jake, looks like
| need a new hat.
Okay, let's go
skin an evil bear.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!