[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ both grunting ]
Oh!
Ha ha! | win!
Oh. Hey, man.
You and BMO play
finger spread quietly.
| need to get
into the zone.
[ chimes tinkling ]
| am ready to receive
instruction
from the realm of
creation above me
for the sandwich | am
about to conceive.
| am open.
Use me.
[ orchestral music plays ]
[ breathes deeply ]
1,2,3,4,5,6.
Rosemary, thyme.
[inhales ]
Sous-vide.
Keep that at 135 degrees.
All right,
now we're getting somewhere.
Cream cheese...
pickles from my boy Prismo...
and some dill!
[ bird squawks ]
Diced boiled eggs!
Bird from the window!
Yeah, baby,
now we're rolling!
Whoo!
Common cucumber!
Sliced roma tomato.
Sweet yellow onion, organic.
[ sniffles, crying ]
Almost done.
Tears for salt.
Meat prepared sous-vide.
[ singsong ]
Bacon.
You're the most
important part.
[ lobster shrieks ]
Lobster soul.
It's amazing.
Ohh-oh.
This is the greatest
sandwich I've ever made.
Is it glowing?
You guys want some?
It's cool, man.
| know you want to
eat the whole thing,
and I'm cool with that.
Thank you.
[ gasps ]
Magic Man!
Magic Dog!
I'll take some sandwich.
You stay away from my woman --
eh, my sandwich!
Hmm, yeah, | cou/d do that.
Or...
wait.
Wait.
[ gasps ]
Sandwiche!
Mijo!
Magic Man!
My sandwich!
That's a good-looking
sandwich.
What are you gonna
do with it?
Something gross?
[ breathes deeply ]
It's got my germs,
so it's mine now.
N-0-0-0-0-0!
Dead arms!
[ grunting ]
Give it back,
you animal!
Look, if you really
want your sandwich,
you'll have to
solve my little riddle.
Unh!
When your face shows 7:20,
when green leaves turn brown,
the only way
forward is down.
Then you'll see,
the wetter, the better.
That's not
even a riddle.
It's word play,
at best!
You try and come up with
something on the spot!
It's hard!
Aah!
Now to savor the moment.
It's just you and me, baby.
[ finger clicks ]
What the --
NEVCRVEL
[ grumbles ]
What's he doin'
in there?
Why did he freeze
himself with my sandwich?
He's not frozen.
He's super-slow-mozen,
motion.
Look.
Aw! That's gross!
Well, let's go grab it
before he hits the ground,
which is when | assume
he'll take a bite.
Yeah, okay.
Hmm.
Feels like
cold spaghetti.
Oh...hey, Jake.
Hey, Finn.
How...long...have...
we...been... in ...here?
l...don't...know.
Retre-e-a-at!
[ both grunting ]
[ both gasp, panting ]
Whoa.
How long were
we in there?
Five hours.
Five hours?!
He's halfway to
hittin' the ground!
Which is when he'll bite
my sandwich, probably.
Yes.
[ groans ]
BMO!
| agree that is when he
will probably take a bite.
You're not helping.
Oh. You need help?
| can help.
Processing.
Must be his new software.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Ding!
| have the solution, Jake.
What?!
BMO, are you serious?
Yes, this plan will work.
Yes!
But we have to hurry.
All right, BMO!
Wait, wait, wait.
BMO, are you just making
a skateboard video?
No, Finn.
This is the plan.
Are you sure?
Jake, you will have your
sandwich back before
my board hits the ground.
Okay, BMO.
Yay, BMO!
He lied to me.
Relax.
I'm calling
Princess Bubblegum.
It's ringing.
[ sighs ] Maybe | should
just make another one.
[ orchestral music plays ]
[ sighs deeply ]
Eh, okay.
Let's do this.
| can make another
awesome sandwich.
Creation realm,
inspire me once again!
[ chimes play off-key ]
Okay...
Thanks again for coming,
Prubbles.
Of course, Finn.
Once you explained about
Jake's sandwich, | had to.
So, how's it looking?
I'm picking up
major levels here.
Of magic?
Molasses.
Oh.
He's using a molasses-based
supercovalent subatomic bond,
slowing down anything
that enters its field,
but only if the molasses
is at room temperature.
Mm, this one.
My molasses warmer will
get things moving.
[ whirring ]
Well, I'm out of ideas.
Who are you calling?
Marceline.
The Vampire Queen?!
Oh.
Maybe...
Maybe it's just as good!
Blaagh!
It's terrible!
[ crying ]
Dang you, Magic Man.
You took my one and only!
BUBBLEGUM: See, | think
the molasses must be protected by
some sort of chemical --
Oh, hey, Jake.
How are you holding up?
Not too well.
BMO looks cool though.
[ sighs ]
Don't be sad.
Yeah, Marceline's
got a great plan.
Yeah, man!
What's your plan?
Demon juice!
R-a-a-a-a-a-a-h!
R-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a...
Hey, man.
What are you doing?
I'm lighting these candles
so | can move on with
the grieving process.
| made them with the leftover
bacon fat from my sand--
[ sobbing ]
| am not giving up.
Let's see.
Who should | call?
Ice King? Shelby?
Tree Trunks?
Tree Trunks?!
No, man, don't call
Tree Trunks!
What's she gonna do?!
Bake an apple pie?!
Don't you get it?!
It's over.
It's over, and I've
never been so sad.
And you know what?
| got to deal with it.
Jake, look!
Hmm?
What? But how?
Because you've never
been this sad!
That's what Magic Man meant
by your face showing 7:20,
or as some people
call it, a sad face.
What?
Nobody calls
it th-a-a-a-a-at!
Nope! No!
Don't get judgmental.
Stay sad.
Right.
Magic Man, I'm gonna
sock you in the head!
Ha ha! Ha ha ha!
Ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...
Jake, every time you
get happy, you slow down!
Stay sad, man!
Make yourself sad!
Uh...okay!
[ crying ]
J-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-ake!
It's okay, Lady.
You got to let go.
He's gone now.
Let me take you
out for a coffee,
get your mind off things.
[ speaking Korean ]
Hey, Lady,
I'm here for you.
Don't you ever forget that.
Hey, Mr. Cupcake,
you stay away ...from ...Lady!
FINN:
No, man!
Stay sad!
Make yourself sad!
Uh...
| -- I love you, Jake.
We should have
hung out more.
What?
Um, | love you too,
Mr. Cupcake.
| didn't want to hang
because | thought Lady
was into your muscles.
And | thought if
we'd hung out,
you'd sweet-talk her
and take her from me.
What?
| would never.
| have got so much
respect for you.
Dude, | have so much
| try to be like you in
some aspects of my life.
Look, if something were
to happen to me,
and | wasn't here anymore,
I'd want you to take care
of Lady and the kids.
That means so much to me.
[ crying ]
| wish we had more
time together.
Me...too!
[ sobbing ]
Yeah, Jake!
The wetter, the better!
Keep crying!
I'm sorry, Mr. Cupcake!
Unh!
Oofl
[ groaning ]
Hunh!
Boardslide!
[ groans ]
[ sobbing ]
Ah-haaaa!
Yay!
| got you, baby.
[ sobbing ]
Sandwich is so good!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!