[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ humming ]
Hmm?
Oh, hello there.
[ laughs ]
Baybel Navel,
it's great to see you!
Here for more graybles,
| reckon.
Well, all right.
Just like last time, we'll watch
five separate stories,
each relating to one
special theme.
Guess the theme by the end
of the episode
and you'll be
the freshest mint-whistle.
[ chuckles ]
Now, look to my visualizer
screen
and let this exciting grayble
dribble all over your
mind-label.
[ laughs ]
Okay, so --
[ chicken clucks ]
Scooch.
Okay, so I'm still pretty sure
this old book's some warlock's
spell book or something.
[ whoosh!]
FINN:
Messed!
Warlocks, dude.
You ready for some ancient
feel-good spellcraft?
Yeah, I'll try it.
Could always stand
to feel better.
Let's see...
you got your bibby?
Check it.
[ snap! ]
Yep.
Little Jack Horner
sat in the corner,
eating a Christmas pie.
He put in his thumb and pulled
out a plum and said,
"what a good boy am 1."
[ squish! ]
| don't feel like a good boy.
You sure you read
the spell right?
Mmm. Yeah.
[ chomp! ]
Still, though... pretty sweet.
Wanna keep sticking our thumbs
in stuff until it works?
Yeah!
[ squish! ]
Oh, what a good boy am !
Oh, what a good boy
am |.
Oh what a good
boy am I.
Oh, what
a good boy am !
Oh, what a good boy
am |.
Oh, what a good
boy am I.
[ breathing heavily ]
Oh, what
a good boy am |.
Oh, what a good boy --
[ inhales deeply ]
Do you feel like a good boy?
No, | don't.
Hey, check out that
gross toad!
[ toad croaks ]
BOTH:
Oh, what a good boy am I.
Gross. Cut it out.
Quit sticking your thumbs
in my back.
Yeah, | don't know.
[ groans ]
Geez, I'm never going
to find this place!
Hmm...
> [ drum rhythm plays ]
Hey!
[ drum rhythm continues ]
MARCELINE:
Hey!
Hey, Rock Giant.
[ drums rhythms stop ]
You seem cool!
Do you know where Wizard Bill's
music shop is?
| can't find it anywhere.
He's got a guitar that plays
the most savory licks in Ooo.
[ rumbling ]
[ crash! ] [ clang! ]
[ babbling ]
Huh.
[ breathes deeply ]
I've got an idea.
Okay, point now!
Aah!
[ laughs ]
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
[ laughing ]
Thanks, man!
[ bell rings ]
[ guitar music plays ] È
Hey, let's find some
more holes.
J La-da-da, la-da-da È
È [ humming ] 2
BOTH:
Oh, what a good boy am !
[ laughs ]
Boys, your manners.
Oh! Oops!
Oh, [chuckles]
SHELBY:
Hey, Tree Trunks.
Excuse me sir, | wasn't
looking where | was --
- Tree Trunks, up here!
- Oh, no!
Heavens no!
MAN:
I'm glad you brought this matter
to the authorities, ma'am.
Now what exactly happened?
Yes, thank you.
I-I heard a man calling out
to me "Oh, Tree Trunks."
So | said "Who's calling?
| don't know."
So | looked, and he was making
a rude gesture.
It left a sour taste
in my mouth.
All right, maÔam.
Let's see.
How do you spell your name?
- Okay.
-...E.
- Hold on one second.
Ugh, I'm sorry,
but the wheels of justice
spin too slowly.
I'm going to have
to take the law
into my own hands.
Thank you all for coming.
The police have failed me
in my time of need,
so | have brought you here
together.
A posse.
I made you all blackjacks
in case things get ugly.
| stuffed some of my stockings
with balled-up newspapers.
I made a big one for you because
you're so strong.
All right, then.
Let's clean up these streets!
Ohh!
There he is!
Goodness!
BOTH:
Eeeeee!
[ both grunting ]
Oh!
Why -- it's just a statue.
|-l don't understand.
It was so rude before.
SHELBY:
Hey, Tree Trunks!
Oh!
Hey, Tree Trunks,
how are you?
Shelby, have you been up
there all day?
Yes.
Just reading this book!
Oh, well, can you read
somewhere else?
You kind of offended
Tree Trunks here.
What?
Uh... uh...
Oh.
Oh!
[ laughs ]
| get it.
Wonderful!
Family meeting!
Family meeting, gather 'round.
Things are gonna change
around here very soon.
You're gonna have a new mommy
to help boss you around.
I mean, well, | haven't exactly
asked her yet.
Well, no time
like the present.
[ singing indistinctly ]
Sweetie, are you awake?
Great, 'cause I've got a query
I've been meaning
to inquire of you.
Well... uh...
[ giggles ]
Oh, well...
when two people...
[ crying ]
Yes, yes, drink up the tears.
Drink up those
good luck tears.
No, not you Gunther.
You're on a low salt diet.
Huh?
What's that dear?
Oh, | almost forgot.
5 Doo, doo-doo, doo-doo
It's a wife ring.
This one's for me.
I'm the husband.
That means | get the remote
control three days a week,
and you get it four.
[ laughs ]
Ahh, sweetie, this is bliss.
Feels so math
to finally be normal,
not like those two
freaks.
What are they doing
over there?
Anyway, | --
Ooh, who's that?
Oh.
Oh, my.
BMO:
Poor Football, you've come so far
and still have
so much to learn.
But | don't understand, BMO.
I'm a real baby girl now.
| can smell raddest lilacs.
I'm can hear
the screaming squirrels,
screaming for nuts.
Oh, my gosh.
| can't believe it's true.
No, Football.
That's not enough.
You have to learn manners,
too.
Otherwise,
you'll be all alone.
Alone?
But -- but what
about you, BMO?
| will not always be here
to protect you, Football.
No, you must learn.
Here, look.
This is a grapefruit spoon.
It's only for eating
grapefruits.
This is a salt shaker.
Here, you try.
[ giggles ]
Now, this a turnip
grincher...
For grinching.
And this is how
you drink tea.
[ clink! ]
[ slurp!]
Ahh!
Like this?
[ slurp!]
Yuck.
It's bitter.
No, no.
Football, like this.
[ slurp!]
Like this?
No, like this.
[ slurp!]
Like this?
[ spark! ]
Like this!
[ slurp!]
Like this, right?
No, Football.
Do it like -- huh?
Pbht!
Sorry, Football.
Lesson's over for tonight.
FINN:
[ sighs wearily ]
Why so glum, fellas?
We stuck our thumbs in
almost every hole today.
But we never felt like
good boys.
[ chuckles ]
| know a thing or two
about good boys.
Why don't you try sticking
your thumbs in these holes?
Controllers?
BOTH:
Oh, yeah!
"Super Good Boys."
[ horn honks ]
BMO:
[ giggles ]
So, did you guess the theme?
Go ahead and pause
your viewer now
if you need a few
more glaybels
to think about it
a little.
Oh, oh.
[chuckles]
Now you've got it.
| can tell.
That's right.
The theme is
"The Five Tastes."
You see, Jake ate
a sweef plum.
Marceline played
some savory licks.
Tree Trunks had a sourtaste
inside her mouth.
Oh, my.
Gunther wanted to drink
the salty tears.
And Football's tea
was bitter.
[ laughs ]
Huh? What?
What's that you say?
You thought the theme was
the "Five Fingers"?
[ laughs ]
Don't be silly.
Nobody's had five fingers for
20 blabillion glaybels.
[ laughs ]
Five telepathy glands, maybe.
[ sighs ]
Slimmin'.
Well, anyway, looks like
it's that time again.
I'll see you crimpy glimmers on
the triode flimpin' the diode.
[ laughs ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!