[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
FINN:
[ humming ]
È Oh, it's just my luck È
D I went on a walk
and | found a truck
È Oh, it's just my luck È
> When | honk this horn J
2 I'll wake Jake up È
[ horn honks ]
Jake, wake up!
| found a truck!
What?
What's happening?
Whoa!
Where did you
get this baby?
| found it
in the woods.
| named it...Hot Daniel.
Anyway, | figure we can do some
pretty sick stuff with it.
Oh, yeah?
Like what?
Mm, | don't know.
Launch it off some ramps, maybe
get it going 30 miles per hour,
crank the wheel into a
Gnar right-hander,
spray dirt everywhere, like a
big hirkin' dirt-wave.
Yeah, buddy! Nice!
Let's crank this beast up!
Can't.
Engine's busted, | think.
Nuts.
BMO, you know
anything about cars?
[ beeps ]
Nope.
Hmm.
Maybe...
Ice King, you know
anything about cars?!
Nope, not a car guy.
Too confusing.
Got better things to
do with my life.
Mm.
Wait.
| know someone
who's good with mechanics.
Hey! Hey, guys! Hi!
Hey!
Hey, Banana Man.
Wow!
I haven't seen you fellas since
you destroyed my home, my land,
and my rocket.
Oh, geez, yeah.
Sorry, Banana Man.
Just sort of happened.
Don't worry about it.
Bygones.
I'm just excited you
called me over.
We're neighbors.
We should help each other out.
| got the soda and the jams.
ALL:
Cool!
| see the problem.
The top of your engine is gone,
specifically the cylinder head.
Hmm. Okay.
That word sounds cool.
But what does it mean?
Let me explain.
The cylinder head is the
top to the cylinder block.
Think of the cylinder head as an
airtight lid to your engine that
regulates air,
fuel, and exhaust.
Okay, cool.
Informative.
What is he pointing at?
Now, this lid is important
because it works to get fuel
into your engine.
[ clears throat ]
You see, your engine has
cylinders,
and in these
cylinders are pistons.
[ clears throat ]
When the piston in
the cylinder moves down,
it creates a vacuum,
pulling in fuel
from the intake.
You mean an
air-fuel mixture?
That's right, BMO.
Have a gold star, dear.
Yay! BMO is so
pretty and smart!
Then the piston
returns to the top,
compressing the
air-fuel mixture.
Then, a spark plug fires off,
creating an explosion,
driving the piston back down,
powering the engine.
[ clears throat ]
Sweet!
So where's the
cylinder head, then?
Hmm.
Well, sometimes people
store parts they are
working on in the car.
Ah! Bingo!
Found it.
Yeah! Drive time!
Well, not quite.
We don't know why they
took the cylinder head off.
It could be cracked,
the gasket head could be warped,
the rod bearings could
have damage from water.
You see, that's the
cool thing about cars.
[ clears throat ]
One tiny little thing
messes everything else up,
so nothing works.
Soit's up to us
to figure it out!
Cool.
Yeah, all right.
BANANA MAN:
2 Fixing a truck with the neighbors JÈ
> Not a better way
to spend some time )
È Hoping to see if
they like me )
> Using automotive savvy È
È Do a good job È
È They'll give me props 2
Bam!
D I'm asked to come
back tomorrow )
D A future | see with
them and me, best buds )
È Hanging out forever JÈ
JÈ Board-game Friday nights È
JÈ Best-friend
pillow fights È
È Hanging out forever JÈ
> Board-game
Friday nights È
È Hanging out forever JÈ
JÈ Best-friend pillow fights È
Whew! I'm bushed.
You guys want to pick this
up again in the morning?
- Sure.
- Sounds good.
Not BMO.
This grease monkey's torqued
up on automotive science.
Yeah, boyee!
Okay, BMO.
Good night, Banana Man.
Have a good evening, gents.
[ tone plays ]
Time for the night shift.
RADIQO: /t's 10 past the hour,
and this is "graveyard shift,"Ó
hosted by me,
Starchy the Gravedigger,
your weekly five-hour dose
of all the strange haints,
phantasmagoria,
and phenomena | see workin'in
the Candy Kingdom graveyard.
Hello, caller.
You're on the
"Graveyard Shift."Ó
Wha-- am [ --
Oh, hi.
Um, long-time listener,
first-time caller.
So, um, | think Princess
Bubblegum has been replaced by,
like, a lizard person.
A lizard?
Yeah, a lizard.
/ love your show!
Oh, Starchy's very
interested in this topic.
What led you to
this discovery, caller?
Ha! They are wrong!
You look more like
a hippo than a lizard.
Well, um, my friend is a very
highly placed official in the
Candy Kingdom,
and I've noticed --
BANANA MAN:
Hi, BMO.
Yow!
Stay back, Lizard!
Oh, sorry, BMO.
| didn't mean to startle you.
| couldn't sleep.
| kept thinking
about the truck.
And biodiesel!
Oh! And | figured out what's
wrong with the engine block.
So, what are
you working on?
Aerodynamics.
Swe-e-e-e-et.
You know, it's been really nice
hanging with you fellas and
working on the car...
it gets a little lonely at my
space-age banana dome.
You don't have
a girlfriend?
No.
| -- 1 don't want to be alone,
but, uh...
I've gotten pretty
good at it.
| putter around the house,
keeping busy with
my little projects.
But it would be
nice to find someone.
STARCHY:
Hold up.
Princess, is that you?
[ clicks |
Oh, Spooky.
Yo, BMO, coffee.
Thank you.
Car looks nice, BMO.
Yeah.
[ snoring ]
Oh, aah! | fixed it!
Are we best friends yet?!
Oh. Oh, hey.
-l fixed it.
| discovered the
cylinder head was warped,
so | went to the junkyard
and got a new one.
Bingo.
Whoo.
[ muffled shouting ]
Biodiesel!
[ breathes deeply ]
[ engine turns over ]
[ backfires ]
ALL:
Yeah!
[ tires screeching ]
Whoo-hoo!
[ all screaming ]
Awes-0-0-0-ome!
[ laughing ]
Yowee wow.
[ brakes squeal ]
She's beautiful.
Well, then go over
and talk to her!
Yeah. Come on, Banana Man.
You're lonely!
Oh, no. That's okay.
Having someone to love
takes up time | could use
to work on stuff.
That's the craziest
thing | ever heard.
[ engine revs ]
[ tires screech ]
Pardon me, Miss.
My friend here is super-smart,
and he rebuilt this truck.
He's very smart
and very single.
Okay...
Anyway, his name
is Banana Man.
If you like what you see,
give him a call.
[ tires screeching ]
[ coughing ]
[ grumbles ]
[ tires screech ]
Help m-e-e-e-e-e!
We got to save Bubblegum!
No, Finn! She's a lizard!
You got to stop listening to
all those conspiracy shows.
They twist up your noodle so
you can't tell what's real.
Look, there she is!
[ panting ]
Whoa!
You want some tea?
[ panting ]
Sure.
[ teapot whistling ]
Thanks, Jake.
So, what's up with
the angry mob, PB?
[ sighs ]
They think I've been replaced
with an evil lizard replicant.
It's sheer nonsense.
Eat this bug!
Lizard!
[ hisses ]
[ all screaming ]
[ roars ]
[ tires screech ]
Punch it, 'Nana Man!
[ tires screeching ]
[ roars ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hyah!
[ tires screeching ]
[ grunts ]
[ breathing heavy |
What the fridge?
Whoa!
Finn, Jake!
Reptilian synthoid
replicants are trying
to take over the Kingdom!
Yeah, we know.
Kill it!
No! No!
I'm the real onel!
[ grumbles ]
BANANA WOMAN:
Hey, speedy.
Unh!
You're coming with me.
What?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
'ÔCause you ain't got
enough peel on that nanner.
You're under arrest
for public indecency!
Bye, Banana Man!
[ laughing ]
[ sobbing ]
It's not fair!
It's okay, BMO.
It's a very mild offense.
It's not like that.
Hot Daniel is dead!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!