[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's adventure time È
È Oh, oh, BMO È
È How'd you get
so pregnant? È
D> Who's the mother? È
5 Oh, who's the father? È
> Shh, I'll tell you È
2 If you keep it a secret )
[ smooches ]
È We will È
> We will È
2 All right, last night
an electric presence
È Came into my
room and said È
È "BMO, | need your perfect body
to host the human incarnation
of a baby!" >
[ gasps ]
[ sobbing ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
BMO, what's wrong?
[ sobbing ]
| think he
broke his egg.
Hey, it's okay, BMO.
[ sobbing ]
Look, Jake and I'll
make you a funny face.
[ sobbing stops |
BOTH:
Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
[ sobbing ]
Here, BMO,
this'll cheer you up.
What the...
[ muffled screaming ]
[ sobbing ]
[ panting ]
Well...
I'm out of ideas.
What?
[ neighs ]
[ neighing ]
Ja-a-mes Baxter!
[ giggling ]
Aw, man!
James Baxter is so good, man!
He always knows just what
to say to cheer a guy up.
Yeah, man.
[ neighs ]
[ neighing ]
Ja-a-mes Baxter!
James Baxter!
So good!
[\ ETal
We should do it, too --
do his thing and spread
the good will!
Yeah, man!
| want to be like
James Baxter,
always rollin' in
on his beach ball,
sayin' his name
in a horse voice,
makin' people smile!
[ sighs ]
Let's do it!
[ laughs ]
Yeah!
[ neighing ]
Fi-i-nn the huma-a-n!
Ja-a-ake!
[ neighing ]
F-i-nn!
Ja-a-ke!
Sheesh. Tough crowd.
| think we should find an
easier person to cheer up.
It was a mistake to do
this at a funeral.
[ coffin rumbling ]
[ laughs, sighs ]
[ splat! ]
Ah!
[ whimpers ]
[ sobbing ]
[ neighing ]
Fi-i-nn!
Ja-a-ke!
[ shrieks ]
[ neighing ]
Fi-i-nn!
Ja-a-ke!
[ screaming, panting ]
[ neighing ]
Fi-i-nn!
Ja-a-ke!
What do you want?!
Please!
I'm just a very sad girl!
[ neighing ]
Fi-i-nn!
Ja-a-ke!
[ shrieking ]
[ both neighing ]
[ sighs ]
[ laughter ]
[ neighs ]
Baxter!
James!
That's so perfect.
Yeah, man.
So unique.
[ neighing ]
Ja-a-mes Baxter!
Man, what's he doing
that we're not?
We just got to figure that out!
No...it's like...
he's shredding on a guitar,
and learning how to shred isn't
just copying the exact notes
of someone else's solo.
You need to learn how
to do your own solo!
[ imitates electric guitar ]
FINN:
Bling, blong!
Wah-wah-whoo,
wah-wah-wah wah-wah-whoo!
Wah-wah-wah-wah!
Whoop!
Whooopsh!
Wah wah-wah!
Na-na-na-na-na!
Boodala-boodala-boodala-boodala!
[ both vocalizing ]
Why am | recording?
You're documenting our
creative flow in case
we make a breakthrough.
Dude, I think we
do got something.
Let's check the video!
[ giggling ]
Bathtub! Bathtub!
All right, BMO,
play the video.
[ both vocalizing ]
Who's gonna scrub me?
I'll scrub.
You take notes.
[ both vocalizing ]
Yeah, right there.
Speed it up.
Slow it down.
[ laughs ]
[ chuckles ]
Yeah! That sounds makes
me feel happy!
Good, good!
Happy's what we want.
BMO,
zoom in on my mouth!
[ laughter ]
Yeah, it's good, but if we
want to be James Baxter good,
we got to go deeper.
The Institute of So-und.
FINN:
Hey! Hey, man!
| receive you.
Welcome to the Sound
Institute of So-und.
Where is the studio to make
the best feel-good sound?
Just think happy thoughts and
follow the beat of your hearts.
Hmm.
[ heart beating ]
Hold up.
This way.
[ heartbeat quickens ]
[ gasps ]
[ equipment crackling ]
Look at this tricked-out studio.
Half stacks,
full stacks!
Oh!
Distortion pedals!
[ both vocalizing ]
[ vocalizing distorts, echoes ]
These sounds make
feel good right here!
Right here! Good!
| feel it here!
Good here!
We need to figure out
how to make our sound...
force happiness
into the listener!
[ both vocalizing ]
Whoa!
[ laughing ]
[ slurps ]
Check our data?
FINN:
Maybe it should be higher?
JAKE: Yeah, maybe --
maybe it could be lower --
| don't know.
Let's both agree that
that sound belongs there.
See that sound?
| drew that sound connecting
to two other sounds.
Hmm.
Something's missing,
though.
[ both gasp ]
That's it!
The missing thing
in our thing!
Yeah!
James Baxter don't just
got his catch phrase --
he's also got his
beach-ball biz.
So we got to create
feel-good body actions
to go with
our feel-good sound!
We just crushed it,
homey.
Dude, seriously, | think our
thing is gonna change the world.
When people experience it,
it's gonna make them so happy.
You're building
it up too much.
[ yawns ]
Let's just do it.
[ sleepily ]
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
[ thud! ]
[ bubble! |
Hey!
There's the sad girl.
[ sobbing, sniffling ]
What?
[ shrieks ]
No, no, no!
Wait a sec!
Reserve judgment until
you've seen the
freshed-up version of
our thing!
I EEL
[ both vocalizing ]
[ giggling ]
BOTH:
We did it!
[ all moaning ]
TOGETHER:
Bummed.
What's wrong?
We're bummed.
[ both vocalizing ]
[ laughter ]
Boo.
Boo?
[ both vocalizing ]
[ laughing ]
Boo!
[ nervously ]
Common rhinoceros beetle...
scientific name --
xylotrupes Ulysses.
Common dung beetle --
Oh, my!
[ both vocalizing ]
[ laughing ]
[ crowd cheering ]
[ both panting ]
Oh, good.
You're still here.
Hey, | know we were
here yesterday...
[ coughs nervously ]
...and we came off
as inappropriate --
Dude, let's just
do the thing!
Right, okay.
[ both vocalizing ]
[ laughter ]
[ coffin rumbling ]
[ winces ]
[ bones crunching ]
[ laughter continues ]
[ all screaming ]
[ both wince ]
[ panting ]
Dude!
[ bones rattling ]
[ grunts ]
Why have you
upset my deal?!
Jake, come on, man.
| need some help.
Sorry.
| acted like a
little kitty cat.
Hyup!
I EEL
[ bloosh! ]
Whoa!
It's milk!
Why?!
Dang, this is real.
Aah!
[ groans ]
He broke my squishy bones.
[ growling ]
Don't worry, Jake.
I'll block this one.
[ weakly ] Finn, when we wake up
in the ninth dead world,
promise me you'll
listen for this sound.
[ clapping rhythmically ]
What?
It's just that there's a
lot of dead people there.
We might get separated.
I'll be the one going...
[ clapping rhythmically ]
Hyah!
[ neighing ]
Ja-a-mes Baxter!
Hey. Holy cow.
Hey, man.
Uh, this guy really knows
how to cheer a guy up.
It's awesome.
Hey, do you know this guy?
Well...sort of.
Yeah, we know him!
Huh. What's his deal?
His name's James Baxter.
He just travels around
on his beach ball,
making people happy.
[ neighing ]
J-a-ames Baxter!
Cool.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!