[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
JAKE:
Beep! Beep! Look out.
Beep! Beep!
Pillow delivery.
Look out, buddy!
Ugh!
- BMO: Ugh!
- Come on, Jake.
Sorry, buddy.
I'm just trying
to cheer you up some.
| mean, here you are chilling
with history's coolest friends,
building an actual
pillow fort,
but you just sit there
sulking.
I'm like, "what gives?"
[ sighs ]
| guess I'm just thinking
about Flame Princess.
| told her
a joke the other day,
and she didn't even
laugh or anything.
Guess it's over between us.
That's it?
A joke?
Maybe she just didn't
get it yet.
Yeah, right, BMO.
More like she used up
all her laughs
at some other guy's
jokes, probably.
Man, having a girlfriend
is hard.
No, being crazy
You're getting all hung up --
all hung up on imaginary
problems.
You got to focus on
what's real, man.
You see this cup?
This is literally
my favorite cup.
Hunh!
Now it's gone forever,
so it's not real,
and | don't care
about it anymore.
[ gasps ] Oh, no!
My favorite window!
| don't even know what
you guys are talking about.
| think I just need
some alone time.
Gotta let my mind fester
a bit, you know?
I'll be back
in a little while.
Finn, festering's
always bad, man!
There's no good kind
of festering!
Finn!!
Man.
This looks smaller
from the outside.
What's this, now?
What the...?
Jake, what's in here?
[ grunting ]
Jake?
Ugh!
Oh, whoa.
[ birds chirping ]
Did Jake build this part, too?
That guy needs some more
girlfriends or something.
Hey, Jake?
You need more girlf--
What the...?
Door's gone?
Hmmmmmm.
Maybe there's another door
in yonder pillow town.
| don't get this at all.
Aah! Dragon! Run!
- Huh?
- Oof!
Hey, mister!
You better get running!
Blanket dragon!
[ roaring ]
Now, tAis, | understand.
Bwaah!
[ roars ]
[ screaming ]
Oh. That's it?
Wow!
[ villagers cheering ]
Hey, uh...
how's it going?
Hoy, there!
I am Quilton,
son of Pillowford.
And you have saved
our village!
You and your sharp pillow.
[ chuckles ] It's nothing.
| kill things all the time.
Oh, nonsense!
This calls
for a celepillobration!
Oh! [ laughs ]
[ up-tempo music plays,
indistinct conversations ]
[ sighs ]
There you are,
Finn the Human.
Oh. Hey... there.
Um... you can just
call me Finn, if you want.
All right, Finn.
My name is Roselinen,
daughter of Quilton.
You have to call me
the whole thing.
Oh! U-Uhh...
[ chuckling ]
Just kidding.
[ laughs nervously ]
Oh!
Uh, your dad seems fun.
[ laughing ]
Oh, my! Puhzah!
[ chuckling ]
Yeah.
Um... you want to dance?
Oh! Well...
... have a girlfriend.
[ chirps ]
[ laughs ]
Dummy, it's a dance,
not marriage.
[ laughs nervously ]
Yeah. Okay.
This place is weird.
Are you telling me that birds
in yourworld
don't poo little
pillowcases?
Nah -- just regular
poo.
Hey -- like this.
[ clears throat ]
Yeah, i-it's really cool.
Where | come from,
| live with my best friend,
who's my brother.
And... he's a dog.
[ chuckles ]
We fight stuff.
It's cool.
It's really different
than here.
Um, where I'm from,
blankets and pillows
are used for
bedding.
[ chuckles ]
Well, they're used for that
here, too.
[ laughs nervously ]
Oh.
[ giggles ]
Pillightful!
Aw, man.
It's been nice, Roselinen,
but | got to get back
to my home.
Quilton, | need your help
to find the portal to my home world.
Of course we will do our best
to help you,
Finn the Flesh Pillow,
but you're not
making a fold of sense.
Please -- share our food.
You need nourishment.
[ chomping ]
[ muffled ]
It tastes like a pillow.
I'll give your compliments
to the pillow.
[ thunder rumbles ]
Oh. There you are.
You found your mug.
| thought you said
you didn't care.
[ sips ]
That mug is empty.
| wonder
what Finn's up to.
Roar!
I'm the blanket dragon!
Well, /'m daddy!
Sha-pow!
Jay, Bonnie,
| bet your daddy
is just about finished
chopping wool.
You guys want to bring him
his lunch?
BOTH:
Yes!
[ grunting ]
[ laughing in deep voice ]
Alphanumeric!
Pillow Sheep, you have more
fluff than sense.
Mwah!
BOTH:
Daddy! Daddy!
[ laughs ]
What is this -- a pack of
fearsome pillow goblins?
[ laughing ]
Daddy! We're your kids!
Psst! Finn!
They've brought you lunch.
Oh, they have,
have they?
Tiny pillows.
Mmm!
[ chuckles ]
Darling, you've outdone
yourself.
Honk! Honk!
BOTH:
Grandpillow!
What's my father doing here?
Pbht!
Oh, Puhoy!
BOTH:
Grandpillow!
Oh! Come here!
But... I've come to speak
with your father.
What is it, Quilton?
When you first arrived here,
you told us
of a mysterious door
that led you to our world.
Yes. Of course.
Archeologists found this in
the pillow catacombs --
the Pillownomicon.
Oh, my glob.
There is no information
about the door,
save for the fact it
shows up periodically
and then disappears.
Quilton, | need to find
that door.
Uhh... hey, BMO,
I-I gotta snag my mug
from you.
Oh. Really?
Hey, don't sweat it.
I'll make us some
hot chocolate.
Jake, you drive a hard
burger.
Hello?
Ah, yes. Come in.
Are these the great
Abba-cadabra Mountains?
And are you Rasheeta,
the great Oracle,
dweller of said
mountains?
Yes. And you must be Finn,
the Human Man,
seeker of the wandering
portal.
Yes. Yes, I-I've searched
for decades.
How did you know?
| read it
in the tea leaves.
This newspaper | found
from the future.
Does it say
how | get home?
The real question is, are you
sure you wantto?
Uhh... yeah.
Well, don't worry.
You won't be here long.
[ farts ]
So, there's another way to --
Oof!
Not long now.
[ farts ]
Ooh!
[ coughs ]
[ coughing ]
Father!
What did the oracle say,
father?
Have we come to the right spot
finally?
| think so, but the oracle
spoke in riddles.
Gonna have to fester
on this one for a bit --
Oh, Finn.
| know you have to go.
All these years,
I've known.
But now that it's time...
[ sniffles ]
Oh, man.
I'm just
all messed up about it.
Just promise me
you'll remember us
when you're back
in your real life.
Hmm.
That reminds me, Roselinen, of
something Jake told me
just before | came
to this world.
[ distorted ]
You're getting all hung up
on imaginary problems.
Stay with your new wife.
You've known her longer now
than any of us.
You're not even sure /ever
really existed.
And I'm pretty sure | didn't
look like this.
Man.
How did he see it all coming
so clearly?
Come on, everyone.
Pack your things.
We're going home.
[ giggling ]
Goodness, Jake.
Why don't you do this
with your other babies?
Well, Rainicorn babies
age rapidly.
They don't need their parents
a couple hours after they're born.
That really stinks, huh?
Mm...
[ bell dings ]
Hot chocolate is ready!
ROSELINEN:
Finn? Finn!
RVECELOA!
Wha-- where?
Are you comfortable?
I'm... all right.
Um... Dad?
[ voice breaking ]
Dad, we just wanted...
to say that... we --
[ sobs ]
That... we love you, Dad.
| remember back
when /was dad.
[ sighs ]
Dad, you are Dad.
| ain't Dad yet!
Oh. No.
Wait!
Here it comes!
Oh!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo, boy!
Hup!
Hey, buddy.
You feeling better already?
Huh? Oh.
Uhh... I don't know, man.
I-I just had the number-one
wildest dream.
- Really?
- Yeah! | was --
[ telephone rings ]
Hello?
Oh. Hey.
Oh. [ chuckles ]
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
That was Flame Princess.
She said she didn't get my joke
'til just now --
and that it's really funny
and awesome.
[ laughs ]
| knew it.
Yeah, that's great, man.
Now, what about this dream?
What dream?
The dream you were just
talking about.
- Huh?
- Just a second ago.
The dream you just had
in the pillow fort!
Pbht!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D to a cliff under a tree. )
FINN:
This party is so crazy!