[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ video-game music plays ]
[ whoosh!]
ALL:
Aaah! A dragon!
[ indistinct shouting ]
[ roars ]
[ all screaming ]
I'm here just in time!
[ zoom!]
[ roars ]
È Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh... È
J ...ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh 2
[ roars ]
[ gasps ]
Whoa.
[ video-game music plays ]
Ahhhh!
[ music continues ]
[ thud! ]
[ whap!]
[ candy people cheering ]
Don't let the
dragon drag on, man.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
[ candy people cheering ]
Thanks.
Sign my rock!
[ laughs ]
Okay.
Finn!
U-uh, uh, uhh...
Have dinner with me!
Please!
Please! Please!
Please! Finn!
Sure, man. Yeah. Sure.
Sometime.
[ laughs ]
How about...
e-every night this week?!
Well...maybe one night.
[ whimpers ]
[ sniffles ]
Come on, man!
Every night!
No, man.
You get out of here.
Boom!
Hey, y'alll Don't fight!
[ both grunting ]
We should get
out of here, Finn.
| think somebody
called the heat.
BOTH:
Weee-oooh!
[ candy people grunting ]
[ shouting in distance ]
[ shouting intensifies ]
Have dinner with me!
Have dinner!
| want you to have dinner!
Finn!
Sucks.
Finn, can go outside today?
Well...I guess | could.
| just don't want to deal
with those guys right now.
Ohhhhh!
Deal with me!/
[ giggles ]
Let's play
"Cops and Robbers"!
Gimme your bank account!
Bang, bang!
[ grunts ]
[ laughs ]
Huh?
Reach for the roof!
And give me all
your goldbricks!
Uh, okay, okay.
Don't hurt me!
Don't worry, Finn.
It's only me -- BMO.
I'm wearing a disguise!
[ laughs ]
[ sighs ]
Hmm.
[ crying ]
Your beauty is destroyed!
[ sobbing ]
[ sobbing continues ]
Hotchal!
BMO, how do | look?
Like the devil!
Whoa!
[ gasps ]
Intruder!
Finn!
There's an
intruder in here!
[ laughing ]
No, it's me --it's Finn.
This is my alter-ego...
Davey Johnson.
Ohhhhhhhh.
I'll dress up like this so
nobody bothers me about
being Finn.
Do you think that'll
going to do the trick?
| dunno.
[ whirl! whirl! whirl! whirl! ]
Huh?
Is that...?
Is that Finn?!
Hello -- um...
[ deep voice ]
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
He-llo.
Uhhhhhhhhh...
[ voice auto-tuning ]
[ Davey's voice ]
Hello.
I'm Davey.
Oh.
Thought it was Finn,
on account he's wearing
Finn's exact clothes.
Oh, man.
Ha ha!
Hi. I'm Davey.
Ah, so what?
You want to have
dinner with me?
Go away, weirdo.
Ha ha.
[ coins jingle ]
[ electronic music plays ]
[ birds cooing ]
[ crunch!]
MAN:
Hey!
Come on!
You got to pay
for those, man!
I'm trying to run
a business herel!
[ coins jingle ]
| got to find a job.
[ bell jingles ]
| need a job.
Can you sweep a broom?
You betchal
[ whistle blows ]
Geez Louise!
Quitting time already?
Sure is, Davey.
Take 'er easy, boss.
Good night, Davey.
[ normal voice ]
Man, today was awesome --
Just normal, you know?
Just like a normal day.
No drama or anything of that --
just super-normal.
Man, it was great.
That's cool.
Good night, Finn.
I'm Davey.
[ chuckles ]
Yeah.
I'm Davey.
[ candy people cheering ]
[ clanking ]
Hey, Finn, you want
to have dinner
instead of breakfast today?
[ clanking continues ]
Finn?
That mustbe him.
[ cheering continues ]
| made you dinner, Finn!
Where were you?!
ALL:
Whoa!
[ clanking continues ]
[ clank ]
Uh, what's going on?
Oh, hiya, mister.
Thanks for putting
me up last night.
I'm just chopping some wood
so's | can build a little
log cabin to live in.
Huhhhhhh?!
[ grunts ]
Hey. I'm Randy.
Randy, want to
get dinner tonight?
Nah. I'm busy.
| like to wander at night.
Finn, what's going on?
You got to start calling
me "Davey," Mister --
because that's my name.
Da-a-a-a-a-vey.
Aw, no!
Have you lost your teacups, man?
Mister, | don't know
nothing about that.
I'm just a working Joe,
trying to stake
my claim
under the sun
and look out on the beautiful
green fields ...called ...life!
Uhhhhh...
RANDY: Hey, Davey,
where do you want these logs?
Oh, just attach
them to the cabin,
like how it should be --
so it looks like a cabin.
We're gonna build a right
wall and a front wall.
Uh... how about the roof?
Maybe. Maybe.
I've been holding these.
They look good.
[ sighs ]
Got to figure a way to
get Finn to act normal.
BMO:
Pyoo! Pyoo! Pyoo-pyoo!
Pyoo-pyoo-pyoo-pyoo-pyoo-pyoo!
[ groans ]
[ rocking chairs creaking ]
[ both slurp ]
Aaaaah!
Gimme the wallet!
Or feel my claw!
The wallet!
Watch out! A robber!
I'll cut you!
I mean, rob you!
Oh, no!
I'm a robber!
I'm gonna rob
this guy's life!
And there's nobody
who can stop me!
Unless...there's a
hero around here.
[ gasps ]
Like, if someone around here was
actually a heroin disguise,
they could probably stop me.
Come on, Finn! Be a hero!
What?
What are we talking about?
Butt out, Randy!
Ohhhhhhh!
Yes, Finn!
Put on your awesome
hat and beat me up!
What?
I'm not talking
to you, Randy!
| called the police.
Hmm.
Wait -- what?!
BOTH:
Weee-oooh! Weee-oooh!
Guys, it's not what
it looks like!
That guy isn't
really named Davey!
It's Finn!
He brainwashed himself
to become Davey,
and | was just trying
to inspire him
to go back to being Finn!
BOTH:
Yeah, yeah!
We've heard that before!
Come along...Robber!
R-robber.
Finn! Don't let the
dragon drag on, man!
Don't let the
dragon drag on!!
Don't let the dragon...
NELCYS
[ slurps ]
Well, that was pretty unusual,
wasn't it, Davey?
[ slurps ]
Get outta here, Randy!
Get 0-0-0-0-out!
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
No more Davey.
But you love being Davey.
| dolove being Davey,
but being Davey caused
Jake to get arrested.
But remember that time
when Davey sat in the park and
saw some people walking around?
[ sighing ]
Yeah.
That was nice.
And remember that time when
Davey swept the floors?
[ laughs ]
Yeah, that was great, too.
But...
Do you really want to go back
to being a famous hero?
Why not just be Davey --
A simple man with simple goals
and simple problems?
You can just blend in and
live the simple life.
Yeah --
blend in.
You know,
maybe I'll be Davey --
just one more time.
One more time.
Come on, man!
That last game wasn't fair!
How about who can hold
up their hand the longest?
Okay.
This game breaks the tie.
Last game.
Hey, fellas.
How's tricks?
Hmm? Oh. Hey, Davey.
[ gasps ]
Keys.
[ keys jingle ]
Hmm?
W-w-what's going on?
Oh. Uh...
[ chuckles nervously ]
Would you care for a...
body sweep?
Um...yeah. Sure.
| do feel kinda dirty.
[ straining ]
Whoo!
You sure know how
to party, Davey!
[ straining ]
Yes, yes!
Yes-yes-yes-yes-yes-yes-yes-yes!
No! No, no! No!
[ keys jingle, lock opens ]
[ clank! ]
Davey?!
No, it's me -- Finn!
Finn!
Here's your mail, criminal.
We feed our criminals.
[ clank! ]
Hey! Stop!
Whoop-whoop!
Whoop-whoop! Whoo!
[ both panting ]
Goodbye, Davey.
Goodbye, Finn.
BOTH:
Weee-oooh! Weee-oooh!
Weee-oooh!
[ groans ]
Hey! There they go!
Yeah, there goes Davey
and the criminal!
Awww!
Huh. Hey, Finn.
Hey, Finn.
BOTH:
Weee-oooh! Weee-oooh!
Good luck catching
those guys!
Thanks!
Glad to have
you back, buddy.
Word.
[ farts ]
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!