[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ laughs ]
Okay, now make
him look angrier.
FINN:
All right, give me a second...
JAKE:
Nope. Not funny anymore.
Sorry, dude.
You ruined it.
Man, | don't have the patience
for this animation junk.
Whoever does this must
have no life whatsoev--
Oofl
Why did | do that?
[ glass shatters |
BOTH:
Huh?
Yo, Finn,
did you order a brick?
Mm, | don't think so.
JAKE:
False alarm.
It's just an e-mail.
FINN:
Who's it from?
Looks like Ice King's
handwriting.
[ gasps ]
[ gagging ]
FINN:
Ugh!
JAKE:
Ohh!
Escape, Jake!
Escape!
All right,
all right, hold on.
| think | can...
[ cooling fan whirring ]
Aw, man.
Thing must've had
a computer worm in it.
Whaaaa?
[ both scream ]
Hi, Princess!
What now, Ice King?
Remember that time last summer
when you said you'd only
go out on a date with me if |
was the last guy on Ooo?
| doubt | said that.
[ both panting ]
BOTH:
P-Bubs! P-Bubs! P-Bubs!
[ both breathing heavily ]
- The computer went...
- Open video and...
- the e-mail...
- potato trampoline...
brick window with
the plastic...
banana hummingbird...
47 grapes...
Ahem.
Anyone having any
[ robotic | computer problems?
[ canned laughter ]
How do we stop that
computer worm,
you pile of goo!
[ laughing ]
My worm exists beyond
your comprehension,
within the
universal source code.
Stop talkin' like a nerd
and give it to us straight!
Once the glitch
does its work,
the whole world will be deleted,
except for me
and my Bubblygums.
[ smooching sounds ]
Mwah!
Mwah, mwah!
Mwah! Mwah!
Mwah!
Oow!
[ stammers ]
Well, see you all.
I'm gonna prepare for my...
date.
Whee-ha-haw!
[ ting! ]
Aaah!
My beautiful face!
My hopes
and dreams ruined!
[ distorted scream ]
Don't worry,
Princess.
We'll take
care of this thing.
Oh, me, too.
I'm gonna take
care of it, too.
Okay!
[ candy people screaming ]
Don't worry, guy!
| got you!
Yee-aah!
Jake, help me!
Okay, shh.
You're safe.
Come here, guy.
No, get away from me!
I'm trying to
help you, yo!
| saw what happened
when you picked up Todd.
But...
Nnooooo!
Jake, this isn't working!
We need a plan.
[ snoring ]
[ snoring continues |
Oh, man!
Okay,
here's my dream plan.
You were wearing tights
made of green feathers --
these finy green feathers.
And | was this wise-cracking
coelacanth that
only ate popcorn.
Anyway, we were in this --
That plan's not good!
Hold on.
I'm almost done.
So, we were trapped inside this
huge egg, and after a while,
you started dancing in
this kind of sign language.
And then
Ice King's glitchy
stuff started
eating my dream up.
| peed my pants, but
you went up and talked to it.
You just...talked to it.
Then talk to it | will!
[ grunts ]
Hey, man, tell me the haps.
Yeah, tell us your feelings.
Get deep.
"Sllabfoog uoy pleh t'hac i."
CANDY PERSON:
Oh, sweet Lord, my face!
"Slaw frog yokel snacky."
"Snacky slaw frog yokel."
"Sea salt yack let a snacky."
Yeah, that sounds good.
Jake, | think |
found a way in!
No, wait, dude!
| think | cracked the code!
There's no time!
CANDY PERSON:
Aaaah!
[ distorted screaming ]
[ distorted trilling ]
[ gasps ]
This must be the
universal source code.
Huh?
Ice King and Bubblegum?
Hmm.
[ snake hissing ]
[ distorted screech ]
FINN:
Jake, don't touch anything!
Huh?
| think these shiny things
are the building blocks
of the universe, man.
They store every single thing
that's a thing back on thing.
Okay, enough
explorin' already.
Where's this glitch guy?
I'm gonna smash his jimmies!
Jake, what is it?
Huh?
[ screeches ]
Unh!
[ knock on door ]
ICE KING:
Oh, Princess Bubblegum!
Guess who!
Can you guess? Can you?
I'll give you three chances.
No.
Okay, four chances.
[ rim shot ]
Ice King,
give me the antivirus,
or I'll shoot you with my
candy horse tranquilizer.
But, Sugar,
look what | brought you --
a box of chocos.
Ugh!
Mmm!
Still good.
Ugh!
Look, | can't prove it, but --
you made a promise that I'd
have at least one date if --
[ slowly ]
If | was the last person on O000000...
[ tranquilizer pistol fires ]
[ sighs ]
Okay.
Well, even if | did promise,
you're notthe last person on
Ooo because /'m still here.
[ smooching ]
Uh...
Ooh. Hey, | have a hand,
too, you know.
If | can lend you one...
Check out my cool hand!
Ugh! That's disgusting.
[ grumbles ]
Come on, Jake.
Pull it together, man.
NELCYS
Oh, no! My arm!
We had so many great
times together.
5 Doo bee doo bee doo bee doo È
5 Skibble dee skibble dee È
2 Bibbity boppty doo )
Huh? Who was that?
Aww!
[ laughing ]
Whoo!
Let's do this --
For righty!
That's the spirit!
Adventure ti--
Oh, my gams.
Hold up, dude!
My body's changing!
[ smooching ]
[ sighs ]
No.
Oh, come on, woman!
I'm trying to be nice!
Can't you at least make
the best out of this?
Whoa-ho-ho!
Are you praying to me?
I'm into this.
Whoa!
I'm still into this.
Ohh!
Still into it. Aah!
Give me the antivirus!
ICE KING:
| can't, monkey peeps.
| didn't make one.
The glitch will delete
everything until we're
all that's left.
You mean forever?
ICE KING:
Well, yeah.
| mean, you say that
like it's a bad thing.
Oh, come on,
Finn and Jake.
So, hey, Finn, how you
plan on taking this guy out?
[ muffled speaking ]
Okay.
| guess it's worth a try.
[ groaning ]
Aah!
What do we do now?!
We got to get those
things out of his stomach.
[ gasps ]
Hey, Finn!
Remember that gross
video Ice King sent?
Ugh! Yeah.
Yeah!
Let's double-team
these locks!
[ both gulping, gagging ]
[ distorted screeching ]
Hey!
[ all groaning ]
BOTH:
We did it!
[ coughing, gagging, spitting ]
You should
wash your hair.
You should wash
your mouth.
Huh?! No way!
Impossible!
[ grunting ]
Uh...
Everything back
to normal, huh?
Seems like it.
Aah! My face!
My beautiful face is back
to norma-a-a-a-a-a-l!
Aaaaaaah!
Hey,
you seen the Princess?
Yeah, she's in the
Ice King's castle!
Aaaaah!
Useless [ grunts ]
computer!
[ grunts ]
You sassafrassin
hammaslammin
[ grunts ]
wammajammin...!
[ grunting ]
Aah-yaa-yaa-yaa-yaaaaaaaah!
Finn and Jake!
My heroes!
Yeah, no big deal.
Sheesh!
| missed you.
| missed you, too.
[ smooching ]
Whoa.
You taste different, baby.
You been playing basketball in
someone else's hockey rink?
[ clears throat ]
Hey, Bubs,
where's Ice King?
| want to kick
his boingloings.
Yeah, where is he?
| want to kick
his boingloings, too!
Uh...guys?
Hello?
Princess?
Let's forget all about this.
Oh, get of me, you creep!
Ow ow ow ow ow
OW OW OW OW OW OW
OW OW OW OW OW
Oow ow ow ow ow!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
> Toacliff ... >
This party is so crazy!