[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
> [ eerie music plays ] È
ALL: [ chanting ]
Birthday! Birthday!
Birthday!
Birthday! Birthday! Birthday!
Birthday! Birthday!
Birthday!
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Nice job,
Mr. Birthday Boy!
Thanks.
Man, you are
like another year older,
but you look good --
like, super good.
Yup. Mom and Dad passed
down some pretty good genes.
Oh, yeah, Mom and Dad.
Hey, did Mom and Dad tell you
any stories
about when
you were born?
Yay!
Birthday story time, please.
[ chuckles ]
Well...
it was a day like
any other day...
[ creak! sloop! ]
There, there, baby.
You're going to be a fighter,
just like your mother.
[ whoosh! plong-g-g-g! ]
Yes!
Barrel roll.
Ugh!
Guh.
[ whoosh!]
- Steak break.
- Let's get started.
These steaks are tough
and stringy... like you.
[ laughing ]
Oh, good one, dear.
Hey, after dinner,
what do you say
we check the ticker-type
for new cases?
Margaret, you're
in a family way now.
You should take a backseat
from investigations.
Oh, come on, Joshua.
Even with this ankle-biter,
I'm as quick as ever.
Sure, my waist is bigger,
but that just means
more bullets
in my ammo belt.
You're missing the point, sugar.
What if something bad happens?
Let's say we're out on the beat,
fighting some lowlife.
He throws a punch -- you zig
when you should have zagged,
and -- oops! -- junior
takes a knock to the noodle,
comes out with a shiner
the size of a grapefruit.
| can't take that kind of guilt,
and neither can you.
| can take care of myself
just fine.
And besides, these babies
don't come cheap.
We need to work together
as a team
to bring in the bread.
Yeah, you got me there.
Now let's get over to that
ticker-type
and look for some
perps.
You relax, dear.
| got it.
[ whoosh!]
Hmm.
Let's get a look here.
"Vampire girl spotted
in the grasslands
harassing sheep and cattle.Ó
Nope, nope, nope.
"Small fire goblin burns down
Candy Kingdom forest."
Hey, that sounds fun.
Let's do that.
Wait. Wait.
Here's one --
"Woman's pies go missing
in bucolic countryside,
where nothing ever happens" --
The perfect case
for my pregnant wife!
What?
Now let's get an egg
in our shoe and beat it.
È Oh-oh È
[ brakes squeal ]
[ door creaks ]
- Yes? Hello?
- Afternoon, Mrs. Tree trunks.
We're Joshua and Margaret
of Joshua and Margaret
investigations.
And this is our boy.
We're responding to a wire
about missing pies.
Oh, yes.
A -- a -- a monster's been
stealing my pies
off of the windowsill.
A monster, eh?
Oh, yes.
You can see the monster tracks
leading off into the forest.
Well, those tracks
are as phony as a $3 bill.
The monster tracks
are very real.
My husband told me so.
- [ grunting ]
Ohh!
Wyatt!
Aw! Aw, geez, you got me.
What's the big idea, Wyatt?
Why'd you burgle
your wife's pie?
Because it's amazing!
Ohh, | can't get enough of it.
You could just ask
for seconds.
But | want thirds
and fourths!
| want to stop
when /want to stop!
Oh, Wyatt.
[ crying ]
Oh, it's the only good part
of my day.
[ sobbing ]
Well, there you have it --
the only monster here
was this man's appetite
for his wife's pie.
Oh, no.
But the monster /s real.
He snuck up and rubbed my elbow
while | was gardening.
And Leftenant Candy Corn said it
came in through the window
and touched him on the chest.
Oh! Oh, now | got myself
all scared.
W-Won't you check around
to make sure
no one is out there?
Of course. Probably nothing
more than a peeper.
Ha! These country yokels are
all just superstitious.
| bet you that old elephant
sees a monster a day.
Joshua, look --
something way larger
than Wyatt made them.
These tracks look real.
Hot cram!
A peeping monster!
Oh, this town would surely
put up a collection
to nab this guy.
Ohh, too bad you're preggo.
We gotta pass.
Come on, Joshua!
What?
- Ha ha!
- Margaret!
Margaret! Wait for pappy!
[ hoots ]
Hmm. The tracks end here.
[ rustling ]
[ growls ]
[ meows ]
[ purring ]
Hey, hey!
Beat it, uggos!
[ yowls, hisses ]
[ rustling ]
The peeper!
[ panting ]
MARGARET:
I'll show that peepsie the pepper!
[ creak! ]
[ grunting ]
Joshua dear, I'm stuck.
[ growling ]
Joshua, the beast
outflanked us!
[ screeches ]
- Gads!
- [ screeches ]
Boom!
[ grunting ]
Do your worst, you masher.
Joshual
[ grunts ]
Ooh!
[ sniffing ]
[ whmmmp! ]
[ gasps ]
[ shing! ]
Drop that daddy!
[ warbles ]
[ groans ]
Babycakes!
Oh, this is all my fault!
Uh, yeah, pretty much.
[ groans ]
[ smacking lips ]
Mmm. Mmm.
Ahh, good last meal.
Okay. Well, | got bit
by a monster,
a creature of the night.
We both know what comes
next for me.
[ shing! ]
Just make it snappy, darling.
Don't.
[ sniffles ]
Don't be melodramatic,
Joshua.
I've been doing some
research.
Listen here -- | think
if we can get
a sample of that creature's
venom,
we can use it
to synthesize an antidote.
[ thud!]
Joshua?!
Oh! Puddin' pie!
Ugh.
I'm fine.
Just got to pop out
and fetch that venom.
You're about as fine
as a canary in a cat mine!
[ clicks ]
[ zwip! ]
[ creak!]
Oof!
Hey, where's the fire,
kiddo?
You stay put.
[ mumbling ]
So's | can keep tabs on you.
Feel better.
Over.
[ smooches ]
[ mumbling ]
[ chuckles ]
[ brakes squeal ]
2 [ suspenseful music plays ] È
[ insects chirping ]
[ static crackles ]
Come in, Margaret.
Do you read me? Over.
[ static crackles ]
I've got the peep peep's
trail.
In pursuit.
[ static crackles ]
You have to say, "over,"Ó or
! think you're still talking.
Over.
Joshua, I've stumbled upon
the beast's lair.
Just hang on, honey bunny.
Over.
[ growling ]
[ screams, howls ]
[ whoosh!]
[ gasps ]
[ warble! ]
Bleh!
Stay right there.
[ zwip! ]
What?!
[ whoosh! whoosh! ]
[ sloop!]
[ meows ]
[ hoots ]
Ohh!
[ grunting ]
[ creak! ]
Ooh! Not yet.
[ grunting ]
[ whooshing ]
[ roars ]
Come on, come on!
Hey!
[ rumbling ]
Hup!
[ groans ]
[ cooing ]
What?
What's your angle, slick?
You poison my hubby,
then play the innocent?
And what's with all this
baby paraphernalia?
Wait a tick.
Are you a baby?
Uh-huh.
Oh, no! | must've
scared the dickens out of you!
[ imitating baby cooing ]
There, there, baby.
I'm so sorry...
[ sparkling ]
...for this!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[ creak! zwip! ]
[ chuckles evilly ]
[ pulsing ]
[ zwip! zwip! ]
[ siren wailing in distance ]
Joshua, | got the venom!
Ohhhhhh!
[ creak!]
Uh-oh, this baby business is
getting serious!
[ breathing sharply ]
Ohh, ohh.
2 [ suspenseful music plays ] È
Joshual
Ohh! Ohh!
Ohhhhh!
[ breathing sharply ]
[ groans ]
Margaret, stay away.
Something's about to happen!
Something's about to happen
with me, too!
SA-EEE ]
- Ohhh!
Margaret!
Aaaah!
Ohhhhh!
[ splat!]
[ glass shatters |
JOSHUA:
Shine the light, dear.
Yowzers!
> Hello, daddy!
Hello, mommy
D It's so nice to be here
with you now J
[ snoring ]
Ohhhh!
Boy, Jake left a scar on my head
the size of a nickel.
I'll have to wear a hat now,
Margaret.
Well, | think you'll look
good in one.
MARGARET: Are you sure having
him next to Jermaine is safe?
We don't even know what he is.
[ smacks lips ]
Of course we do, dear --
he's our boy.
That he is.
Yes, we've got one boy
that | gave birth to,
and one boy
you gave birth to.
Let's never tell him
how it happened.
Agreed.
And so they never told me.
Never told you what?
| don't know.
They never told me. Ha!
È Come along with me È
And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!