[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Hello-lable!
Cuber?
Blable brother?
Where are you?
Oh, this cave air is doing
wonders for my physiological
bable, bable,
bable, bable, bable.
Oh! Aah!
Oh!
But I'm a baby!
Tuber?
Sister Tuber?
Bable, bable, bable.
[ creature growling ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ creature roars ]
Aah!
Hmm? Aah!
Oh, you surprised your old pal,
Cuber, aboard his spaceship.
Oh, this old Grayble?
It's just
sentimental blabling.
You know, the present can be far
more interesting than the past.
Let's see.
Oh!'lt's a
space wedding!
Let's go in for
a closer look.
Easy.
[ shouting in alien language ]
[ alarm blaring ]
Wable.
Bable, bable.
Bable, bable, bable.
Oh! Survival!
Remember your training.
[ whimpers ]
Trust your Graybles.
Oh, and you
children at home,
don't bother trying to
guess tonight's theme.
Applesauce to a theme!
Your friend Cuber
doesn't want to die!
[ wind whistling ]
Oh, come on.
[ whistling continues ]
It's Finn.
Hey, Finn!
I'm a Weather Vane!
I'm a cliff diver!
What?!
[ air rushing ]
Ohh!
BMO, you got to let
me dig this hole.
It's important.
A hole, you say?
Yeah.
We beat this
evil wizard, see,
and we stole
his giant wand.
Don't listen
to him, BMO.
/beat the Wizard, so I'm
making Finn dig the hole,
even though | could do
it in like two seconds.
Heh, heh, heh.
Rude!
This wand is crazy
powerful, right?
It's a Thought Cannon.
It makes anything that
you think of turn real.
Up, please.
So it's too strong, so
we're burying it for safety.
JAKE:
I'll tell you what I'd do.
I'd use that Cannon
and imagine a hole.
Jake, remember what they say
about absolutely power.
I'm tired of
your wisdom, BMO!
Now watch and learn!
Yeah, okay, my name's Jake,
and I'm gonna take this magic
Thought Cannon,
and I'm gonna think,
"l want a hole to bury
this Thought Cannon in,"
and bobble, bobble, Jake gets a hole in
which a Thought Cannon may be buried!
What if for a split second
you think of something else?
Nope,
my brain's my hands!
[ Thought Cannon warbling ]
[ sizzling ]
Whoops!
Looks like | was thinking
about a sandwich.
[ muffled ]
Enjoy your labor!
Heh, heh, heh.
[ sighs ]
| used to
wish | was you.
Now | just wish you
would dig faster.
[ dirt scraping ]
[ grunts ]
[ grunting ]
What's this, friends?
Could it be the aformabled
Thought Cannon?
"Bobble, bobble"
as the dead might say.
That's the
power of Graybles.
[ speaking alien language ]
[ gasps ]
[ sighs ]
| guess here
goes bable.
[ Thought Cannon warbling ]
[ electronic whirring ]
[ laughs ]
You try notto
think of a sandwich,
and look what happens!
A sandwich!
[ air rushing ]
Oow!
Mama's milk!
Oh, my mama's milk!
Oh, that milk!
Graybles!
[ snoring ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ high-pitched voice ]
"I will marry you, Ice King.
[ will marry you,
lce King.
/will marry you --
[ crash ]
[ yawns ]
[ smacks lips ]
Good morning, madness.
What?!
Broken leg again!
[ sighs ]
And...
Hup! Hello!
How are you?!
Oh!
Gunther, did you
see how this happened?
| love you, Gunther, but
I'm on to your business.
Hmm,
just like that, huh?
And...
hup!
[ gurgles ]
You can do it, Cuber.
[ gasps ]
[ inhales sharply ]
[ whimpers ]
[ electronic whirring ]
You can do it, Cuber.
You can run away.
Friend or foe,
| doble know.
Now what?
Maybe Grayble.
[ clicks ]
| see that Mr. Cupcake is at
Madam Ecclair's apartment again.
His massage business
is really taking off.
Hmm.
[ clicking ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Starchy?
Yes, sir.
Starchy is just
going for a walk.
[ breathing heavily ]
Ooh! A grass lard!
Oh, look, wildflowers!
Psst, psst!
Hey!
[ gurgles ]
[ clicks ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ beeping ]
Well, I'm just gonna
pick these flowers now.
[ grunts ]
[ moaning ]
No holes.
[ beeping continues ]
Yeah, in the ear.
Oh, | mean,
in the rear.
That's what all the
walking's good for --
gives me self-esteem
to have a nice rear.
[ beeping continues ]
Aah! Oh!
No! Agh!
Mercy from the wet eyes!
[ grunting ]
Whoal! [ whimpers ]
[ roaring ]
Unh!
[ moans ]
Starchy?!
Did Starchy just die?
[ breathing heavily ]
Hey, hey!
Things looking up.
[ coughs ]
Mm.
[ breathing heavily ]
[ beeping ]
[ rumbling ]
Thank you.
[ grunts, sighs ]
[ beeping continues ]
S.0.S. -
Save Our Skin.
[ pounding ]
[ speaking in alien language ]
[ gasps ]
[ pounding ]
Aah!
Welcome home, Starchy.
Never mind!
[ breathing heavily ]
[ beeping ]
[ gasps, shouts |
[ grunts ]
[ electronic whirring ]
[ gasps ]
Oh, what time is it?
Oh! Grayble!
[ speaking native language ]
Well, one Grayble left.
[ creature growling ]
[ creature roars ]
Aah!
[ gasps ]
Tuber!
Self-actualization,
Lable brother.
[ creature whimpering ]
You can be a hero, Cuber,
and what a cube can be must be.
[ speaking in alien language ]
I'm a hero!
Cuber first!
[ roars ]
[ engine revving ]
[ electronic whirring ]
[ creature cackling ]
Now, wasn't
that a thing!
We've had
laffs and gaffs,
thribbles and chibbles,
some close calls,
secrets and questions,
and memories to share.
We barely made it
out with our scaybles...
all thanks to Graybles.
Sister Tuber?
I'm sorry for this mess.
| love you.
Psh!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!