[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ humming ]
[ buzzing ]
S Bzz, bzz, bzz,
bzz, bzz, bzz È
5 The waffle doll shall fall,
lest you eat the yellow dough >
> Bzzzz S
[ humming ]
Hmm.
I'--1'N
finish this later.
[ yawns ]
I'm so tired.
But also...hungry.
Maybe | should...eat some --
[ snoring ]
[ moaning ]
[ groans ]
Huh?
Uh...
Huh.
Hmm.
Everything's made of...me.
Pretty neat.
| bet there's like --
like a cool city
or something around here.
Nicel
Jake Cit-tay.
Hil
Oh. Uh, hi.
Jake!
Huh?
How you doing, Jake?
Uh, good, man. Good.
Man, this place is awesome!
Ooh!
Cool dolls.
They look like the rare,
antique kind.
Maybe my kids
will like them.
Hmm.
Wonder what my kids are
gonna have for dinner.
Maybe pizza?
[ rumbling ]
W-whoa! Whoal!
[ rumbling fades, stops ]
Some kind of Jake-quake.
Eh?
Is that Jake?
Hey, there...um...
Come on, man!
It's Goosel
Your best friend -- Goosel!
Oh! Uh...of course.
Goose!
Oh, Jake, Jake, Jake,
Jake, Jake, ya big goof.
How long's it been --
Two, three years?
Let's see --
uh, one, two, uh...
I've never been here.
[ laughs ]
"I've never been here."
You still got it, Jake.
[ laughs nervously ]
Come on.
Let's get you home.
Everybody's waiting
for you at the party.
Uh, party?
No -- par-taaaaay!
[ upbeat music plays,
people cheering ]
Jake's here! Jake!
[ dance music plays ]
[ laughs ]
Do it again, Goose!
[ grunting, slapping ]
[ laughs ]
GOOSE:
Hey, Jake?
Hey, what?
Now that you're back,
how about that
5 bucks you still owe me?
Uh, what 5 bucks?
Cheeseburger cheesecake
ring a bell?
[ rumbling ]
What --
[ partygoers murmuring ]
What /s that?
Oh -- oh, that.
Don't worry about that.
Do not.
[ thinking ]
Guess | better not worry about it.
Hmm.
I'm hungies, Goose.
| think there's a
leftover nacho basket
or something
in the fridge.
[ rumbling ]
Just a sec.
Cold-cut-and-nacho
sandwiches!
[ rumbling ]
Al right!
[ slurping ]
Ahhhhh.
Oow!
Something's wrong, Goose.
Jakey can't eat
any of these nachos.
[ rumbling ]
But Jakey need nachos!
Aaaaah!
[ knock on door ]
[ British accent ]
Mr. Jake!
Mr. Jake, the Mayor
wants to see you straightaway.
Al right, lad.
Show me the way.
[inhales ]
[ panting ]
Jake!
Hey, | got a for-real
important question.
Do you like cereal
in your cake?
NELCYS
Hmm.
Mm-nn-mm.
[ panting ]
Mr. Mayor?
Urchin.
Thank you
for your help.
Help yourself to
the herring cakes.
Righto!
Hello, Jake.
Thanks for making it.
Heh. Okay.
Now, look,
we're at orange alert here.
Below us are gathered
the city's top minds.
Hmm.
And they've noticed that our
seismographic troubles have
increased exponentially
since your arrival.
Mayor, uh, I-I want
to meet these minds.
Here are some of the minds.
Jake, we want to perform some
tests on you to discover the
cause of the quakes.
There's no need.
| got it figured out.
The tremors are happening
because Jake is hungry,
and his stomach
is growling,
and the hungrier
he gets,
the worse the
quakes will become!
[ laughter ]
JAKE:
I'll prove it!
TOGETHER:
Huh?
Mention a food item.
Omelet!
[ rumbling ]
Whoa! Whoal!
Whoa!
What's in the omelet?
[ rumbling ]
Chili!
It's a four-egg
chili omelet!
[ rumbling ]
[ minds murmuring ]
TOGETHER:
Aaaaaah!
Watch out!
Analysis, Tim.
It's too early to say.
This evidence is anecdotal.
Look, just let me stretch
outside to get something to eat,
and the quakes will stop.
That doesn't
sound very sciency.
No, but you have my
permission to
test your idea.
| don't like that idea!
Huh?
If Jake leaves,
that would mean the utter
destruction of our world.
| believe that Jake is an
extra-dimensional being --
a "Glob, "
if you will --
whose psychic field
holds our world together.
If he leaves, his flesh
will reconfigure,
and everything and everyone here
will disappear completely!
Oh, Dr. Erik Addamkimson,
you're just a fringe scientist,
well known to have a
crackpot of crazy theories.
Hmph.
Perhaps | am,
and maybe | am wrong.
But are you really willing to
take that chance?
We should imprison
Jake immediately!
What?! No way!
The world's not gonna end just
because | go get a bagel.
[ rumbling ]
Seize him!
Uhh...peace!
Raah!
Aaah!
[ grunting ]
Why?!
Finish him!
N EEEEEEEE]
Oh!
[ whimpers ]
Bagel...
[ rumbling ]
[ crowd gasps ]
This feels weird!
Don't worry, everybody.
| will journey to
Jake's Glob world,
which legend would have us
believe lies beyond the
great sky hole,
and bring back the food
of the Globs to appease
Jake's appetite,
thus saving everybody.
[ crowd cheers ]
Wait! Wait!!
| want to go with you, son.
I'm sorry, dad.
You -- you can't.
It's -- it's too dangerous.
Y-your mind is unprepared.
[ crying ]
My son...
[ sobs ]
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
Huh?
Yeah!
There it is --
the sky hole!
Phew!
[ projector whirring ]
Oh, my stars.
It's just as | envisioned.
O mighty Jake globs,
| beseech your aid!
Do you have bagels?
Hello?
Hmm.
Maybe those aren't
the true globs.
Yeah, they're --
they're too ugly to be --
[ slurping ]
[ gasps ]
N-0-0-0-0-0!
[ sobbing ]
| thought you'd be beautiful,
but you're not.
[ sobbing ]
You're hideous! Hideous!!
[ slurping ]
BMO, resume.
Spaghetti...
[ rumbling ]
[ all screaming ]
Don't.
[ slapping ]
BOTH:
Huh?
[ both laughing ]
Hey, you're hilario--
Ohh!
Ugh!
[ sighs ]
[ grunts ]
Huh?
Goose?!
Go.
But -- but what if
Erik Addamkimson is right?
What if you and all
the Jake peeps disappear
and | can't bring you back?
Then you won't have to
pay me back that 5 bucks.
But --
Ugh! Ugh!
Go eat, Jake!
[ inhales deeply ]
Huh?
What is that?
[ all screaming ]
N EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE]
Uh...Jake?
What's going on, man?
Feeling okay?
Just getting a snack, Goose.
Just getting a snack.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!