[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ bones crack ]
Hey, man.
Oh, hey, Finn!
[ chuckles ]
So you got my map?
- Ha, yeah.
- [ chuckles ]
So, how's your
experiment going?
Ah, it's going great.
| really feel like | fitin...
[ chuckles ]
...80 to speak.
[ laughing ]
So...are you ready
to come home?
Nah, | think I'm just gonna keep
being a brick for a while.
Mmmmm...
what are you doing again?
Finn, ever since | was little,
| wanted to see what
it's like to be a brick
in a brick shack
when the brick shack falls down.
And this shack
is gonna fall down.
Just look at it.
Like sand castles in the sun,
baby.
[ laughs ]
You're too young.
You wouldn't understand.
[ chuckles ]
You're right.
| don't understand.
But I'm cool with your mystical
journey or whatever.
I'm gonna leave
this walkie-talkie
so we can stay in touch,
justin case.
What?! No, man,
bricks don't stay in touch!
Dude, Beemo is, like,
really worried about you.
Aww... you tell that little
goofball | said hi.
[ will.
Welp, | guess
| should head back.
Oh... really?
So soon?
Yeah, well, it took me
like half the day to get here.
Besides, you're just
a brick, right?
[ chuckles ]
Yeah.
All right, see ya,
Jake!
Bye!
Okay, back to being a brick.
I'm so bored.
Pb-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-ht!
Ooh, I'm starting to get
a little tippy in my teacups.
[ leaves rustling ]
A bunny!
Looks like our long-eared friend
is onto something.
Bunnies love to dig.
He's making a supreme effort,
and | think | can guess why.
That's right -- a carrot growing
out here free and wild.
Probably the result
of a stray seed
pooped out
by a passing bird.
[ leaves rustling ]
But what's this?
A mysterious rustling
in the bush.
Could mean trouble.
Mr. Bunny seems to think so.
His sensitive whiskers quiver
at the hint
of imminent danger.
Unfortunately for Mr. Bunny,
this is what nature
is all about.
[ rustling continues ]
It's a male deer.
Not a threat to Mr. Bunny,
in the predatory sense,
but still above him
in the food chain.
Mr. Bunny, wishing to avoid
an encounter,
hops away to safety.
Wow. Deers are jerks.
Hey, man, you know | can hear
everything you say, right?
What?! Ohh!
[ grumbles ]
No! | had no idea!
Yeah, but you saw me
leave the walkie-talkie.
And | left it on.
You know that, right?
- Hi, Jake!
- Hi, Beemo.
You need anything?
A soda?
No.
So, what's Mr. Bunny
doin' now?
It's not about the bunny!
The bunny is incidental
to the brick experiment!
- Oh. Sorry, man.
- Forget about the bunny.
- Sorry, man.
- Sorry, Jake.
Look, we'll, uh --
we'll leave you alone.
[ static ]
Finn, are
you still there?
Finn?
Beemo?
JAKE:
Mr. Bunny retreats to his warren,
its homemade comforts
some consolation
to help pass
the hungry night.
Twilight falls
on the peaceful forest,
a twilight unaware
of the struggles
it both soothes
and conceals.
The crickets begin to stir,
rehearsing their musical
rhapsodies.
[ crickets chirping ]
In the distance,
flashes of heat lightning
illuminate a purple
summer sky.
Even angry deer, at last,
must come to rest.
And so it is
with our erstwhile antagonist,
who has disappeared
into a stand of trees,
perhaps to dream of tomorrow's
pointless battles.
[ yawns ]
[ thunder crashes ]
Oh, my glob!
It's a crazy storm!
This might be it!
This weather might knock
the whole thing down!
[ laughing ]
If a definition
of bravery exists,
this must be it --
a lone bunny, facing off
against the elements...
ineffectually pushing around
some twigs
with his pink bunny nose --
a symbolic gesture, perhaps,
but sometimes
that's all we have.
The wind is beginning
fo pick up,
and it's becoming clear
that mother nature has not
Just knocked on the door.
She has come in, sat down,
and poured herself a drink.
Mr. Bunny has no friends,
no family,
no loved ones of
any kind.
The wind is really
picking up now...
...small puddles gathering
around the entrance
to Mr. Bunny's cozy home...
beginning to grow in size
and connect with one another.
It won't be long now.
But what's this?
Looks like this unflagging
little hero of a bunny
will have some help, though.
A family of friendly beavers
appears to have
taken up the cause.
Often called
"nature's architects,Ó
these intrepid mammals are
sparing no effort
to shore up
the endangered burrow.
[ tail patting ]
Here's an unusual sight.
It's a sea lard!
You'd expect to see a few mudscamps
out in weather like this,
but here we have
a rare treat, indeed.
This little beauty is pretty far
outside of her natural habitat
But I've heard it said
by wise old salts
schooled in ancient
maritime lore
that a storm wifl sometimes
blow them off course
fo a remarkable degree.
Looks like we've got some
pretty good evidence fonight.
Yes, sir, sometimes
those old sailors
know what they're
talking about.
/tÕs the triumph
of experience
versus the secondhand
verities
of musty academic tomes.
This feisty sea lard is
pitching right in
to save the rabbit hole,
belying its slothful
reputation.
She uses her prodigious,
swiveling behind
fo increase
the size of the hole
while the beavers continue
fo reinforce the sides
with straw and stick.
At times like these,
the supposed cruelty
and indifference
of the natural world --
all too often its most
salient feature --
pale before
the nobler instincts
of even our most humble kin.
[ patting continues ]
In the morning light,
few signs remain
of the summer storm that
battered this idyllic glen.
The beavers are finished
with their work
and are heading home.
The sea lard looks like
she's gonna
wander the woods
for a while.
Maybe she'll find her way back
to the ocean
and write a novel
about her experiences.
Mr. Bunny is exhausted,
but can rest easy
knowing that his home
is secure.
[ leaves rustling ]
But, alas, the bunny's rest
is short-lived.
The deer is back.
The deer, perhaps confused
by the antler-like appearance
of Mr. Bunny's
protective dam,
is now testing the situation.
Mr. Bunny is unsure
of where this is going.
And with a single smash
from the deer's powerful
front hooves,
the bunny's home is
under attack!
Mr. Bunny has hopped to safety
and can only watch
as the deer continues
its relentless rampage
on the only home he knows.
A couple of more
mighty smashes, and the dam --
[ water rushing]
The dam has been breached!
Water is now flooding in!
The deer continues its attack!
This deer's misplaced rage,
combined with its size
and weight,
/s more than enough to
bring down the weakened walls,
which are now
starting to give,
aided by the unforgiving
weight from the free above.
[ wood creaking |
Even Mr. Deer,
in his blind fury,
seems fo sense
what's about fo happen,
as he steps to one side.
[ wood crashing |
/t's over.
The warren has been
destroyed...
an injustice
of astronomical levels.
Words fail me.
[ footsteps approaching ]
Actually, he doesn't
seem that upset.
He's on his feet, checking out
his new surroundings.
Even the deer is impressed.
As if confused by the events,
he performs a comical
double-take
and retreats into the forest.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this bunny is indomitable!
[ all cheering ]
[ whistles ]
[ laughs ]
Yay!
[laughing |
This bunny has
the right attitude.
Who cares about being
a brick in a wall
of a falling-down shack?
There's something bigger
than that,
and the bunny has answers!
Teach me, Mr. B!
Uh! Aww...
FINN:
Jake? Jake?
You there, buddy? Over.
- Hey, Finn.
Hey, man.
You ready to come home?
That sounds good.
Awesome. See you soon.
[ walkie-talkie shuts off ]
Yessss!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!