[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ humming ]
[ grunts ]
Oh!
Parm, parm, parm.
Asiago's like parm.
[ humming ]
Whoopsies.
[ blows ]
[ chuckles ]
Okay,
now easy does it.
[ splash ]
Ohh!
[ glass shatters |
[ growls ]
Thanks a lot, dad!
Finn?
What's going on?
Is the spaghetti
all -- whoal!
Finn, what happened?!
| messed up the spaghetti,
and then | got mad,
and PB's candy arm exploded.
[ scoffs ]
Man, | knew that
arm was bogus.
Yeah, it wasn't
the greatest.
Sorry about
the spaghetti, though.
Man, don't
worry about that.
You just went through some
outrageous beeswax with losing
your favorite
arm and et cetera.
You can't expect to just
bounce right back to normal.
| can't?
Nah, man. Listen.
All these princesses donating
all these gross fake arms --
they mean well, but they're
throwing you off your game.
You got to go
at your own pace.
If you listen deep
in your melon heart...
[ heart beating ]
...that's where the
real instructions are.
My melon wants to punch my dad
in the face and steal his arm.
[ laughs ]
Well, those things are bad,
so they can't be the real
instructions,
but you keep listening.
Me -- I'm gonna go
to the spaghetti store
and buy a new mop head.
I'll be back soon.
Just remember --
listen to your melon heart.
FINN:
[ sighs ]
Melon heart.
Man, | don't know.
It'd be so easy if | could just
go find him -- my dad, that is.
That portal he went through
after ripping off my favorite
arm went right
to outer space.
And outer space is up there
somewhere ...I'm told.
Maybe Banana Man could help me
build a rocket or something...
or some stairs or...something,
something, something.
Or...or...or...
Wow, it's like a --
like a --
like a magic Finn arm.
[ energy buzzing ]
She's powerful.
You must've exploded
the candy arm before
and made the
rock pile just now.
It's almost like I'm trying
to tell myself something,
like a message
from my melon heart.
[ humming ]
NEVGCINELGH
Oh!
I'm so glad
you're here.
Afternoon, Princess.
What's that
you're building?
Wait, you don't know?
l...might?
Here. Look.
It was taped to the tower.
"Jake, I'm going to space to
punch my dad and steal his arm.
Back soon -- Finn."
Wow, what the he?!
My biggest powerometer
back at the castle
was flipping
all the way out.
It looks like Finn somehow
manifested a sort of telekinetic
electro-emotional
prosthesis.
Word. Word.
With this much raw power,
he could be a danger
to himself or others,
so I've quarantined the area
till I can coax him down.
Pbht!
T.M.L.O., Princess.
What does fthat mean?
"That means lay off."
Finn's feeling this
one out solo-style.
Give the kid a chance.
[ whimpering ]
FINN:
JÈ Daddy's got an arm È
È And baby's gonna harm his
arm by tearing it off his dad È
> Baby's building a
tower into space JÈ
È Space is where he's
gonna find his dad È
> Daddy's got an arm and -- È
[ chomp ]
> Baby's gonna harm his arm
by tearing it off his dad È
[ whimpering ]
> Baby's building a
tower into space JÈ
È Space is where he's
gonna find his dad È
JÈ Daddy's got an arm È
È And baby's gonna harm his
arm by tearing it off his dad È
[ shrieks ]
Oh. Hi.
Get out of my house, or I'm
gonna face bla-a-a-st you.
Hi.
[ rumble, crackling ]
Whoa.
Yep, yeah. | know you.
You're one of
those swimmers, right?
A real swim nut.
What? No.
I'm Finn.
Well, you can't swim in me --
Not anymore.
I'm not water.
You can't get
me up yournose.
Okay.
I'm gonna keep going.
I'm gonna keep going...
into here.
È Oh, baby's building
a tower into space JÈ
È Space, where he's
gonna find his dad È
[ hammer thumping ]
[ blows ]
Good night, buddy!
I'm proud of you!
[ whimpering ]
[ birds chirping ]
> Baby's building a
tower into space JÈ
D To tear off
his dad's arm >
D From, like, where that round
of the arm bone meets that weird
flat bone at the
top of the back È
È Gonna pull that
until it comes off JÈ
> Baby's building
a tower of revenge )
Hey, kid.
It's me, again.
Carroll.
My name's Carroll.
Finn.
Finn, look, I'm sorry about
blasting you yesterday.
Hey, man...are you really
gonna do those things?
Uh...yeah. For revenge.
| think it'll feel good.
| getit. | getit.
But let me tell
you something --
| used to be water, like
a pond or something real wet.
| used to hate people swimming
in me -- kicking and stuff.
So what did | do?
| evaporated.
| got myself out of there.
You should've pulled
off their legs.
No, no, no, no, no, no, No.
Listen -- you have to stop
obsessing about revenge.
Hmph.
Be like me and run away.
You have to run away and never
stop hating your old life.
You got to really
dwell on it.
WEEEEL]
What was that?!
| just thought about my
anxieties,
and it's like my mind-hand
touched a hot memory stove.
Mm.
WEEELL
Interesting.
Oh, hey, what are your
thoughts on melon hearts?
| don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, all right, then.
I guess I'll
see you later.
[ whistling ]
Hey, Jake. Where --
Where's Finn?
Finn's just working
some stuff out.
And that's healthy!
It's not healthy!
It's bizarre,
and he could get hurt!
Feelings hurt!
Yeah!
Yeah.
Ehh.
[ wheezing ]
CARROLL:
Finn!
Hey, what's it
like up there?!
I'm thinking | could turn
into space ice or something.
[ wheezing ]
[ warble! ]
[ gasps ]
[ wheezing ]
Dad!
[ groans ]
Oh, man.
My nogmaster.
Hello?
Hel-- oh!
[ stifled laugh ]
Hey. Hey, dad.
Huh? Oh. Good.
You're awake.
Mmm! Gotchal!
[ laughs ]
[ creak! ]
Give -- give it.
Give me the --
give me. Give it.
[ moaning ]
Oh, no. My --
my favorite arm.
Oh, no.
[ sighs ]
Bu-u-u-tts.
Butts.
BUBBLEGUM:
Didn't help much, did it?
No.
Wait. What?
Bong. Bong.
Sorry, buddy.
PB?!
Wait, where am 1?
We're in the
Candy Kingdom fallout shelter.
| brought you here after you
passed out on the tower.
You were
hallucinating like crazy,
so it was really
easy to trick you.
| figured you'd thank me later
after you learned your lesson.
Right. Right.
And look --
the arm is gone, too.
See?
So, what do you think?
Mmm.
[ heart beating ]
Yeah, okay.
Thanks, Princess.
[ snoring ]
[ whimpers ]
Oh, hey,
buddy, you're back.
How you feeling?
Um...neutral, | guess.
| don't want to
punch my dad anymore.
Ha ha! That's great!
You can always trust the old
melon heart to get you through.
So, | guess we won't be
needing this thing anymore.
You want to
do the honors?
Yes, | do.
[ rumbling ]
BUBBLEGUM:
Aaah! My arm!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!