[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ thunder rumbling ]
BMO:
Kya! Kyal!
Hmm.
Ohhh,
that's pretty good.
Kya!
BMO!
Keep it down!
But you said 8:00 to 10:00
is my time to do karate.
It's my karate time!
| know, but |
got a headache,
and I'm in a funky mood.
What's wrong, dude?
| don't know.
| think | got
restless-leg syndrome.
Is that from
gettin' chubby?
What?
No, man, it's
just restless leg.
Oop! My bad.
What are you reading?
This old copy of
Adventure Boy magazine --
The only magazine for
boy adventurers.
This kid Rusty is
getting chased
down the river by
three grown otters.
This magazine rules!
But I'm saving the
end for tomorrow.
Cool.
Well, | hope your leg
feels better.
I'm turning in.
I'll see you up there.
[ inhales deeply ]
Pbht!
[ singsong voice ]
NELGH
No, BMO.
Kya!
[ roars ]
No, BMO!
No more!
[ thunder rumbling ]
Maybe some soup will
take the edge off.
[ soup bubbling ]
[ buzzing ]
Bzzzt, bzzzt!
[ slurps ]
Ew! Gross! Nasty!
Bzzzt, bzzzt!
Hyah!
Bzzzt, bzzzt, bzzzt!
I'm sorry you were born a
fly and | had to kill you,
you disgusting,
disgusting creature.
BMO:
Kya, Kya, Kya!
BMO, please!!
[ snoring ]
[ yawns, smacks lips ]
[ rustling, knocking ]
Finn, was that you?
[ snoring ]
Probably just BMO
or something.
[ needle scratches ]
[ jazz music plays ]
That's weird.
BMO doesn't
like '30s jazz.
[ music continues ]
Yeesh. Creepy.
[ music stops ]
[ gasps ]
| didn't know we had
one of those.
[ ghostly wailing ]
Hey, hey. Hey, who?
[ wailing continues ]
[ buzzing ]
Aah!
[ wailing continues ]
Hey.
| killed youl!
Aah!
[ whiffle! ]
Ghost Fly touching me!
Finn! Finn!
Aah!
Ghost Fly, man!
Aah! Aah!
Okay.
Come on, man.
Let's get out
of the house.
It's a Ghost Fly!
So what?
No, man, Ghost
Flies are filthy!
They carry diseases such as
tuberculosis, polio, dysentery.
They leave those little fly
doodies on your soul.
[ whooshing ]
Aah!
[ shing! ]
[ both gasp ]
BOTH:
Aah!
[ thud ]
Finn, Jake!
What's wrong?!
BOTH:
Ghost Fly!
ACEEEEEE ]
[ all screaming ]
[ panting ]
[ sighs ]
Thank goodness
we lost him.
He's gone.
[ buzzing ]
Whoo.
Aah!
Run! Just run!
Oy!
Ai, ai, ai, ail
[ wailing ghostily ]
Hmm.
Kya! Kyal!
[ gasps ]
Who-o-o0-a!
Aah!
[ grunts ]
We should ask what its
unfinished business is.
Ghosts always have
unfinished business!
Ghost Fly,
what's your problem?
[ grunts ]
Come on, dude. Tell us
your unfinished business.
Aah!
It's no good.
He's a tortured
little spirit.
We need help to communicate
with this Ghost Fly.
Nah, man.
Let's just get someone
to banish it --
someone with serious
paranormal juice.
[ dialing ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ cellphone rings, vibrates ]
BMO:
Is he coming soon?
JAKE:
| think so.
His ways are kind
of mysterious.
FINN:
That's cool.
[ wailing ghostily ]
[ all scream ]
[ all shouting ]
[ clattering ]
Who-0-0-0-0-a!
[ footsteps approach ]
Woo0?
Let's get this
ritual rolling.
| got stuff to do.
Woo!
Hey! No!
Unclean demon,
feel the sting of holy water!
Thank you.
These circles will protect you
from the ghost's attacks
while | prepare
the banishing ritual.
Worry not, fellow believers,
for in this bag,
| possess all the darkest
and most powerful tools
of magic ever to be
assembled in one place.
We're perfectly safe --
as long as ...we ...have...
[ glass shatters |
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
[ bonk! bonk! bonk! ]
Well, huh.
How about that?
No biggie.
We'll just hang out inside these
magic circles until morning.
That's when ghosts
go to sleep.
Yep.
Just got to make it...
till morning.
[ wailing ghostily ]
[ wailing continues ]
Woo!
[ papers rustling ]
Hmm?
[ gasps ]
The end of my story.
And it's so close.
Don't doit, bro.
It's a trap.
FINN:
| know.
It's an obvy trap.
But wait.
What if...
Watch this.
Ha!
Mm?
Dude, what are you --
If | extend the circle...
farther...
| can get closer
to the magazine.
Theoretically,
that is possible.
Yeah, but I'm still getting
a "woo-jah" feeling.
This seems like
a bad idea.
Just have to stay
inside this circle!
Ha ha!
How'd you do it, Rusty?
How'd you shake
them otters?
[ laughs ]
Man, what a great ending!
[ gagging ]
Finn?
What's wrong, buddy?
[ breathing distortedly ]
[ both screaming ]
Oh, Finn,
you're disgusting!
[ grunting, gurgling ]
[ buzzing ]
Aw, that's it!
I've had it with
this Ghost Fly!
| wish | were a
ghost so | could
punch him with
my ghost fist!
Jake, | have a
radical option.
I've been studying
a karate move
that could
temporarily stop your heart
long enough
for you to
fight the ghost on
his own plane of existence.
What?
It's okay!
| learned it out
of a magazine.
Finn.
All right.
But first you got to give me
some unfinished business so
| can come back
as a ghost.
Tell me a joke.
Okay.
What do you call a bear that
only attacks guys named Paul?
Kya!
[ gurgling ]
| killed Jake!
Yay, BMO!
Whoa!
BMO, you killed me.
Whoa. Wow.
Wow!
Jake!
| can't hear you!
| will start your heart up
in five minutes, okay?
This many.
Okay.
Five minutes.
Whoa.
[ animals calling ]
Is this some kind of
low-level dead world?
That's a bummer.
[ thuds ]
Aah!
[ panting ]
[ screams ]
[ hiss!]
Aah!
Oh, stuff!
Ohh! Ohh!
Get away!
[ grunts ]
Aah!
You killed it!
[ panting ]
Aah! Aah!
Get away!
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
Aah!
Whoa!
[ panting ]
Aah!
[ grunting ]
[ moans ]
Aaaaaahh!
[ wailing ghostily ]
Hmm?
Ooooo0h!
[ slurping ]
That's right.
You never
finished the soup.
That's your
unfinished business!
Woo-hoo.
And now that
you've finished it,
you get to ascend to a
glorious new peaceful realm.
[ twinkle! ]
Ahh!
Bam!
Shouldn't have tried
to kill me, son!
[ blows ]
Yes!
What's happening?
Oh, BMO must be
bringing me back!
Yes! Yeah, BMO!
[ monitor beeping ]
Mm.
BMO?
NELGH
| missed you, bro!
Jake!
Don't ever
leave me again!
Good job, BMO!
You brought me back.
RVECELOA!
Yes. Yay, BMO.
BMO is so good.
Whew!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!