[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Chips?
[ laughter ]
Ice cream?
Chips!
[ laughter ]
Chips.
Ch-i-ips!
Ice cream!
[ laughter ]
| don't get it.
Ah, just keep watching.
BMO said the
second act gets crazy.
Chips chips chips.
Chips chips...
Chips!
Ice cream!
Chips...
Ice cream...
[ cheers and applause ]
Bravo!
What the
stuff was that?!
Now, who wants to
invite me over for dinner?
[ all cheering ]
Come on, kids!
We're going
to Grandma's.
[ sighs ]
Dinner?
Please can we
invite him to dinner?!
No.
But, Jake, | never
ask you for anything.
When did | ever
ask you for anything?
Yesterday.
You said, "Jake, please take
me to see Chips and Ice Cream!
It's a Broadway smash!"
And | believed you.
[ crying ]
You don't
understand me, Jake.
[ sighs ]
Please come
over for dinner!
| love youl!
[ squeals ]
Yeah.
Dinner sounds great!
[ chuckles ]
Yeah!
Wait.
The place where
you eat dinner,
does the moon shine
through the window at night?
Sure.
Al right!
Let's do it!
Oh, ooh!
And when Chips trips over
the turtle, it was so funny!
But also sad.
It made me think about the
fragility of my own life.
Just a little more...
Y'all ready for
some sushi burgers?
| don't eat burgers.
Got any Chips
and Ice Cream?
Uh...sure.
| just sculpted
these buns, though.
[ fist raps ]
Give the man
what he wants!
So0000...
is your name Chips
and Ice Cream?
My name is Morty Rogers.
| see.
Okay! Food's done.
[ both cheer ]
Let's a//dig in.
Yes, eat it.
Eat that Chips
and Ice Cream.
Oh! Yes, sir!
[ gasps ]
It's time.
Chips chips chips?
Ice cream ice cream.
No...flipping...way!
By the light of
the waxing moon,
which was just unveiled
by the parting clouds,
| command these two
Imps that have taken
possession of my ears to
transfer onto the head of
the being who is directly across
from me and is currently eating
Chips and Ice Cream!
Chips chips?
Ice cream...
Huh.
It worked!
I'm a free bear!
[ laughs hysterically ]
Well, now I'm a guy
with these things on my head.
| guess I'm just gonna
roll with the punches.
Uh...
Don't worry, man.
I'm gonna pretend
they're not even there.
Chips!
Ice cream!
This is the greatest
day of my liiiife!
Chips chips chips...
Chips chips...
Maybe if | put
a towel over my head,
they'll go to sleep.
Huh.
What's on your head?
| don't even notice it.
Heh.
Yeah, okay.
Chips chips.
Ice cream.
[ crying ]
Chips...
[ sniffles ]
Huh?
Chips...
Chips!
Chips chips chips.
Chips.
Chips chips!
[ moaning ]
Ice cream?
Chips chips!
Chips chips chips
chips chips!
Ice cream?
Ice cream
Ice cream ice cream!
[ grumbles ]
All right,
that's enough.
They're going outside.
Noooooooo!
Chips.
Ice cream.
Poor Chips and Ice Cream.
J Ah, ah, ah, ah )
D lce cream JÈ
Chips chips chips chips...
D Ice cream,
ice cream J
J Ah, ah, ah È
Chips chips.
[ moans ]
Why are you up so early?
| got to get to the
Farmer's Market before all
the choice stuff is gone.
Oh.
Why is BMO on your head?
He is?!
Chips chips.
Ice cream.
I'm onto
something important.
Quit clownin' around.
Okay.
| was done anyhows.
[ distorted ]
Chips chips...
So, you want me
to pick up any snacks?
Yeah, maybe
some ketchup chips?
Chips.
And...some kale...
chips.
Chips!
And some corn...chips.
Okay.
Later, dude.
Later.
Chips!
Ice cream!
[ sighs ]
Hmm.
Nice choice!
Those are two of my fave.
Chips!
Yeah, we have chips.
Ice cream?
Sorry. | don't
have any ice cream,
but | know who does.
[ whistles ]
Hey, John!
Yo!
| gots a
customer for yous!
I'll bag
these for you.
Enjoy and
stay awesome.
Yo!
| got ice creams!
Ice cream?
| recommend the
hamburger flavor.
Also, the pizza
flavor is tremendous!
MAN:
Do you have taco?
One second!
One taco flavored.
You have the best!
You have the best,
out-of-this-world day.
What's your
spectacular choice?
[ gasps ]
No. No!
Stay away!
You can't make
me take them back!
Oh, hey,
Morty Rogers.
Ice cream!
Aaaaaaah!
Tremendous!
[ panting ]
No more Chips.
No more Ice Cream.
Beans.
That's what
regular-sized-ear folks eat.
Regular old Morty Rogers.
Aaaaaaah!
[ groaning ]
[ inhales sharply ]
[ mid-tempo music plays ]
[ record needle scratches,
record skipping ]
Oh!
| hope the record is not
scratched or chipped.
Chip?
Ice cream.
Chips.
Chips chips chips.
Ice creeeeam.
Chips chips! Chip chip.
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Hush! Hush!
Hush!
Noiseless, Chips!
Inaudible, Ice cream!
Nyaah!
Chips chips chips chips.
Chips chips chips...
Ice cream ice cream.
Ice cream ice cream...
Chips chips chips...
Aah! Quiet!
| thought | could just
ignore them, but | can't!
Chips and
Ice Cream have to go!
Listen. Even if | could
find Morty Rogers again,
| don't know how to get these
things to go back to him
or even if
they want to.
Chips chips!
Ice cream!
| finished with
my computations!
As | thought, it's a real
language they are speaking --
Based on intonations!
Chips?
Chips chips chips!
Ice cream?
Ice cream ice cream!
| know what we have to do.
How many years did | search
for a rube to take my burden?
What's wrong with me?
You two brought me
nothing but pain...
and | can't stop
thinking of you.
But | don't
want you back!
| don't want you!
Chips chips chips...
What's that?
- Do you hear that?
- ) lce cream )
- It's like...
- È Chips È
D lce cream JÈ
l...must...
|...must!
D Ice cream, ice cream J
Chips, chips, chips, chips...
D lce cream JÈ
He's here!
2 | love you,
Chips and Ice Cream )
2 | hope you never leave È
No! Those are my
Chips and Ice Cream!
By the light of
the waxing moon,
which was just unveiled
by the parting clouds,
transfer those two imps
that have taken possession
of Jake's ears to the
head of the being who is
watching from the window!
Chips and Ice Cream!
BMO, it's happening!
No!
My Chips!
and Ice Cream!
Free!
Noooo!
Whoa.
What's going on?
Chips and Ice Cream
wanted to be free.
But they could only be
released if | interrupted
the transference ritual.
- Free?
I'm sorry for keeping
you dudes as my prisoners
for so many years.
But what am | gonna
do without you?!
Chips.
Ice cream.
What?
Chips!
Ice cream!
Chips.
Ice cream.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!