[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
I'm home!
[ whirring ]
Who's gonna have
dinner with me tonight?
[ beeping ]
Sorry, fellas.
| got to go make
some dreams come true.
Where are we headed,
Dream Token?
Aha!
Aw, Finn again.
[ laughing ]
[ lightning striking ]
Say "Cheese!"
[ camera shutter clicking ]
Cheese!
[ hoots ]
- leybdoog Yas
- Hello!
Huh? Wait, wait!
Who's that?
[ camera shutter clicking ]
[ lightning strikes ]
She's so beautiful!
[ camera shutter clicks ]
Butt feathers!
Huh?
Whoa,
the Cosmic Owl?!
Does that mean this
dream is important?!
Is this a
prophetic dream?!
And is this stuff all
symbolic or literal?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, sort of.
Wait.
What does
it all mean, boy?
Dang, she's gone!
What? W-w-what
are you asking me?
Uh,
| can't tell you that.
[ hoots ]
[ breathing shallowly ]
| don't know, Shelby.
| think it's
too dark in there.
Aah!
Pull him up,
pull him up!
[ sighs ]
Think | just had
a prophetic dream.
Cosmic Owl was in it.
He was acting
all choco-loco.
Finn, you got
to go back to sleep.
Huh?
Cosmic Owl dreams
are important always!
You got to
find him again!
Yeah, but last time |
chased a Cosmic Owl dream,
| got dumped.
Shh!
Get back in there!
It's too important.
You don't got time to
waste on my class ring
or bets with Shelby
or stomach fishing.
Oop!
What?
Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh!
[ snoring ]
All right,
let's do it.
Hey, Cosmic Owl!
You still here? Oh!
[ bear roars ]
Butt feathers...
Love is weird, man.
It really does come
when you least expect it.
Dude, you've been working
on that since you got here.
Take a break.
You haven't even asked me
about my banjo lessons.
They're going great!
Dude?
Sorry, | just can't stop
thinking about her.
[ laughs ]
You really are
in love, huh?
All right, tell me
more about her.
Where'd you meet?
In a dream.
What?! Whose?!
Finn the human.
What?!
Who's that?!
No, wait,
| know that guy.
Look, | don't think you were put
in charge of prophetic dreams
so you could meet ladies.
Who cares?
I'm in love!
[ chuckles ]
What am | even
worried about?
How will you ever
even find her again?
Do you have any idea how many
people are dreaming every night?
Yes, | do.
Dude, it could take
you a million years.
Then it would
be worth it --
For love!
[ banjo music playing ]
Forgot my sketchbook.
[ mid-tempo music playing ]
[ grunting ]
[ mid-tempo music continues ]
It's gonna be
a long night.
[ beeping ]
[ mid-tempo music continues ]
[ chains rattling ]
[ beeping ]
Uh...
[ warbles ]
[ ballroom music playing ]
[ indistinct talking ]
Hmm?
[ gasps ]
[ buzzer sounds ]
Excuse me?
Are these weenies?
Shrimp puffs,
monsieur.
Oh.
[ sighs ]
Uh, hi.
Onh.
Is that a weenie?
It's a shrimp puff.
Oh, | love
shrimps puffs!
Here.
This is a
dream come true.
[ chuckles nervously ]
[ munches ]
Do | know you?
I'm crashing.
Oh.
| saw you in a dream,
and | had to see you again,
even though just by
me being here,
events in this dream
will come true.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Agh!
[ laughter ]
Oh, geez,
that poor guy.
- Whose dream?
-Hmm?
Whose dream did
you see me in?
- Oh, uh, Finn the human.
- Hmm.
| shouldn't be here.
No, you intrigue me.
So powerful.
W-what's happening?
You're waking up.
Oh, no!
Can't you go
back to sleep?
No, once I'm up,
I'm up!
But | want to
see you again!
I'd like that.
Okay, I'll bookmark
your dream coordinates
and come to you
tomorrow night.
[ munches ]
What do | do with
the toothpick?
I'll take it!
PRISMO: And so then she's like,
"l really like you,"
and | was like,
"l really like you, too,"
and she was like,
"I don't want to hold
hands until I'm in love,"
and | was like,
"That sounds great.
I'm all about
going slow,"
and she said, "What?
You don't want to hold my hand?"
Huh?!
Okay, what is going on
with that toothpick?
Huh?
| can get you
a new toothpick.
No, | don't
want a new one.
[ warbling ]
| got to go!
No, wait,
there's one --
[ buzzer sounds ]
Hil
Hi.
Hmm, are there
any appetizers?
No, | think it's just
ice in this dream.
Oh, I wish | could
dream another place.
| have an idea.
My apartment.
Oh.
It's a bit of a mess.
[ chuckles ]
I'm not used to
having company.
No, it's got...
personality.
| know, right?
Hey, do you
like board games?
Tell me about #Ais.
Oh, | use that for work.
It's interesting.
Yeah, | guess it is.
Y-you want to spy
on people's dreams?
Can we?
Sure.
[ chuckles nervously ]
What's it like to have all
this at your fingertips?
| guess | don't even
think about it.
But you're not powerful enough
to see into everyone's dreams, are you?
I'm totally that powerful.
Even royalty?
Like Ice King
or something?
His dreams are so sad.
Like Princess Bubblegum.
Surely, she has some sort of
dream security system in place.
[ chuckles ]
No, we can
go right now.
Is that what
this is about?
Yes, let's
go right now.
[ chuckles nervously ]
T-this feels weird.
It seems like you
really want to go.
It's okay to
feel manipulated, right?
[ buzzer sounds ]
[ rumbling ]
[ cheers and applause ]
Oh, thank youl!
Thank youl!
[ cheers and applause ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
A-after all I've
done for you?!
Agh!
What?
Something's wrong.
Does this dream
seem weird to you?
[ hoots ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
No!
| worked so hard!
[ creature moaning ]
Aaaaah!
Hey! Hey, you!
Huh?
Do you have any
idea what you've done?
You interfered
with a dream!
Oh, man,
a dream | was /n/
Why did you do
[hoots] it?!
| --1can't
really explain it.
It just felt like
the right thing to do.
You -- you
ruined everything!
We would've been
so perfect together!
Oh, who | am kidding?!
It's over...
It doesn't
have to be over.
We can run away --
together.
You're dreaming, Kid,
and it's time to wake up.
No, I-I --
[ hoots ]
[ gasps ]
Wenk!
Gunther?
Oh, did baby have
a bad dream?
Let me get
you a bottle.
Aah!
[ laughter ]
Wenk!
Huh, what's eating him?
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!