[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Annyong!
[ laughing ]
Whoo-hoo! Hoo-hoo!
Hey, bear dude,
sorry to drop in like that.
Oh, hey...brother.
Whoa. Jermaine?!
We must be dreaming
at the same time again.
Yeah.
| was just hanging with
a couple of ladies outside...
or a couple of
the same lady...
then bam!
Skyboxed!
Ugh.
Jake, I'm here to work.
| got to keep everything
where it should be.
So, uh...how are you
and Finn doing?
Whoop! Ah!
[ Rainicorn laughter ]
Uh...
Epsilon, Eucradies,
Dernesto...
[ sneezes |
Jermaine?
You okay, man?
No, no, I'm --
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
Oh.
Epsilon, Eucradies...
Dernesto...
Hey, listen, um, maybe we should
get together in the awake world?
You know,
meet in Meatspace?
Uh, yeah.
Sounds great.
See you later.
[ breathes deeply ]
In the dream, Jermaine
was wearing a bear suit.
| wonder what
that symbolizes.
Maybe it means Jermaine
needs us to visit.
It has been a while.
Workout time!
You want the
can or the cup?
| like the can.
[ sips ]
Hmm. I'd hate it if my kids
didn't ever see each other...
Or if Viola shoved Jake Jr.
down a dream hole.
| don't know.
Jermaine's always been
kind of a dream hole.
Whoa.
WENCEL
getting older.
We should go see him now,
or we might regret it.
Eh. It's not a great
time just this minute.
Trying to figure
this deal out.
[ air hissing ]
Whoa!
[ sips ]
Okay. Let's go
see Jermaine.
There's a lot more
demons here than | remember.
Huh. Yeah.
The only constant
is change, bro.
| want my yoyo!
Yo yo!
That's rude, dude!
Give back my cup!
Huh?
Bring me my cup,
or I'll skull cup you!
[ roars ]
[ both scream ]
[ hissing ]
Yipe!
Jake!
Whoa!
Oh, you guys
really came.
Quick! Get behind
the salt barrier!
They can't
cross the circle.
It's made from dad's
old shaman-blessed,
sage-infused salt.
Return my cup!
Stop poking me!
[ laughs ]
Knock it off, guys.
Just get in the house.
You guys can chill here till morning
when the demons thin out a little.
Whoo!
Oh, Finn --
Oh, no!
Instant regret!
Whoo! My house!
My house!
Instant regret!
[ gasps ]
Whoo!
Remember, Jermaine?!
We did this when we wanted
to make room for dessert!
| don't care
about that memory.
What?
Whoa -- ohh!
Dang! My back!
Come on!
This ain't the
tree house, man!
| got systems!
Hey, Jermaine,
this thing is rad--
Whoa!
Okay! No more sleepover!
Oh, no! Don't --
don't kick us out!
Go do your Gaucho Marks
slapstick with them
goofballs in the woods.
| got a responsibility to
all this booty in here --
staves, medallions, cups,
goblets, dormant jinn,
grimoires, hard drives...
all this random
valuable booty, okay?
[ watch beeping ]
Oh, shoot.
| got to run this beast.
"Open, ya sissy!"
DS Inthe end )
D> We'll be friends È
> Flip me and È
È We'll start again >
Yeah, flip the tape,
| know.
S Good times never end... >
"Good times."
Right.
Hey!
I'm Booboo Sousal!
You want
to be friends?
We been friends,
Booboo.
D Hello, there È
È Good morning JÈ
5 Booboo Sousa È
You're slippinÕ,
Jerm.
No, I'm not.
You're gonna miss
that alarm one day,
and I'm gonna eat you from
the bottom up so you can
watch me while | eat you.
Then, in my triumph,
| will retrieve the poster
your Dad stole from me!
Bryce, | put the
poster right there.
You're still
mad about that?
How dare you use
tacks on my poster!
You're gonna
get it, man!
You know, Bryce, | would've let
you and your poster go years
ago if you'd stop it with all
that "From the bottom up" talk.
You would?
Yeah, man.
| don't want to flip
that tape all day!
That's you
and Joshua beef
Ôcause you wouldn't stop
breaking in for that poster.
Well, come on, man.
Let's be bros.
No way, you psycho.
| ain't never gonna trust you
after all that stuff you said.
I'm gonna taste that dog
carne asada, you hear?!
You're never gonna taste
my carne asada, Bryce.
Dude, you can't
live like this!
Yeah, you got a
plan "B" for Bryce or what?
| don't need a plan "B."
I'm responsible.
You guys want fried
rice or something?
| can make fried rice.
No, Jermaine.
We'll make
you fried rice.
Okay. Just don't
break any more junk.
That's our parents' valuable
artifacts, you knuckleheads.
I'm gonna white-knuckle
you, Jermaine!
You'll see!
[ laughter ]
[ sighs ]
Whoo-hoo!
| never even made
fried rice before!
Get the plates.
Whoosh!
D-u-u-ump!
Pre-sen-tation.
Good plating.
Sorry | only
have one chair.
To brothers!
ALL:
It doesn't have
to be weird, you guys!
[ howling in distance ]
What's that sound?
It sounds like howling.
Let's eat!
Dang, dude, this
fried rice destroys!
How'd you get
all this flavor?
Sesame oil and salt.
Salt is one of the
five taste sensations.
Sweet, sour,
bitter, umami, and salty.
| guess I'm just
used to bitter.
That's weird.
| haven't had salt
in like five years.
Hold on.
Epsilon, eucradies,
dernesto, quillduct...
Uh, where'd you get
the salt from, Jake?
| snooched a
little from outside. Why?
Aaiee!
[ demons howling ]
Get my cup, Ariel!
Please, dude!
You get it!
| need my DAT tapes!
| can't fit through
that hole, Ariel!
Aaaaah!
I'll shock him, and
you guys ace his brains!
BOTH:
Gotiit!
That sword's too
unwieldy, man.
But it'll look decent
when [ triple combo this bozo
with this thing, right?
Like how?
Like this, bro...
[ grunting ]
Aah! Oofl
Boo, stupid!
Aaaaaaah!
Where's my DAT tapes?!
Epsilon, eucradies,
epilindus...
Oofl
Why is this thing so dense?
| got your tapes over here!
Give me my ta-- oof!
Aah!
| got him!
Hup!
Sha-boom!
Whoa! Watch it!
Cut his arms, Finn!
Okay! Hyah!
[ both shouting ]
Whoa!
Wha--
Aaaaaah!
My cup, Jermaine!
Oofl
You're a pain, Jermaine!
Jermaine the pain!
Awesome, dude! We won!
| didn't win!
When do | win?!
Special guys one and
two win every day!
Crackin' jokes,
readin' foodie
mags in your
treetown funhouse!
Must be nice to be so special
you can go off and find your
own fancy ways!
Meanwhile, | got to stay here
and watch dad's trashy booty
'cause | never stretched into
the sky and farted on the wings
of a falcon, | guess!
Dude, | never farted
on the wing of a falcon.
[ snorts ]
Aah!
Bros!
Chill, Jermaine --
oof!
Think | don't want a
cushy tree-house life?!
| don't even get salt!
S-a-a-a-alt!
Bark! Bark!
Bark!
Huh?
Yeowch!
[ growling ]
Unh!
I'm sick of bein'
daddy's watchdog!
[ grunts ]
[ grumbling ]
This must've been
building up for a while.
[ roars ]
[ grunts ]
Whoa.
Wha!
Hand fire.
Ahh!
You got to be
dad's favorite!
| got stuck
with his mess!
Come on.
Dad didn't
have a favorite.
He just liked
my fart jokes.
I'm the fart joke!
Shazbaz!
Uh, no.
Ow.
Dad loved us both.
You could've
left anytime.
| know!
If you
punch me again,
I'm gonna fart.
[ farts ]
Heh...
[ chuckling ]
[ farts ]
Oh, man.
I've really
built my own cage.
Guys, guys, guys!
This whole place
is burning down!
So if you're done
being angry bonkers,
let's work together!
Jermaine?
You gonna leave
me hanging, bro?
Let it burn.
Huh?
But all
of dad's stuff!
No.
| think it's all right.
The salt
line got broken.
Where'd all the D's go?
Maybe with
their stuff gone,
they had no
reason to stay.
[ watch beeping ]
Oh, no! The tape!
[ grunts ]
Open!
[ coughing ]
| got my poster!
[ coughs ]
Booboo Sousa...
| ate his
stupid face off.
It was sick.
Ugh.
Do you even know what you sound
like when you talk like that?
| sound cool.
If that's what you think.
That's what | know.
Dang. Has it always been
so bright out here?
Makes me wanna
explode the sun
and banish the earth
into darkness.
JERMAINE:
See? You're doing it again!
D Hello, there È
È Good morning JÈ
5 Booboo Sousa È
> Come closer >
D> Never leave me )
5 Booboo Sousa È
2 Our friendship È
D It matters b
5 Booboo Sousa È
D Hello, there È
È Good morning JÈ
This party is so crazy!