[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Sick! Sick!
So si-i-i-ck!
Dying!
Check it out.
| got snacks
for while we wait.
For Marcy --
red lick-rish.
Thanks.
And for BMO...
[ gasps ]
Fresh Boyz!
So, Finn...
What are we
waiting here for?
What? Dude, it's
Super Porp Day.
Yeah.
Don't you know
about Super Porp Day?
Wait.
"Super Porp"...
like in the old commercials?
Uh, let's see, like...
> Super Porp È
2 It hits the spot È
È Messes up your
train of thought .
2 If you're thirsty
and out of shape )
ALL:
È Get down on that fizzy grape! È
Yeah, yeah,
that's the one.
Today's the day when
Squeez-E-Mart always gets
their monthly shipment.
What?
That's really weird, guys.
Why would s--
Stop talking!
Here it comes!
[ up-tempo music plays ]
Enjoy Super Porp!
| love you, Cheryl.
[ gulping ]
Man, this biz
takes me back.
| used to drink this stuff
all the time when | was a kid.
What?
That's not right.
How could the exact same soda
still be in production hundreds
of years after the
Great Mushroom Wars?
Eh-eh-eh-eh-eh!
Okay, listen.
So, okay, we could
go track down
the mysterious
source of Super Porp.
Do up a f'real quest,
end up fightin' some big
soda-computer-god-baby
or whatever...
We totally could.
But...
Super Porp is good.
So why question this
good thing, man?
Why?
Hmm...
Yeah, okay.
Let's just go home.
Yay! Super Porp!
Yay! BMO!
[ indistinct conversations |
[all gasp ]
[ cheering ]
[ chanting "Super Porp" ]
Enjoy Super Porp!
ALL:
We will, Cheryl!
No, Cheryl.
Susan will nof enjoy!
Chill out, Susan Strong.
Yeah.
Super Porp taste good!
Super Porp is good!
No.
It fake juice.
Tough-guy hyoomans do
not drink fake juice.
Hmph.
Go away, robots!
[ growls ]
[ baby cooing ]
[ gasps ]
Baby?
Baby!
Eh?!
[ grunts ]
Baby!
Huh?
[ gasps ]
Oh, dang!
[ grunts ]
Hyah!
Baby.
Porp fountain.
[ growls ]
Hmm?
[ grunts ]
Cheryl.
Where's baby?
Cheryl better talk!
Hello, and welcome to the
original Super Porp factory!
Are you ready
to get Por-orped?
I-I-I think we all need
to get Po-0-0-0-0-rped.
Baby!
[ gasps ]
Susan killed Cheryl!
[ sniffs ]
No!
This is fake
style bubblehead.
Cheryl trying
to trick us!
[ groaning ]
[ gasps ]
Baby!
That hole too
small for Susan.
If Sally say so...
Hup! Hyah!
[ crash! ]
[ grunting ]
You two,
follow baby cries.
[ grunts ]
Susan will
find other way.
Hmm?
Hmm...
[ droning ]
ALL:
> Super Porp È
2 It hits the spot È
Eh?
JÈ It messes up your
train of thought .
2 If you're thirsty
and out of shape )
JÈ Get down on that
fizzy grape È
ALL:
> Super Po-0-0-0-rp È
Uh...
Hey!
Ugh!
No one is allowed to
taste pure Porp syrup!
You know this, Carla.
But it looks sooo good.
Well,
of course it does!
| mean, I'd smash everyone's
face in this room for a single
drop of pure Porp.
But that's not the
Super Porp way.
[ whimpers ]
Aw, cheer up, girl.
Maybe we'll
get bonus reg-Porp
after that new
baby gets processed.
[ growls ]
Baby!
[all gasp ]
Hey!
Where's your hairnet?!
[ grunts ]
Oow!
W-w-where's your hairnet?
Where's your hairnet?
Where's your --
Okay, verbal
warning this time.
Protect the pure Porp!
- [ grunts ]
- [ growls ]
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh! Uh-oh!
Oofl
Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh.
- Rah!
Uh-oh.
Now you tell Susan where
you take baby or I'm --
Hey,
are you new here?
Are you new here?
[ gurgling ]
[ gasps ]
[ mutants screaming ]
[ dramatic music plays ]
[ buzzer ]
Attention.
All employees report to
the break room for the daily
Porp break...
Sponsored by Super Porp!
Baby.
Break time,
break time.
Get down on that fizzy...
break time, break time.
Susan is camouflaged.
2 If you're thirsty
and out of shape )
È Get down on
that fizzy grape È
[ thinking ]
Why is Susan in this line?
Susan didn't
think this through.
Wait.
[ sniffs ]
That poorly disguised intruder
is covered in pure Porp!
ALL:
Pure Porp!
Pure Porp! Pure Porp!
[ mutants growling ]
Lick the syrup
from her eye holes!
[ grunts ]
È Get down on that
fizzy grape! È
Susan needs no fizz!
Susan have hero heart!
[ mutants groaning ]
[ buzzer ]
Break time --
Sponsored by Super Porp --
is over.
Get back to work.
The Porp must flow!
ALL:
The Porp must flow.
Must flow!
Ugh. It's sticky.
[ gurgling ]
Hmm.
[ growling ]
You a good doggy?
- You know where baby is?
- Rrr?
Doggy help Susan?
[ snarls ]
[ grunting ]
Rrgh?
No!
Hurgh!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
[ baby crying ]
Baby!
Hold on, baby!
Yaa!
[ cackling ]
Huh?
[ both growl ]
Aaah!
[ groans ]
[ gasps, pants ]
Huh?
Hi-ya!
[ whimpers ]
[ grunts ]
[ baby crying ]
Shh-shh-shh-shh-shh.
Hey. How's it goin'?
Cheryl?
Susan hates Cheryl!
So...
you're the dinguses
who trashed my facility.
Yes, Susan is the dingus!
Now gimme the baby!
Oh, | see.
You don't understand
what's going on.
Thisis a
super spesh baby.
A destiny baby.
Selected by my loyal delivery
drones to take my place as
high mascot Cheryl.
For you see --
Uhhh!
Don't drink that.
[ groans ]
Good job, Bozo.
Without a new Cheryl,
brand awareness will go
straight down the toilet.
Our in-your-face flavor
will be lost forever.
Who are you to condemn
our weird ancient ways?
[ mutants shouting ]
Stop!
Cheryl?
Yes, | am Cheryl.
[ grunts ]
[ mutants gasp ]
And Cheryl says this
is what we do now.
Back to work!
Everybody,
destroy the factory!
ALL:
Destroy the factory.
Back to work.
All right.
Well,
it's one month later.
[ up-tempo music plays ]
Aw, yeah!
Here it comes!
Hrm...
Enjoy Super Porp!
[ gulping ]
Ugh!
| jinxed it!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!