[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog È
D and Finn the Human )
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ horn honks ]
BOTH:
Road trip!
Check out this sweet
make-out wagon!
Life-Giving Magus, bro!
-Yo, yo, yo.
- Yo, yo.
Ron James, bro!
- Whazzup!
- Not much, not much.
Finn's old hat, bro!
- Uh, name's "Little Dude."
- Sure, sure.
Hey, uh...
- It's Beau.
- Beau, bro, right!
Leaf Man bro!
And, uh...
Who's this guy?
| don't know.
We just picked him up.
That's the kind of trip
this is gonna be.
It's a "destiny will guide us"
kind of thing.
How 'bout we call you...
Giuseppe.
[ farts ]
That's right,
Giuseppe.
Okay, Ron James,
it's time.
A'ight, listen up, brahs.
Here's the plan.
ALL:
Oooo0h.
We're heading
for Big Butt Rock.
At sundown, we'll gather
on the Cheek's Peak,
and using the ah-has,
deep feels,
and woo-wo00s we score
from the journey,
we will chant a totally
original spell,
thus forming an entirely
new school of magic!
Kind of like those jerky
secret societies,
but less jerky.
[ blows ]
[ all cheer ]
Just got one more stop.
Finn and Jake's
crib?
They won't come.
They're out of our league.
Hey, Abracadaniel's here,
with a bus full of lame
wizards.
Here we go.
They're probably gonna try to
lure us on some dumb trip.
ABRACADANIEL:
Hey, water nymphs!
Uh... hi.
Uh...
do you girls feel like,
uh...
going on a road trip?
Um... no thanks.
Okay, but what if I...
[ straining ]
Ew.
[ panting ]
RON JAMES:
Hey, ladies!
Hellooo.
Whoa, do you guys know
this person?
No, but his eyes are just...
gorge.
[ nymphs laughing ]
[ engine turns over ]
[ both laughing ]
Oh.
Here we go!
ALL:
Wooo!
[ bus clatters, engine stops ]
Uh, why'd we stop?
| think we ran out of gas.
[ loud clank ]
And the wheels fell off!
[ cows mooing ]
Well, this ain't goinÕ
the way we planned,
but fate has decreed
that this place
is just
what we need.
Draw your inspiration from
this muddy, old cow pasture.
Here, bros.
We got a full stock of t.p.
and magic ink.
Let's all write down arcane,
cryptic words
in unexpected new combinations
and patterns.
Maybe the nymphs can dance
on top of the bus
to be, like,
our muses.
Inspire us, water nymphs!
We don't want to.
We'd rather write.
I'll dance
if dancing is needed.
& Doo-doo doo doo-doo È
> Yah yah!
Doo-doo wah È
5 Dance, dance
È Dancin' dance writing È
2 I'm dance, dance, dance,
dancin' È
LITTLE DUDE:
Hey, check it out, y'all.
The dirty old stranger's
writing, too.
MAN:
What's all the ruckus?!
| own this pasture,
so git back in your vehicle
and qit!
We can't!
Our wheels fell off!
[ gun cocks ]
[ gasps ]
Back on the vehicle.
I'll make a slick ice road.
[ gun cocks ]
Are you gone?
| can't really see!
[ groans ]
Oh!
[ panting ]
Is there a problem?
| ran out of juice.
Can | take over?
Yeah,
maybe you should.
Hey, let's switch headgear.
Ooh, it fits!
[ giggling ]
Yeah, girl,
let the ice magic flow.
Oh, b-but be careful, okay?
- What?
Oh! [ laughs nervously ]
Not me.
Nice ice road.
Thanks.
Hey, | don't think
we're moving.
Uh, hold on.
Everyone, time to push
the bus!
Eh, | don't really want to.
Come on! Destiny!
[ all grumbling ]
ICE KING:
Push!
[ all straining ]
Okay, back on the bus!
Back on the bus!
Huh?
Ooh, a crabapple tree.
Giuseppe, make yourself useful
and grab us some of them
crabapples.
Get ready.
Jump!
Oh, no!
Giuseppe can't catch up!
What?! Magus of Life Giving,
take the wheel!
[ panting ]
Uh, okay, but | am not
a confident driver.
- You're doing great, buddy.
- Don't touch me!
Giuseppe,
throw the crabapples!
Giuseppe?
We have lost Giuseppe.
Mm! Hmm?
Well, let's see
what old Giuseppe wrote.
[ gasps ]
Listen to this, everybody!
"These are not my tear drops,
daughter dear,
but just a sheen of dew
that lingers here,
past other fields
where other fathers lie
who kept their daughters
better far than I."
[ sniffles ]
What do you guys think?
What's wrong with you guys?
[ chuckles ]
[ sniffles ]
Looks who talking.
Huh?
This is true art.
[ blows nose ]
Well, let's see what you
other guys wrote.
Little Dude, here's yours.
"Days don't have shades.
Directions with no ways.
Adjusting minimum
scholarly curriculum.
To enrich empty minds
it takes refracted sunshines."
That is awesome.
"Take this light
with your great might
Free hearts that are gated
Seeing truth in things
exaggerated."
Ah, some interesting
spell combos going on, guys.
Ice King!
| see the butt rock!
The hour of glory
is upon us.
Cauldron!
[ murmuring incantations ]
[ nymphs yawn ]
[ moans ]
[ both moan ]
Smells so good down here!
What's cooking?
[ snoring ]
[ gurgles ]
Aah! Aah!
[ screams ]
[ all scream ]
Girls, we can help.
Okay, one, two, three!
Lift!
[ nymphs straining ]
Ow! Ow.
Um...
let's get out of here.
RVECELOA!
No, don't go.
Hey, | could freeze
all of us.
Then we'd be safe
from drowning,
and once someone discovers
our preserved bodies,
we'll be saved!
Be like 200 years, tops!
[ all grumble ]
Oh! Let me try this!
Mommy!
Oh, grog! | can't swim!
- Aah! Oh, glob!
- Ymmom!
Somebody!
[ bus clanks ]
Sorry.
| was hoping it wouldn't come
to this --
my "last resort" poshe,
obtained from a mad yogi
in the mystery mountains.
It's time to find out
what it does.
Ba-bam!
Nice and slow.
Ooh, gent--
oh!
[ breathing heavily ]
[ gasps ]
[ laughs ]
Oh, I'm flying!
Yoink.
Take my head away
from here, baby!
[gulps]
- No!
- [ all screaming ]
Maybe this is
a test from destiny, guys!
If we all just surrender
to these events,
the answer
will reveal itself.
[ inhales deeply ]
ERELAA!
Whoa.
] Wha?
ey, it's Giuseppe!
Giuseppe, how have
you done this?
ALL:
Whoa.
What was he?
| don't know,
Abracadaniel,
but | think he was
trying to show us something --
something new.
ALL:
Sploo!
Jicka haka boogy noona
hubba gubba --
secret wizard
handshake!
Later, Chinchizerd.
Bye, Berdzerd.
See you at the secret thing
tonight!
Loser.
ICE KING:
Giuseppe.
È Come along with me È
And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!