[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
[ smacks lips ]
[ inhales deeply, exhales ]
[ explosion ]
[ thud ]
That's the comet you're
supposed to follow.
Right. Right.
| knew that.
Hey, be careful, okay?
Hold on tight.
It's okay.
| won't ever let you go.
[ thinking ]
That's...true.
Wow. Already?
That was fast.
Yep. We're here.
It's time to
wake up now.
What? Now?
Yep.
Like, right now?
[ coughs ]
Ah. Where am 1?
What the heck?
Is that the comet?
And a little
farming village?
How long have
| been walking?
Man, two whole days --
at least.
Wow. | need some water.
No, wait --
Ah...geez.
Hmm.
Fields are looking
a little sparse.
Kind of runty.
Wonder if this village
even has any wat--
Oh, snap!
| see some!
[ panting ]
Excuse me, sir.
Could | have some water?
I've been
sleepwalking for days.
[ laughs ]
Awesome.
[ gargles ]
[ laughs ]
Heck yeah!
Thanks, little friend!
You just totally
saved my life.
No pun intended.
What's the matter?
Can't talk?
Oh. Or are you
guys Comet Boyz?
From up in there?
Listen, I'm no expert,
but I think y'all are
gonna need a
lot more corn.
And it's supposed to
stand straight-up-like.
Or maybe Comet Boyz
only need just, like,
a little bit of limp corn?
No, I'm a regular guy.
I-I'm just not supposed
to talk to strangers.
WOMAN: Lionel, what did | tell you
about talking to strangers?!
You get your butt
inside this instant!
[ echoing ]
Human boy!
What the...?
The Tree Spirit does
not permit freeloaders!
Either help fetch the escape-pod
engine or kindly move along.
Dad?
Wait! Wait!
What are you doing?
Don't come over herel
Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm.
Dad?
Ptoooooo00000000!
- MARTIN: Finn!
- FINN: Dad?
BOTH:
What the heck are you doing here?
What?
You were just
yelling at me.
No, no, that was
the Tree Spirit --
Commander of all trees,
bringer of hard times.
Dad.
You're not falling
for it, huh?
Well,
it was worth a try.
You know, those little
guys down there,
they'll do anything
for the Tree Spirit.
| got them fetching
parts to fix my escape pod
instead of
planting their fields.
Isn't that sweet?
Dad, your arm.
Oh, this?
[ laughs ]
Yeah.
When my ship crashed,
| got shot out of the window.
| knocked a kite
out of the air,
then caught my arm
in a woodpecker hole.
Whoa.
But it's cool,
you know.
Arms come and go.
It's family
that's important.
[ tink! ]
Speaking of arms, though,
| see you got yourself a
brand-spankin'-new one.
How about that?!
Oh. Yeah.
| got it from my
P.B. Dream sword.
Uh-huh. Neat.
Actually,
for a while there,
| thought if |
ever saw you again,
| was gonna tear
Yyour arm off.
Well, shoot.
Who could blame you?
Yeah.
But you definitely don't feel
that way anymore, right?
No. No.
It's --
it's okay now.
[ laughs ]
Great! Great.
How about a hug?
[ grunts ]
What the heck, Dad?!
Is everything
you say a lie?
No, no. 'Ôcourse not.
Well [scoffs] is there any
way | can tell the difference?
[ laughs ]
| hope not.
[ bell rings ]
Hot dang!
Hold that thought.
Those little guys are back with
the engine bulb for my pod.
Excuse me.
[ echoing ]
I am sending forth my holy emissary,
Martin Mertens,
and his regular son, Finn.
Don't forget to do
whatever Martin tells you!
Almost there.
Little further.
Uh-huh.
Keep it coming.
There you go.
A Jittle further.
And...stop.
Fantastic work, boys.
Absolutely fantastic.
[ all panting ]
Holy stonk, dad!
You're messing them all up!
This is why you're
lying to them?
So they'll mess
themselves up for you?
Wha?! No, no, no!
Look --
they love it. See?
Goochy goochy goo!
[ giggles ]
Goochy goochy!
They're helping a poor, old,
stranded man in need.
You like to help
people, don't you?
I-I'd do it myself if | could,
but I'm too strong to fit
through the service hatches.
Come on! Gimme a chance!
[ grunts ]
They're gonna fetch
me one last piece,
and you and | can
watch them do it.
Then I'll be out of your
hair by tomorrow morning.
Oh. Right.
Yeah, don't worry.
| know I'm cramping your style
down here, am | right, huh?
Uh...yeah.
Yeah, |-l guess.
MARTIN:
Sure | am!
Now let's go
fetch that piece.
It's really
warm down here.
[ gasps ]
Whoal!
Well, yeah, son.
That's just
the ship cooking.
One thing about this ship --
it cooks.
Should it be cooking?
Nah, but that's
just real life.
Okay, babies,
| need this piece.
It's a steering wheel.
It's in the steering room.
[ sighs ]
Last one in breaks
Tree Spirit's heart!
Wait! Wait!
W-w-wait!
You don't have to go in
there if you don't want to.
Nah, | think we want to.
Okay, | know, | know.
Listen, that's the last
piece of the pod, right?
Well, | promise I'll make it up
to the little boogers tonight.
[ laughs ]
Come here!
[ tribal music plays ]
Live it up, pals!
This is your night!
Hey, hey!
Careful with the finish.
That buggy's ready to blast.
[ gulping ]
Yo! Party animals!
Still hungry?
Mm-nn-mm.
Come on.
Tree Spirit says!
Scoop it till you poop it!
Let's get gross!
BOY:
Finn?
Oh. Sorry.
So...you guys want to
learn another one?
Okay, watch this.
[ snapping rhythmically ]
[ chuckles ]
Cute.
Uh, hey...
So, you guys really
believe in the Tree Spirit?
Eh, not really,
| guess.
We're kind of just
looking to help out.
Hmm.
Hey!
It's Finn with the grin!
Mind if | sit down?
[ grunts ]
[ laughs ]
Look at this!
You ever see
someone sit like this?
| guess not.
Hey, Martin?
Yeah?
Uh, I think | really need
some answers to stuff --
like where did | come
from or who's my mom?
[ laughs ]
Whoops.
[ chuckles ]
[ sighs ]
Okay, uh,
long story short --
you were born on a...
boat...I guess.
Like a...banana boat...
[ thunder crashes ]
...in the middle
of the ocean.
So all kinds of stuff
tried to eat you --
whales and fish...
squids.
Uh, there was a tiger...
[ tiger snarls ]
...and...
seaweeds.
The sea's weeds.
[ babbles ]
Your mom was...okay.
| don't know.
Talking about it
stresses me out.
Maybe later.
So, one day, | got called
on a dangerous mission --
no, like a dangerous
life choice,
two roads diverging in
the night and all that.
And | couldn't
bring you along.
| always planned to come
back for you, but | didn't.
That's...true.
The end!
Look out!
Everything is ruined.
Everyone is fat.
Aah!
[ gasps ]
Martin!
Again?
Oh, good morning,
sweetie!
Martin,
are you leaving?!
| absolutely gotta, kid.
| got pressures on me,
stuff you wouldn't understand.
But what about
the villagers?!
That ship looks like
it's gonna blow up!
Uhhhhh...maybe.
| don't know.
Maybe it won't blow up.
I've seen 100 things weirder
than a ship not blowing up.
Oh, Dad!
| need to
go shut it off!
Okay, okay, wait! Wait.
If you're gonna
turn it off,
you got to pull the heat-dump
toggle in the engine core.
It was too snug
for me to get to,
and those little guys
aren't strong enough.
Hmm.
Hey,
| could wait for you.
Maybe we could go
into space together.
Why didn't you tell me about the
heat dump in the first place?!
| don't...know.
Wink.
DEEEEEEL]
What the --
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
Heat dump!
[ grunting ]
Too...stuck!
Ohhhh, no.
This is new to me.
Mm...
[ sighs ]
[ growls ]
[ grunts ]
[ steam hissing ]
Man, you know
what's weird?
That wasn't even a comet
that crashed back there.
So, then, what was
that dream about?
/ don't get my brain.
Okay, when we get back
to the tree house,
let me do the talking.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!