[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
Commence dinner.
[ all munching ]
Dinner is concluded.
ALL:
Concluded.
Ooh!
Mm.
Lights out!
[ tearing ]
Huh?!
[ tearing continues ]
[ roar in distance ]
Uhhhhhhhhhh-
FEEEEEEEEEEEEEL
Bye!
[ both snoring ]
Better get
up here, Jake.
It's about to happen.
Coming!
Just got to get
this cocoa pipin'.
Your loss, man.
The dap of the heavens only
happens every 20 years.
[ twinkle! ]
Oh, man.
It's going down.
[ crash! ]
JAKE:
Okay. Let's watch some stars.
Hmm. You missed it.
It was honestly a
little disappointing.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, man, | think | hear
something weird over there with
my little doggy ears.
[ mid-tempo music playing ]
Phew!
Oh, my glob!
You are Killing,
Cinnamon Bun!
This routine
is locked up!
Oh!
Thank you, Princess.
You are also killing.
You mean
Flame Princess?
Naw, man.
What | heard didn't
sound like her.
Give me a
peek on there.
This is pretty
much just a tube.
Huh.
It's Lemongrab.
Uh, Lemongrab?!
What's he up to at
this time of night?
Uh...it looks like he's headed
for the Mountain of Matthew.
| hear beaucoup spookoo
legends about that place.
Beaucoup spookoo,
you say?
We should follow him.
Huh?
How come you care
where Lemongrab goes?
He could -- you know,
he could be messing with crazy
mystic power at that mountain.
It's like seeing a baby
playing with dynamite.
Plus, seeing Flame Princess
kind of messed me up.
Now | got to distract
myself with work.
Okay, okay.
| feel you.
Let's do some things.
There's his
lemon camel.
Lemongrease must
be inside already.
Whoa!
Come on, man!
Nope. Nope.
Nuh-unh.
Dang it!
Quit bustin' my buns!
You have no beeswax in
the Mountain of Matthew,
supple yellow dog.
But you,
plucky adolescent --
you have
way-cray beeswax.
[ groans ]
You gonna be
okay by yourself?
Yeah, man.
Okay.
Just gonna sit
down over he-e-e-e--
not even.
Dong it!
[ whimpers ]
Rocks.
Dripping water.
More rocks.
Oh, I'm
becoming stressed!
VOICE:
Continue forward.
Hmm?
To reach me,
you must choose correctly.
Aah!
BUBBLEGUM:
Come, Earl of Lemongrab!
Let us play
the game of catch.
| am eager to
relate to you.
Yes.
| desire this, as well.
Huh?
Thank youl!
Thank you all!
As your younger,
more relatable new ruler,
| shall endeavor
to undo all the
order imposed by
my predecessor!
[ all cheering ]
I-I unaccept!
No, Lemongrab!
You are unacceptable!
Prepare to be served in a
pitcher by a little child!
What a wondrous time
you've experienced,
and tomorrow there will
be more adventures to be
had for little
Lemonsweets.
Ooh, wave farewell!
What a lucky little boy
you are to live so gaily.
Lemonsweets.
Choose.
Ohh!
BUBBLEGUM:
Lemongrab!
ALL:
We understand your styles.
We are of
the same styles.
[ laughs ]
[ playing upbeat melody ]
CINACEEEEEEEEE ]
No!
It is my love
that he prefers!
He is spiteful
of your love!
Don't hurt him!
(©lalalalalalalalalalal!
[ breathing heavily ]
What?
[ grunts ]
No!
[ both shouting indistinctly ]
[ grunts ]
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
(©lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalal!
I'm inside youl!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[ grunts ]
Mnh. Sticky.
[ groans ]
Gross!
Aww!
What is this?
Aaaah! Why?!
Ohh! Shoosh!
[ grunting ]
Okay.
[ groaning ]
Whoa! Ohh! Whoa!
[ grunts ]
Whoa! Whoal!
Oh, whoa! Gross!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoal!
[ gasps ]
Blackness all over!
Rolling in grease!
You want to
humiliate me?!
Whoop!
[ grunts ]
Taste the grease,
Lemongrab.
Okay.
It's Lemony.
Look up, man.
[ grunts ]
P CEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEERL
| am grease?!
Lemongrab,
where you at?!
Uh, cool.
To reach me,
you must choose correctly.
Who's that --
Matthew?
Whuh-oh!
Yo, get up, C.B.!
This routine's got to be
high-level outside the box!
Hey, Finn, quick --
Be me, bro!
Oh, yeah!
It's time, BMO!
What is it?
| can't smell.
Finn cakes, boy!
Yummy! Ooh.
Yo. Dang.
Finn cakes.
That's not fair.
Okay.
Goodbye, Lemongrease.
Goodbye, where?
Goodbye from my grease
body into the blackness,
where only my
pure essence can go!
Up-up, BMO.
Finn always gets
the first Finn cake.
Yo, give me a break.
LEMONGRAB:
Pure essence!
Eject!
[ squish! ]
Blorg! Bleject!
Lemongrab!
Huh?
Whoo!
Later, spirit bro.
[ grunts ]
Huh?
What the heck
am | running on?
Oh, whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Cool.
[ chuckles ]
[ laughs ]
Lemongrab,
you okay?!
Finn,
don't mess me up.
Hi, Finn.
You're Matthew, huh?
[ shing! ]
Your rep
precedes you, bro.
"Proceeds"?
What kind of rep?
Some stuff Jake said that
| interpreted as negative.
Well, ask yourself
if that feels right.
What do you say, guy?
The meat bodies who've
journeyed to this mountain
have distilled themselves to
their original source materials
and now exist in oneness.
OnenessÓ?
That's you, bro?
| keep adding to myself until
the second age of terror,
when | will emerge in my final
form and restore the world.
That's why you're
here, L.G. --
to merge with Matthew?
It is one option --
to know the ecstasy
of my ego death.
Oh.
Well, nice knowing you?
| mean,
| know you got issues.
But you're, uh --
| know.
Are you sure, though?
Here's my other option.
You see these?
Lemonjons?
Uh-oh.
These lemonjons are me, and |
wonder if they can destroy you.
Ooh, boy.
Lemongrab,
hold up!
If you are the head that
blooms atop the ziggurat,
then the stairs that lead
to you must be infinite!
Careful with
those metaphors, bro!
Infinite stairs are
unacceptable!
[ gulps, gasps ]
Ohh.
I CEEEEEEEEEEEE L
Ooh! Whoal!
Whoa! Geez!
[ all groaning ]
Oh, no, bro!
Heck, no, bro!
CEEEEEEEEEEE
Yo!
Smash that Lemongrab!
[ all shouting indistinctly ]
Try it, grease!
[ shouting continues ]
Yes! Pow!
Yeah! | got you, bro!
Why are you being so opaque
about not letting me in there?
Well, get out
a pen and paper
and I'll school
you on this biz.
[ boom!]
Gol' ding!
Dude, | was gonna
ask him to move.
Oh.
Yo, class,
hold on.
Uh...
[ all moaning ]
I'm done! Let's go!
Okay. Here we are.
Bye!
CEEEEEEEEEE L]
[ munching ]
[ spits ]
[ splat! ]
Yo, yo!
It's grease!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!