[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human È
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
BMO, when is something going
to happen?
Shh. Just watch.
It happens once a month.
| promise.
[ yawns ]
This is it!
Ooooh!
But where does it go?
That's none of our business.
ANNOUNCER:
Tickets! Get your tickets here!
See the world's greatest
tiny circus!
Witness the amazing
wood-eating termite!
The mighty strong-ant!
You're late, Blue Nose!
Get into makeup!
[ audience "oohs" and "aahs" ]
[ audience gasps, applause ]
[ drum roll ]
[ audience gasps ]
[ cheers and applause ]
[ soft music plays ]
[ music continues ]
[ sad music plays ]
[ laughing ]
[ audience booing, hissing ]
[ crying ]
Too much artsy,
not enough fartsy.
We talked about this, clown!
[ chuckles nervously ]
Wasn't that something?
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
you're perfectly safe.
But at this time,
I'd like to ask anyone
with a medical condition
to please leave
the premises at once.
What you're about to witness
with your own eyes
may shock and astound you
to your very core.
Tonight, | give you the wildest,
most dangerous beast
anywhere in captivity!
The horrible,
the stupendous...
Goralina!
[ audience gasps ]
[ whip cracks ]
[ growls ]
[ whip cracking ]
[ roars ]
[ audience gasps ]
[ growls ]
[ whip cracking ]
[ laughing ]
Attagirl!
[ body thuds ]
[ audience screaming ]
Don't worry, junior.
It's all part of the act.
[ screaming continues ]
[ slow music plays ]
[ coin clanking ]
[ knock on door ]
Blue Nose!
Boy, am | glad to see you.
Come in, come in!
Sit down.
You did good out there tonight
with the belly-dancing
routine.
Real good.
Aw, don't give me that look.
| know we said we were going
to let the chipmunk go
at the end of last season,
but Goralina is our big draw.
You understand that.
We're barely breaking even
here.
What do you want from me?!
Look, there's another show
in an hour.
You come up with an act
that can rival Goralina,
then we can talk.
But look what she got us
last night --
three whole pennies.
Think you can make me
this kind of cash?
You do that, | won't need
the chipmunk anymore.
I'll let her go,
just like | promised.
But you're gonna have to lose
the fancy-schmancy stuff
and give the people
what they want!
Get it?!
[ door closes ]
[ mid-tempo music plays ]
[ music stops ]
[ gear cranking ]
[ sad music plays ]
[ whoopee cushion deflates ]
[ laughter ]
The old Blue Nose magic.
Aren't you glad we came back
for the second show?
[ sad music continues ]
[ record needle scratching ]
[ laughter ]
[ cheers and applause ]
Oho! You were great, kid!
That's what I'm talking about.
With you and the chipmunk
in the show,
we're gonna have a real
1, 2 punch!
Hey...
| know what | said, but | want
to see how many boxcars
this gravy train has on it.
[ chains rattling ]
Look at her.
It's like looking at a big,
sad dollar sign.
[ gasps ]
Yipe!
[ laughter, cheers, applause ]
Whoa-ho!
[ laughing ]
Oh!
[ laughter continues ]
[ growls ]
[ audience gasps ]
[ grunts ]
That's right.
Lift with your legs first,
then put your back into it.
There he is.
Gotchal
Thought you could
skip out, eh?
And start your own circus!
Yeah, you!
You and your corny clown hat!
Hey, he's smiling!
What's so funny?
- You rat!
- You creep!
What's the big joke?
[ audience gasps, murmurs ]
[ horse whinnies ]
[ sniffs ]
[ both laugh ]
Ha ha! Neat!
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
FINN:
This party is so crazy!