[ mouse squeaks ]
[ penguins wenk ]
[ all cheering ]
[ screeches ]
D> Adventure Time )
È Come on, grab your friends È
È We'll go to very distant lands J
È With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
D The fun will never end >
D It's Adventure Time È
What the --
Why's it so
purple outsi--
[ explosion ]
What?
It's too
smoky to see.
Oh!
Something's peeking.
Someone's jacking
your spaceship!
That /s my ship!
But it looks like
it's been modded out.
That much engine power --
it'll break through
the atmosphere
before | can do anything
to stop it.
Finn and Jake!
Yeah! Get that guy!
BOTH:
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[ squeaking ]
BOTH:
CEEEEEEEEEE L]
[ clank ]
Oof!
My thorn.
| think
we should go inside.
Oofl
[ clank ]
[ hatch creaks ]
Gunther!
What are you doing?!
What am | doing?
A fog shrouds my true intent
even from myself.
There!
The catalyst comet.
It all becomes clear.
| am more than Gunther.
Like a mighty chrysalis
pushing out of a damp cocoon,
| emerge!
[ creaking ]
Jake! You okay?
Yeah, man.
Just don't croak out here.
Hey, man,
look at Gunther.
Behold!
| am Orgalorg!
Whoa.
That's pretty.
Looks good, right?
Hey, where's Glob?
| don't know.
Um, he exploded in space.
Yeah, thought so.
Man,
are you still Gunther?
'Ôcause you seem like
you're not.
I'm Orgalorg.
Well, what the heck
are you doing, Orgalorg?
It was just
time to come out again.
Glob K.O.-ing himself,
the arrival
of the catalyst comet,
and a ship to carry me
out of this planet's gravity --
These are doorways
the universe presented to me.
Oh, | know about
open-door philosophy.
What's that? You just
say yes to stuff all the time?
Pretty much.
That seems all right.
It's all yours,
if you're
willing to take it.
Destroy worlds,
crush anyone blocking the door.
Feel their bones crumple
and their goo spill out.
| don't like that
at all.
He made it ugly.
You can't stop me.
I'm Orgalorg.
I'm pretty sure
| can take you, bro.
Not after | absorb the power
and knowledge of that comet.
Absorb a triple salchow
to your kneecaps.
Oofl
BOTH:
Whoa!
- Grab my hand!
- Okay.
[ grunts ]
Shoot.
Hey,
stop drifting!
I'm not trying to!
Ooh! Maybe | can use
jet propulsion.
[ straining ]
[ farts ]
Oh, no, | can't breathe.
Jake, no!
Don't worry, man!
I'm working out a plan!
Freaking bing bong!
Jake's gonna fulfill
his croak dream after all.
And that dirty umbrella
is gonna enslave the universe.
[ grunts ]
Cram -- come on.
This is gonna take forever.
Man,
I'm gonna croak out here,
NCERIE)
in the hands of a child.
[ breathing heavily ]
[ inhales deeply ]
[ exhales deeply ]
Okay, Finn.
Time to make an appeal
to greater forces.
> Everything's
falling into place È
2 I'm right
where | should be È
D The tides of life
all led me here È
È And that's why
I'm not scared È
2 | know the answer will appear,
ple-e-e-ease J
MARTIN:
Hey, Spaceman.
Wha-- Dad?!
[ laughs ]
This is so crazy, Finn.
What are you doing
out here?
Floating to my grave!
Hurry up and save me!
Can't, buddy.
This baby does what it wants.
Are you kidding me?!
No, for real.
Look.
Hey. [ whistles ]
Get that guy there!
See?
I'm just flying random-style.
It's not random!
| merged my intention
with the universe.
You what?
Oh! Wait.
| have an idea.
Really?
Here --
grab on this.
No, it's cool.
You got gloves on.
Oh, yeah.
[ grunts ]
You all right?
[ sighs ] Yeah.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks, Universe.
Come again?
Oh! We got to save Jake!
He's out there
choking on gas!
Like | said, | got
no control over this beast.
We're on
a journey into mystery,
unless | figure out
what this bozo responds to.
It's kind of fun, right?
See, there's no reason
or purpose or what you said --
uh, universal intention.
Look around, Finn.
Empty crud.
So empty.
| don't know.
There's some stars and stuff.
You're squeezed so tight,
your bottom's gonna fall out.
Put the phone down.
- "Put the phone down"?
- Yeah --
Whoa!
What's going on, huh?
Look!
The light of the comet.
Ahh.
That's pretty neat.
This moth
is so bananas, man.
"Bananas, man."
Uh-oh. What's that?
Almost there.
That dude's gonna absorb
the comet's mystical power
and crush everybody.
Who the heck
raises guys like that?
You think he had
neglectful parents, like you?
Or would he have always
been a no-good Orgalorg?
Oh, gob slops!
Not Orgalorg!
You -- you --
you know him?
Yeah!
What do you think --
I'm a dumb brick?
| don't know Orgalorg?
[ laughing ]
Oh, yeah.
Snaps!
He ate the comet!
| got to stop him.
It's too late, buddy.
It's out of our hands.
Skronk that!
I'm gonna use these hands
to sock him in the chops!
In the chops!
[ screams ]
Hey! Dinglord!
In the name of...
the Universe, stop that!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[ cracking ]
Grass sword.
Raaa!
Huh?
Y ah-ta-ta-ta-ta!l
Whoa.
| didn't open this door.
Cool.
Finn,
do you remember?
Oh.
Yeah, I-| think so.
A long time ago,
| was you, sort of.
And | crashed on Earth and
became a butterfly or some biz.
And | guess it was
just some random absurd thing,
just a joke I've been
playing out for centuries.
Who's creating the joke?
Are you?
And if so,
then are you my creator?
Uh, maybe.
| don't know.
Probably not.
Probably not,
but who knows?
I've been around forever
and experienced
so much impossible junk.
I've embodied
all that is good and evil.
And now we're here.
It's unprecedented.
And | give you
a choice --
come with me
to the end and the beginning
or struggle here awhile
like a beautiful autumn leaf.
- [ bell ringing ]
- What's that bell sound?
Cool, man.
This is your crisis.
As you stand
on the edge of freedom
from love...
hate...
friendship...
isolation...
jealousy...
secrets...
violence...
video games...
ice-cream walffles...
sadness...
madness...
power...
honor...
loyalty...
saucy...
mothers...
fathers...
scoundrels.
How long
are you gonna list stuff?
It's a long list.
You're telling me
to abandon all this stuff,
but you're not really
making it sound bad.
It's notbad.
I'm just giving you the choice
of a new mode of existence.
| feel like | put a lot of work
into this meat reality.
I'd like
to see it through.
Fair enough.
Hey, how about
/get a new mode?
Are you seriously trying
to bail out again?/
What?
This deal sounds pretty good.
[ sighs ] Dad.
Uh-oh.
| know that look.
When you fled the scene
like a ding-dong-ditcher
in the night --
Listen, Finn.
No answer | give you
will be satisfying.
Besides,
it was like 40 years ago.
I'm 16!
| don't have a star
to revolve around to track time.
Well, why do you
always run from everything?
You burn enough bridges,
the only direction to move
is forward.
Hm.
Well, there ain't
no changing you, | guess.
Well, I'm glad we finally
understand each other.
Start the engine,
comet boy!
Prepare
to discorporate.
[ echoing ]
Goodbye, son!
Bye, Dad.
| should have asked
for a lift home.
Unh!
Jake!
| thought | had lost...
You.
Noooooo!
- You okay, Finn?
- What?!
Jake! Banana Man?!
How?
| was just
floating around,
and | drifted
into B-Man's flight path.
Pretty random, right?
I-i-it wasn't random.
/did it.
Let's get
the jazz out of here.
Nooooo!
[ chirps ]
PEPPERMINT BUTLER:
There we go. See?
Problem
took care of itself.
You think Finn and Jake
are all right?
I'd say
it's about a 50/50 chance.
That's pretty much
everything in life, isn't it?
Yeah.
Whoa! What's that?!
Hey, PB.
We took care of it.
[ chirps ]
Good job, guys.
Mm, I'm gonna croak
out here.
È Come along with me È
2 And the butterflies and bees
È We can wander through the forest JÈ
2 And do so as we please È
È Come along with me È
D To a cliff under a tree È
This party is so crazy!