(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
(QUACKS)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
(VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYS)
Beemo, I've been playing
this 72 hours straight.
Can I please save after this battle?
No, it takes up too much brain space.
I'm out of candles. Huh?
Man, if Finn were here,
we'd be doing this in shifts.
Oh, well, let's keep grinding.
I cannot talk and run this game
at the same time.
No!
Well, I guess that means I'm free.
I live again!
My name is Jake, and love my life
Kissin' on lady 'cause
she's basically my wife
Fixin' up Neptr 'cause he fell from a tree
Catchin' up with Maja and Aptwe
Maja's in a coma, and she might not wake up
I'm glad you got a friend now
even though that's messed up
Take T. V. To the market to get him into fruits
Take a little nappy in my blanket cocoon
Wake up really early just to cook
for my friends
Later in the field at night
I thought I saw death
Made myself a boat, and I sailed with a whale
Took T. V. To the market so he could try kale
And some other stuff
Ah!
Nice song, Jake.
What a crazy two weeks.
I think I'm ready to hole up
and go round two on Age of Grinders.
But where's Finn?
I need him on this adventure.
Uh, well...
Hold on. What?
If you don't know, I'm not sure
it's my business to tell you.
Don't you dare, Shelby!
Give up that greasy gossip!
Word on the street is,
Finn's been hangin' with a new lady.
Who the honk is it?
- I don't...
- Muscle Princess. It's perfect.
- Me-Mow, from the future!
- (GASPS)
- Nobody knows.
Finn's been keeping this on the super DL.
- Why?
- He's just trying to be careful this time.
Oh, yeah, I get it.
But, I still got to know who this girl is.
Okay, just don't blow up his spot.
JAKE: T won't!
Ooh! Ohhh!
- Hey, Jake.
- Oh, hey, Science Cat.
Where's Sword Shark?
He died of old age.
Hey, are you gonna find out
who Finn's girlfriend is?
Who told you that?
Word gets around, man.
Not to me, apparently.
Let me know the dirt when you find out.
I won'tl!
(SNIFFING)
(FLUTE PLAYING)
Huh? What's that?
Sounds like a flute
coming from above the canopy.
(FLUTE CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
Huntress Wizard!
- Stop.
- (PLAYING STOPS)
This isn't working, Finn.
- Dude.
- (SCREAMS)
Oh, hi, Jake. What are you doing here?
I wanted to check out your new lady friend,
but I guess she just dumped you
like a diaper in the dirt, bro.
(CRYING) I'm sorry, man.
I want you to have a healthy relationship
with someone cool.
That's so sweet, Jake. I love you, man.
Me, too, man.
Okay. I'm okay.
But, dude, me and Huntress Wizard
weren't together.
We're just trying to conjure up
the Spirit of the Forest with my flute spell.
What the blood are you talking about?
It went down like this.
I was just minding my own business
in my new alone place I've been
hanging out at.
(GURGLING)
(FLUTE PLAYING)
(BLOWING RASPBERRY)
- Hello.
- How are you playing like that?
I don't know. I'm just making stuff up.
Something in your notes has the quality
of a powerful evocation spell.
What spirit guides your hands?
Tell me, or I'll put this up your nose.
First off, I'm a great fighter.
And I'm especially agile
when I'm nude, so good luck.
Second, my flute improv ain't no secret.
I let my grass hand do whatever it wants,
which is usually sort of shreddy and busy.
Let me see that hand.
You're what I've been looking for.
Lookin' for a dope boyfriend.
No, man,
she thinks my grass arm flute playing
could summon the Spirit of the Forest.
I've been playing different songs for two
weeks, though, and he hasn't shown up yet.
Who's that, her ex-boyfriend?
Uh, I guess they used to hang out
but maybe in some kind
of mentor-student capacity.
So my theory holds.
You can still make this happen.
Yeah, I really want to help
her summon this dude.
Finn, that's not why you're here.
That's why I'm here.
Come on, let's make some magic happen.
Yeah, my magic flute spell.
(GROANS)
- HUNTRESS WIZARD: Finn.
- (BOTH SCREAM)
I had an idea.
Hi.
I think the problem is your flute.
We should make you a better
one from a magical tusk.
Like the tusk of the legendary Thunder Boar
that lives in these woods.
I'm down for whatever if it helps.
I'm also here.
Hey, what's up?
It's late. Why don't you guys
crash at my place tonight?
We'll start the hunt first thing in the morning.
Ha-ha! I'm like your sleepover chaperone.
- Grow up.
- You grow up, you teen!
So, yeah, here's the place.
We got some nice soft dirt right over here.
Pantry, in case you want a snack, bathroom.
I got a console if you get bored,
but it was a gift,
so I haven't really set it up yet.
Night, boys.
(SNORES)
JAKE: Dude, I think I figured it out.
You can't summon the Spirit of the Forest
‘cause you ain't playing that flute for him.
You got a crush on HW.
HW's just training me to live
an ascetic life like her.
Mmm, okay, I buy that for like zero seconds.
Before we hunt the Thunder Boar,
you should drink from this enchanted spring.
It might give you crazy dreams,
but when you wake up, you'll be immune
to the Boar's electrical attacks.
Let's roll those dice. (GULPING)
Hey, dude, are you sure you want to do that?
Mm-hmm. Blah!
I've had plenty of weird dreams... Okay!
That was fast. (CHIRPS)
Welcome. I am the Spirit of the Forest.
Wow, dude, we've been trying
to summon you for weeks.
And why do you seek me?
I don't, personally,
but Huntress Wizard really wants
to talk to you, man.
Did you know that a wolf's eyes
are on the front of its head?
But, yeah, didn't you guys used to hang?
Most predatory species are like that.
This little buddy doesn't even know I'm here.
Fella, I don't want to have
a science talk right now.
Huntress Wizard only sees straight ahead.
Eyes on the prize.
Now, why did you really need to see me?
Oh, yeah!
Can you make me immune to electricity?
- Here.
- Whoa.
Now plunge that into your heart.
And this'll give me immunity to electricity?
I'll do it. To help Huntress Wizard.
(YELLS)
How long was I out?
Seven long, harrowing seconds.
Hold still.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- FINN: Yeah, feels fine.
- Great.
Now we can hunt down the Thunder Boar.
Oh, yeah, the Boar.
Try to stay focused.
Magic dog, what do you smell?
(SNIFFS)
Mostly, Finn but also some
kind of giant wild pig.
There!
(GRUNTS)
(SQUEALING)
Jake's joking. I smell fine.
(GRUNTS)
(SNICKERING)
Hey!
Good work.
You just wanted a tusk?
- You could have asked!
- Oh.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(FLUTE PLAYING)
You can stop.
He is not coming.
He's gone for good, and I should just deal.
Maybe if I played it a little jazzier,
like, all syncopated?
Hey! Why don't you two try playing together?
Use that chemistry to guide the music.
Yeah, just get in there. Cozy up.
I guess we've tried everything else.
(FLUTES PLAYING)
Wow!
What?
Who summons me with the sweet song
of longing?
Oh, hey-oh. Can you see me now?
- Yes.
- SPIRIT: How's it been going?
I've been talking to a lot of twigs.
- Where have you been, dude?
- I've been right here.
But the forces that drew us close
became obscured
as you drifted into the
lifestyles of magic city livin'.
Attracting forces come and go.
It's the way of the world.
I still can't tell if you guys dated.
But I'm ready to come back now.
- Are you, though?
- That's what I'm saying.
Finn, who was your flute spell for?
Um...
I was playing my flute for you the whole time,
but I knew you had a thing with this dude,
and he seems cool,
so I was just gonna keep playing
this flute song
about my secret feelings until my flute broke.
I, uh, I worry that hard meat don't get eat.
That is to say,
if I ever find what I'm looking for,
I'll become soft and I'll cease
to matter in this world.
What?
Fear of softness is what drove me
to the mad and sad world of wizarding.
- And, Finn...
- Yeah? What?
(GASPS)
My flute spell was for you, too.
You're an exceptional beast,
and you have great hair.
But exceptional beasts
like us cannot fall in love.
That is the secret of ordinary people.
Uh, that's real dumb.
I agree.
Wait, you agree with me or her?
Take it easy, Huntress Wizard.
FINN: Man, I can't believe all you can do
is upgrade your armor in this game.
It's all about patience
and treating each grueling,
repetitive battle as if it were your first.
FINN: Oh, snap!
Finally!
BOTH: Whoo!
BOTH: Blah!
What a bad and boring game.
It was just what I needed.
I'm sorry it didn't work out
with Huntress Wizard.
She just needs time to miss how cool you are.
Attracting forces come and go, man.
(SINGLE NOTE PLAYS)
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!