(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
with Jake the dog and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
JAKE: (PANTING) Remember last time
we were out this way?
It was right after you messed things
all up with Flame Princess.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, that sucked.
But then we found
the Dungeon Train, remember?
FINN: That was awesome.
JAKE: No. It wasn't.
Sure it was. Anyway, Flambo's brother's map
says the weird cave should be,
like, right over...
Ah! It's right here.
(CHUCKLES) Come on, Jake.
Okay, hold on,
let me get out my sidewalk chalk.
I want to write all over the walls in there.
(ECHOING) What?
You can't use that stuff in here.
This is like an ancient, sacred temple.
Oh, well, now, that's just great.
You don't put traps in the foyer!
The foyer is a safe space.
Man, not even Jake could smash
through this mess.
But maybe there's a back door or something.
Uh-oh! Options.
Better leave a little trail in case I get lost.
Bread-crumb style. (CHUCKLES)
Plus, for if Jake gets in
and tries to track me down.
Too bad I don't still have that sidewalk...
Ow! (CRASHING)
(GROANS)
Okay, well, scratch that.
Now I really hope there's another way out.
Hall of Egress.
Egress. Egress.
What's "egress" mean?
"Exit."
Egress means exit.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SHUDDERS)
Okay.
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Great. What am I supposed to do now?
(INHALES DEEPLY AND SIGHS)
Wait.
Hey. Hey, I just smashed you.
Ah!
Magic door. Okay.
Right. But if I...
Ah?
Well done, Finn. You solved the magic door.
That ought to have done it. And...
Oh.
I guess this door's just too tricky for me.
Guess I better give up, right?
Wrong. Wrong!
Let's try that again.
Hmm.
It's smooth like metal.
Floor's smooth too.
Oh! What have we here?
An errant thread!
(CHUCKLES)
It must lead back out.
Bread-crumb... Ooh!
Trap door?
(GRUNTS) Yow!
Spike trap.
Better head back and regroup.
Fiendish.
Anyway. Don't let's do that again.
And right then straight.
And... Hey, now. Hold the phone.
There should be a left turn here.
Letters?
|IEII...
IIGII. ..
Egress! It spells "egress."
(CHUCKLES) This way!
And here's another one. And another.
(CHUCKLES)
- (TRAP DOOR OPENS)
- Whoa!
Oow!
Okay.
So, every map I make is wrong.
All the exit signs led to traps.
Plus the braille, the hieroglyphics,
and the tape recorder message too.
It's almost like the maze is
trying to tell me something.
Something confusing. Whatever!
Who needs you anyway, with your
stupid signs and messages?
I'm Finn Mertens, ya heard?
And I don't need no nothing!
Watch me. (INHALES DEEPLY)
(BABBLES)
(BABBLING SLOWLY)
(PANTING)
JAKE: Finn?
Finn!
Jake! (LAUGHS) Jake, I'm coming!
Finn? Where are ya, buddy?
(GRUNTS) Jake!
(SUCKING TEETH)
That's a little disappointing. Still, though.
I'm in the homestretch here.
(BABBLES)
(GRUNTS) Jake!
Finn! Hey, there you are.
Yeah. Sorry to pop up,
then disappear again like that.
Again? You just got here, son.
I did? Shoot, man.
This cave has got me straight
scrambled up and down.
What cave?
What? Oh. Uh-oh.
- FINN: Well?
- Well, I followed your map,
but there's just a bunch of grass here.
What? Let me see!
Dang it. (BABBLES)
So, yeah. Everything I did to try
to make sense of the maze
or to play it safe totally backfired.
But when I got fed up,
and started just charging in willy-nilly,
I was able to get to the end and find you.
JAKE: And then the whole thing disappeared.
But I wonder how come I don't
remember any of it.
I don't know.
I'm just hoping, maybe if I sleep it off,
maybe I'll be better in the morning.
Okay, well... Good night, buddy.
Thanks, Jake. Good night.
BEEMO: Are you awake?
Yes.
Are you gonna open your eyes now?
Maybe.
Are you scared?
- No.
- Then do it.
(GULPS) On three.
BOTH: One, two,
three!
(SCREAMS)
JAKE: So, been almost a month now.
What do ya think?
You wanna try opening 'em?
It's a beautiful day.
Plus, I need someone
to tell me if this hat looks cool.
Man, I told you...
If I open 'em now, it'll just be the same.
I got to wait till something's different.
Yeah. That makes sense, I guess.
So, um, I got you a little something.
- A little present.
- Wow, thanks, man!
You're really gonna thank me.
- Gotcha!
- No!
FINN: Yeah, you've done it, like, 30 times now.
Ahhh! Ahhh!
It's like programmed
into your DNA or something.
(CHUCKLES) Well, shoot, man.
If I wanna do it that bad,
it must be kinda right, right?
- (SIGHS)
- Look at it from where I'm sitting.
All this funky pizzazz that only you can see,
that's like the literal
definition of a hallucination.
Either all that stuff is a dream,
or like, I'm a dream.
And I ain't no dream, ya heard?
Yeah, I know. I heard.
It's just that, well...
- Hyah! Open up!
- (SCREAMS)
(SIGHS)
Oh, Jake.
I know you mean well,
but I guess I got to see this
one through on my own.
(SIGHS) I'll see you around, buddy.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Huh?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SLURPING)
Huh? What the...
(GASPS)
How long has this been going on?
CREYS)
Someone's apt to track me down,
bread-crumb style.
E.g. Jake.
Can't let him catch me.
No more threads to follow.
No more egress.
(GRUNTING)
(SNORING)
(GNAWING)
(SPITS)
Mmm. It's cool in here.
Ain't nothing wrong with that.
Deep too. That's good.
Ain't nobody gonna be looking for me down...
Ugh!
(GASPS)
Egress! Egress! Egress! Egress!
BEEMO: Something's different.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
GIRL: Hurry, Finn.
At the seashell's center lies
the cornucopia's smallest door.
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
That must have been some cave!
(LAUGHS) No comment!
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!