(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
(QUACKS)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
BOTH: Calling all Curlys!
(BEEPING)
- Curly! Curly!
- Curly!
Called!
- Yeah!
- All right!
One more, and we'll have called all the Curlys!
I know!
- Curly! Curly!
ANNOUNCER: We interrupt this video game
for a special news flash!
- No!
Ahh! Save game, save game!
It's okay, Beemo.
What's the emergency?
Hold, please.
ANNOUNCER: This just in.
President Porpoise is missing!
(GASPS)
Who's President Porpoise?
Is he real?
He's real, and he's missing!
Mmm...
He is real! We video chat sometimes.
We need to find him before
they give the oath of office
to Vice President Blowfish.
BEEMO: That creep!
Okay, let's go find President Porpoise.
I guess we should ask Banana Man
if we can borrow his submarine.
- BANANA MAN: No problemo!
- (BOTH SCREAM)
Anything to help the friend of my friend.
Uh... What are ya doing
behind our couch, neighbor?
Sometimes I get Ionely
and need to hear the sound
of other people talking.
We should let it slide so we can use his sub.
But only if I can go with you guys.
Nobody steers the S.S. Inquisitive but me!
Then it's the three of us!
Four!
(ALL LAUGH)
- ICE KING: Five!
- (ALL SCREAM)
(CHUCKLES)
Uh... Anybody else?
Okay, let's go!
As soon as I finish loading
these supplies, we can ship out.
Finn, you're my first mate.
Nice.
Jake, you're my morale officer.
You keep our spirits up
while the sub is down.
Dude, we're both big-shot officers!
What's my job, Finn?
You have the most important
job of all, Beemo...
To distract Ice King until we get away.
That decision was good for morale!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SUBMARINE POWERS ON)
Aah!
Hey! You forgot me and the cabin boy here!
Hey!
Shh! We are on the submarine.
What? No, we're not!
Yes, see?
(MIMICS BEEPING NOISES AND WHIRRING)
Beep, beep, beep...
Think we'll see any beautiful mermaids?
Get serious, Lieutenant!
We're in dangerous waters!
Aye-aye, sirl
I'm locking in the coordinates
for the last-known whereabouts
of President Porpoise.
Aye-aye, sirl
Hey, Jake, do you think I'm doing a good job,
like, as a first mate or whatever?
Yeah, man, you're doing great...
Considering we're all gonna die.
- Wait, what?
- We're all gonna die.
You're supposed to be keepin'
our spirits up, remember?
Yeah, but it's so cramped in here.
Ooh! BRB!
- Jake?
- Yeah, man, I'm fine.
- I just had to shrink down a little!
- What?
Look at all this room I have!
Ha, cha-cha-cha... Whoa! (SCREAMS)
- Jake!
- (SCREAMS)
I'm good!
- What?
- BANANA MAN: Hey, Finn?
Can you come help me
calibrate the windshield wiper fluid valve?
Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
Ahhh!
I'm good!
(LAUGHS) What?
Look at how small I am.
(LAUGHS)
When did you get so claustrophobic?
It's a middle-age thing, I think.
Okay, I guess I can calibrate it by myself.
(CHUCKLES) Me too, huh, guys?
(CHUCKLES) You see that?
(CLAMORING)
Will my colleague from
the Great Kelp Forest yield?
Thank you.
The President is missing.
Yes, we all agree.
And while he is missing,
Vice President Blowfish is acting president.
Again, yes, agree.
But to swear in a new president
while the current one is missing?
Do not agree!
This is an outrage, Secretary Octopus!
Undersea law dictates that
when the clock strikes 5:00,
I become President!
You're not allowed to puff out
in the court of food!
(CRASH)
Attention, Fish Parliament!
We're here to help!
Who and what are you?
Jake, get up here!
Stuck again!
My brother video chats sometimes
with the President.
I'm a good friend of President Porpoise!
(ALL MURMURING)
(SIGHS)
Hi. Oh!
(SIGHS) Aw.
Boy, when I first signed up for this adventure,
I just wanted to see pretty mermaids.
But now I realize it's all about the camaraderie
of my fellow sailors, you know?
I do know. I had a feeling you'd...
Hmm. I don't like the look of this.
Everything okay, sir?
No. We are running out of air.
- (GASPS)
- We need to surface immediately.
But if we show ourselves now,
the enemy will be right on top of us!
Shh!
(MURMURING)
FINN: Please, just give us a chance!
(GRUNTS) Just make me president!
Don't trust these filthy surface boys!
I guess it is kind of weird
that you guys just showed up
and you're not even fish.
We're mammals, just like President Porpoise!
Yeah, man! Nerves and fur.
Oh, that's a good point!
Uh, wait!
I demand this be put to a vote!
Wow, this is intense!
Okay, everyone who thinks
these guys should just go away,
raise your fins or claws or whatever.
Two, four, five...
And with Governor Anglerfish, that's seven.
Oh, eight? Wow. All right, eight.
And everyone who wants them to stay
and help find the President?
No one?
Oh, wait. Representative Sybil.
(GASPS)
Well, if that's everyone,
then the final vote is...
Wait! I haven't voted yet.
Ahh...
Ah! There! Now it's nine to eight!
SECRETARY OCTOPUS: The yeas have it.
Finn and Jake, you have
20 minutes to find the President!
They must give a 20-minute presentation first!
We're on to you, Blowfish!
(PANTING)
Stay collected, Lieutenant!
We'll get you home to the
children you speak of so fondly!
It's no good. My guns are barkin'.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Pull yourself together, Lieutenant!
Slap, slap! I bring my boys home!
(GRUNTING)
Careful, I bruise easily.
FINN: You're acting highly sus,
VP Blowfish!
I suspect you may have had a hand
- in Prez Porp's disappearance!
- (ALL GASP)
VP BLOWFISH: You be quiet!
You're not right!
Okay, guys! I'm going to go look for clues!
Something about this
whole situation smells fishy!
Ah! Ha-ha!
Whoa!
(MURMURING)
I'm headed out!
Wouldn't say no to company!
President Porpoise!
President Porpoise?
President...
It's like there's this instruction manual
that explains how to talk to people
and everyone in the world
got a copy except me.
Ow! (CHUCKLES) Just, uh, taking a break.
Gonna keep looking!
Uh, what?
(GIGGLES)
(SCREAMS)
(SINGING) We've only just met
We've barely said a word to each other yet
But already I know that
We fit
Yes, two halves make a whole
And wholes are whole
Like an arm through a sleeve
(GROANING)
Or a cup into a movie seat
You haven't said a word to me
(GIGGLES)
Only just giggled gleefully
Uh, security!
But already I know that
We fit
Yeah, we fit
You're kissing my space helmet
And already I know
That two halves make a whole
This has been so nice.
But I should probably go help my
friends find President Porpoise.
Eh, come on, who cares?
Oh!
But he's your president.
National politics don't really
represent my interests.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Talk, Blowfish! Where's the President?
I don't know where he is!
I'm the President now!
- (CLOCK CHIMES)
- (LAUGHS EVILLY)
Oh, no, bro!
- (SCREAMS)
- Do not agree!
- (CHIRPS)
- Huh?
President Porpoise! But where have you...
- (CLICKS)
- A three-day weekend?
I don't remember you mentioning that.
I tied a string to my tentacle
to remind myself?
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, NOpe...
No... Oh! Well, T'll be!
Isn't it always on the last arm
you check? (CHUCKLES)
Please, Finn and Jake,
when you return to dry land,
tell no one of our lax record-keeping.
Ah, don't worry, Secretary Octopus.
We wouldn't want to deflate anyone's ego!
(BOTH LAUGH)
Huh? Ahh! Oh! (CLEARS THROAT)
My kids must be worried sick!
(HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAKING)
Man, I can't understand a word you're saying.
I said, where's Banana Man?
We're getting low on air, and I'm freaking out.
Uh, maybe there's a radio or something.
- Huh?
- Oh! Oh!
Aargh!
(LAUGHTER)
You know what, bro? I'm glad you're here.
JAKE: 'Cause dying together sucks
a little less than dying alone.
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!