(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
FINN: Wow, everything sucks here.
Finn, look!
FINN: Oh, geez, this looks pretty real.
He's got the Enchiridion!
And wait...
Is that Billy?
Why's he so tiny?
Hey! There's our guy.
Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, just hang out there for a while!
I love it!
I feel fresh! (LAUGHS)
Well, this is the weirdest thing I've ever done.
TOGETHER: Round and round
and round we go!
(EXCLAIMS)
BOTH: Oh, yeah!
School's out, ya tranch!
Whoa! (Grunts)
Hey, Prismo's calling.
Nice! Let's go say hi.
BEEMO: You're lucky I don't take
the other one, kid.
Quit crying, baby!
BOTH: Prism...
Oof!
BOTH: Mo...
...Otion!
PRISMO: Thanks for responding
to my call, guys.
I'm in a serious pickle,
and I mean the bad kind.
I mean, like, a really smelly, brown pickle.
Don't sweat it, boy.
Finn and I got your back.
Who's bullying you, Prismo?
Nobody's bullying me. Look...
Um, 'member when you wished
The Lich never existed
and you created a new wish reality
that ended up totally not working out?
- No.
- Vaguely, yes.
What?
You don't remember making that wish?
Whu-huh?
I thought I explained it to you that one time.
Dude, T'll catch you up.
Look.
After you wished The Lich never existed,
you got zapped to an alternative wish reality
where magic doesn't really exist.
FINN: Wait.
Who's that dude?
That's you, but sort of less cool.
Uh-huh. Proceed.
PRISMO: So you find an old Marceline
and the magic crown on the body
of Ice King's skeleton
who was smooshed under the weight
of a frozen mutagenic bomb.
But then the Destiny Gang steals
your family donkey,
SO you use the crown to become Ice Finn
and save your donkey and your family.
But the crown makes you crazy
and you ice everything up like a dumb bozo,
which sets off the mutagenic bornb
which releases the spirit of The Lich anyway.
But then this reality's Jake made
a counter wish
which supposedly fixed the problem,
but as it turns out, it didn't really.
Can I just say that I don't remember
any of this stuff.
Because technically it didn't happen to you.
But also it still happened
and that wish reality continues to exist.
Is this why, all of a sudden,
one day I was way better at the flute?
JAKE: Oh, yeah, I noticed that.
Listen. Something really bad
is about to go down.
Ice Finn is using his world's Enchiridion
to build a portal to the multiverse.
We literally do not know what will happen
if he succeeds,
but it could defs be catastrophic
to the architecture of these realities.
Now if that happens, my boss,
let me repeat that,
my boss will hold me responsible.
And by proxy, y'all both'll be in the dip, too.
Finn why not just "bloop-bloop" it all better?
Something there is dampening my powers.
I am losing my picks over this biz!
His boss? Who's that?
All right, man, what do we do?
Take this and use it to take care
of the Ice Finn.
Oh. Wait. What do you mean
by "take care of?"
Good luck, guys!
We're all depending on you!
- Whoa.
- What is it?
(GRUNTS)
- Oh, golly!
- What's that nay now?
It's like 50 bowling balls on my teen bod!
Oh, check it. There's instructions.
"The Maid will handle all Class A
interdimensional Bung-ups
"if you follow these simple steps."
"Direct the small end of The Maid
toward your massive mistake.
"Focus your intention until all distractions
leave your thought sphere,
"then recite the words,
'A man needs a maid' three times."
All right. (GRUNTS)
Here we...
Go, oh!
- Help, help, help. Help, help, help!
- Lower it.
- (SCREAMS)
- (FARTS)
Ledge, ledge, ledge.
Whew! Okay...
Focus my intention.
Just a few more jewels
before I can open the portal to a better world!
My intention to heal the madness
of this other self.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't think that's what we're
supposed to do.
Prismo said, "Take care of him."
Yeah, that means make him feel better.
Are you being stupid on purpose?
Yeah, but dude, that is me.
That's me.
I heard you the first time.
There's got to be something else we can do.
Bro, you heard Prismo.
We don't have a choice.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay, but you do it.
I just can't, man. It's too messed up.
All right. You're right.
Shut your eyes and cover your ears.
(CHANTING)
Whew!
JAKE: A man needs a maid. Whew!
A man needs a maid.
A man...
Needs...
Nope!
This is bull juice!
Oh, flip!
- (CHANTING CONTINUES)
- Hey, hey.
- Did you do it?
- No, man.
- Let's just go steal the Enchiridion.
- Whoa, yeah!
That way he can't open the portal
and nobody gets obliterated.
That should work!
That's not gonna work, you guys!
Don't walk away from The Maid.
No!
ICE FINN: Ah, it's gonna be so great
in the next place, guys!
It's like we're spinning... Spinning...
Spinning into the new land!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Sneaky fashion.
(GRUNTS)
(ZAP)
FINN: Aah!
JAKE: Ohh!
ICE FINN: What's this? Oh!
Oh, two more converts to my empire of frost?
Finn, I love you.
Just in case we eat it fighting this guy.
Oh, yeah. I love you, too.
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
ICE FINN: Oh, wonderful.
I thought I'd rescued all the humans!
Now you can hang out here
with everyone else.
Gunter says we just need a few more gems.
Anyway, now I'm going to freeze you.
Wait!
Huh?
Straight up magic!
Are you a wizard, too?
Yeah! Check out my amazing wizard bod!
JAKE: Hey, over here, man!
Look at me.
I'm a portal to another world.
You can't be.
I'm magic. I can do anything.
Don't you believe your own eyes?
Why would you be able to turn in...
JAKE: Why anything?
Why is the sky blue, bro?
That's right.
Just keep looking at me.
Hey, what's up?
I'll get you out of this, Billy.
It's Bobby.
Look out.
FINN: Who's that?
Enter the portal... What?
JAKE: Big Destiny?
Jewels.
- (MUMBLES)
- FINN: What's wrong with him?
He looks possessed or something...
Ew, boy, here we go.
That's my body, dog!
My friend, you return!
(LAUGHS)
This was all his idea!
Come on, that's The Lich!
He's evill
He's not even trying to hide it, bro!
CREATURE: Release.
(GASPS)
Big D's mind is back. Whoo!
I must escape first try!
Um...
What are you doing?
Whoa!
Traitor!
FINN: Jake, let's boogie!
You dirty gangsters!
We're not a gang! That's you.
Aah!
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Sleep.
(GROANS)
Gimmel!
CREATURE:
Bring the book.
Okay, buddy.
Are we gonna save the world now?
Bobby.
(GROANS)
Open, oh, great book!
The final hole is mine...
To put my thing in.
(CHUCKLES EVILLY)
(LAUGHS)
What dimension is this?
All of them.
That's great.
Then we can live everywhere.
Everywhere you will die.
Heh. What?
You, your family, everyone will die.
Over and over.
Mountains of broken bodies...
Beneath the wheel.
N GISNIE))
- Huh? What the...
(GROANS)
IEGIRVIEL
What the...
Aah!
Ew. Gross!
You used me!
Whoa.
ICE FINN: I trusted you, Lich!
JAKE: Mathematical.
Huh?
Freeze!
Oh. My power. It's gone!
- Aah!
- JAKE: Hang on, Finn! (ROARS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ow. Ow!
(CLINK)
Yes. The frost!
(LAUGHS) Doh!
Dude, don't kill him! It's me, kinda.
Other Finn, just listen at me.
Your name is Finn Mertens!
Your best friend is Jake the dog.
You have a birthmark like a flaming,
sideways teardrop...
In like a really weird place.
What? What's going on? Bartram?
Yeah, yeah! Your whole thing is you want
to help people, remember?
We can fix all this.
(GRUMBLES)
It's like the most evil heartburn!
FINN: Jake!
Get out of the way!
A man needs a maid! A man needs a maid!
A man needs a maid!
- (DING)
- WOMAN: Housekeeping.
(SCREAMS)
(SIGHS)
(PANTS, BARKS)
You're welcome!
Ha! I dunno what he's saying. Let's bounce.
Prismo, wait!
We have so much to talk about.
Oh.
Prismo, I'm sorry if this is breaking the rules,
but you got to help this guy out.
He's just always gonna be messed
up with that crown around.
PRISMO: Okay, I can try
rearranging some stuff.
- (MOUSE CLICKS)
- PRISMO: Just a quick cut...
And... Paste!
There! Now the ground zero bomb explosion
should destroy the crown in that reality...
And... Play.
PRISMO: So, yeah. This all goes down again...
Bomb goes off... (EXCLAIMS)
So, yeah. The crown is totally gone.
Your guy here goes back to normal.
Aww. (CHOMPING)
FINN: Huh, that's his family.
Hey, look how dumb I am in that world.
Here's me... (BARKS)
(CHORTLES) I eat stuff off the ground.
I dunno, what are dogs even into these days?
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!