(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
JAKE: Man, birthday-holiday overlap.
That's some tough luck.
Everyone's all jollied-out
when it's your turn for jollies.
Well...
You know, it's not actually the holidays.
Plus, Beemo wasn't actually even really born.
Well, I suppose.
But you don't got to be so technical about it.
Listen, all I'm saying is we...
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Is there a big rainbow
over your house right now,
spelling out "Happy birthday, Beemo"?
No. Actually, it's snowing like crazy.
Okay, that's what I was afraid of.
Peppermint Butler spilled grape juice
on my experimental weather machine,
and now it's going kablooey.
I got to stay here and fix this thing.
Tell Beemo I'm sorry I missed the party.
- That's okay. Beemo doesn't care any...
- (LINE DISCONNECTS)
Beemo only cares about one special guest.
- (GASPS)
- BEEMO: Moe!
Hooray! Moe is coming!
And he brought me a special
surprise for my birthday!
Moe is the smartest man in the world.
He's way smarter than you and you
and you, too, Jake...
And you're the smartest guy I know.
Hey, thanks.
And he knows everything about robots.
He built me, and he built
himself, and all the other Moes.
He's so smart!
I bet he could even fix Neptr.
What? What's wrong with me?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Oh, boy, oh, boy. He's here!
(GIGGLES) Hooray!
- (CRASH)
- Hooray!
Oh.
You are not Moe.
Why, of course I am, Beemo.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, okay.
Hey, Moe! New haircut?
Whoa, Moe!
What happened to your body?
Oh, oh! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, that old thing?
She conked out on me months ago.
I guess I don't make 'em like I used to.
(CHUCKLES)
Not like little Beemo here.
You got all my love and affection.
Thanks!
Well, we made a cake.
We weren't sure if you eat,
but Beemo insisted.
Eating helps me grow!
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Well, er, uh... When in Rome.
(CUTLERY CLINKING)
So, Beemo, are you ready
for your birthday surprise?
Boy, howdy!
For your birthday, I got you...
A special mission!
A mission?
A special mission, like a vacation.
For all of us?
No, no, no.
A special solo mission.
For Neptr?
(CHUCKLES) No.
It's a special rite of passage
I designed just for you, Beemo.
A simple jaunt to the Moe factory and back.
That's all.
And then you'll be a grown-up.
Wow.
FINN: Hmm, I don't know.
Sounds kind of dangerous.
Yeah, Beemo's like a baby almost.
Oh, don't be silly.
Every other Moe has done it since forever.
But won't I miss Finn and Jake?
Oh, sure.
But don't worry.
They'll be here when you get back.
But... Won't Finn and Jake miss me?
(CHUCKLES)
No, that's the beauty of it.
I'll be Beemo while you're gone.
- (CHUCKLING)
- NEPTR: Hooray!
Hooray!
- Hooray?
- NEPTR: Hooray!
(WIND WHISTLES)
Air?
Are you there, air?
It's me, Beemo.
I know it's been a long time since we talked.
Sorry about that.
But, well, maybe if you don't want to talk,
you could just listen.
Moe told me if I do this thing,
I'll be a grown-up,
and that sounds cool, I guess.
Like, if I was grown,
then I could drive to
the playground all by myself.
And I could buy my own pacifiers
at the store, if I was grown.
But then, if I change, will Finn
and Jake still love me?
Will I still love them?
Moe changed to a new bodly...
And he'’s still the same, I guess, sort of.
But does growing up just change
your body, or also your soul?
(SIGHS)
Maybe I could just stay the same forever.
So...
So!
(CLICKS TONGUE) Um...
Yeah, it's nice to see you, Moe.
Yeah, you too.
Uh...
So, Moe, do you want to...
Jake?
Oh, hey, I'm on my way. One sec.
Um, hold on, Moe.
Jake, what are you doing?
Finn, all this is
heck of awkward without Beemo.
Way more awkward than I thought it'd be.
I think maybe I don't like old people.
They make me feel like
I'm gonna get old one day, too.
I'm just gonna stay in this cup for a bit.
I'll be out later.
You can't do that, it's rude.
And what about Princess Bubblegum?
She's way old, and you like her.
Yeah, but she listens to music.
Moe probably only, like,
listens to the sound of the earth decaying.
Come on, you're being weird.
Hey, sorry about that, Moe.
Boys, I know this is new and different.
I am not Beemo.
But I will do the best to be your friend.
This is the daybreak of our lives,
and we have all the time in the world
to learn about each other.
For now, I will be your little robot.
Would you look at that beautiful snowfall.
Hey, let's get out there and have some fun.
I think I'm feeling better now.
Oh, whoa! Hey!
Hello there, Beemo!
Hello there, Dmo.
I'm here on a solo birthday mission.
Oh, yes, yes, Beemo, I know all about it.
Moe left special instructions for you.
(CHUCKLES)
He wants you to stand on that "X" over there.
Oh, okay.
Like this? (GASPS)
Dmo, what happened?
Oh, this? (STAMMERS) It's nothing.
It's just whatever.
Uh, I don't know about this, Dmo.
Something doesn't... Ahhh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Ugh!
(MACHINERY RUMBLING)
Hello?
(CHUCKLING)
Boys, look at this!
This is cool, right?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
- Yeah!
(LAUGHTER)
Oh!
(SCREAMING)
Whoo!
(LAUGHTER)
- Classic!
- Yeah!
Did you see what we did, Moe?
(SOBS) This is horseplay!
Stop it! (SOBBING)
We need to go inside
and do what I want to do!
Oh. Okay. Lf, if you want.
(SOBBING)
Yeah.
Dmo? Hello?
Anybody?
The "X" door opened, and I fell through.
I think something went wrong
with the mission.
Uh...
Abort mission!
Unless... Maybe this is all part of Moe's plan.
It doesn't seem like it.
But maybe that's the point.
Maybe the lesson is that when you are grown,
you won't ever be able to tell
if everything is going totally haywire,
or maybe actually everything is perfectly fine.
- (MACHINERY WHIRRING)
- Huh?
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Huh? Who's there?
Moe?
No. It's only me. Beemao.
Beemo? Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
Who are you? Are you a Moe, too?
Oh, Beemo, no, no, no.
I am all Moes.
All Moes?
Uh... I don't understand.
Of course not. I'm so sorry.
Let me explain.
Peace had reigned in Moe's wondrous factory
for a hundred, hundred years.
There was a place for every Moe,
and every Moe was in its place.
If you wanted a free hug,
all you had to do was ask.
No one could say no, it was a rule.
Until one fateful day, yesterday,
when a mysterious viral signal
somehow breached our firewall
and was broadcast throughout the factory,
instructing all us Moes to do somersaults
- into the trash compactor all day long.
- (CRASH)
BEEMO: That's horrible.
And we've been trapped here
all smushed together, ever since.
That's horrible, too.
How... How do we get out?
Well, that's why we're so glad
you're here, Beemo.
You're the key. The key to escape.
Only you can save us now.
Let's see. $4 off a...
Honey-baked ham.
I don't like ham.
$1 off of beets.
Do beets have tannins?
What is that?
Oh! $4 off a honey-baked ham.
Moe?
Call me "Gwampa."
How's your rose water?
It's exactly what it says it is.
So, hey, uh, Gwampa, feels too quiet in here.
Maybe we can hang out with Neptr?
He can rap or something.
(TREADS SCREECH)
(RAPPING) B- b-b-bread
Where's my needle and thread...
MOE: No!
(BOTH GASP)
Eh, well, Neptr is too distracting.
Who wants to play video games?
Oh, you have games like Beemo?
Let's do that, Gwampa.
I have one video game.
- It's called hangman.
- (GASPS)
That sounds griz as nuts!
Yeah, let's play hang-a-man!
Coming right up.
(BEEPS)
Pick a letter.
Show us what you did, hangman!
(BUZZER)
MOE: Pick a letter.
BEEMO: But, Allmo, I don't understand.
How can I help?
I mean, I'm just a little baby kid still.
Even though it's my birthday.
Happy birthday, Beemo.
I don't know about that,
but I do know about your special mind.
As the accumulation of all Moes,
my computing power is unmatched.
Yet still, I lack the imagination
to think outside my collective programming.
I can only see the world as it is.
But your imagination, Beemo,
lets you see the world how it could be,
or might sort of be like.
If the two of us work together,
we can think up a way out of here.
I will do what I can.
All right. You see that hatch over there?
That hatch leads to an exit corridor.
- But it's locked from this side.
- (BEEPS)
The vent up there leads to the other side.
But it's too high up.
Oh.
What if we use this trash
to climb up to the vent?
But all this trash is too small.
Ah-huh!
Whoa. You just blew my mind.
What haven't we guessed yet? "B."
"Burgess Meredith"?
(BEEPING)
I don't even know what that is!
Do you boys want to play again?
(GROANS)
Boys love games.
Pick a letter.
Uh, I don't know, "E."
Is this "burgess Meredith" again?
(BEEPS)
Not cool!
Come on, Finn, let's find a real hangman.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(METAL CREAKING)
(GRATE CLATTERS)
Yuck.
This room gives me
the heebie-jeebies straight-up.
ALLMO: It is the room of Amo,
the first of our siblings.
He, too, was special.
As you were built to give love,
Amo was built to receive.
But he could not think
outside his programming
and was blinded by his need.
Such is the cruel physics of love
that those who crave it most will repel it
and only the dang rich get richer.
Well, maybe as my birthday present,
I can ask Moe to fix Amo.
But this is impossible.
Moe went off line yesterday
and has not re-Iogged.
Our sensors would know.
But he's at my house right now
with Finn and Jake.
He got a new body.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Did this new body
happen to have jagged prongs
and a cannon phaser on top of its head?
No. (LAUGHS)
Phew!
(LAUGHS) He had a huge, gigantic wig on.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
The spikes are under the wig!
Oh, no! Of course!
Your friends may be in grave danger.
He must have sabotaged the factory.
Quickly, hoist me up on top of your head.
We must depart straightaway.
Uh...
You're stronger than you know.
Also, I'm lighter than you know.
I'm sorry we didn't find any hangmen.
I don't even know what I'd do
with a hangman if I got one.
MOE: Bloo-hoo. Bloo-hoo.
Ah, bloo-hoo.
Moe!
Bandits stole my legs! (CRYING)
FINN: Yeesh.
If you tell us where the bandits went,
we'll avenge your legs!
We're sorry we left you!
You should be.
I'm your gwampa wobot.
Carry me.
(GRUNTS)
Over here.
There! There's the thief!
The thief with my legs!
FINN: Neptr?
Throw him out! (SOBBING)
Come on.
Maybe Neptr did it like, accidentally?
Neptr's out cold.
He's got a heck of a dent on his head.
What? Who could have done that?
Forget him! You love me, right?
You love me like Beemo?
What? You're all right, but we...
We love Beemo.
Yeah, man, be cool.
Beemo's like our best friend.
Beemo's trash!
Moe!
Moe's dead!
Amo?
You don't love me!
- Owl
- Argh!
Wake up and love me!
BEEMO: Imposter!
Amo!
Hello, Beemo.
I'm your cute sibling, Amo.
I know about you and your dirty hands.
Where are Finn and Jake?
I think Finn and Jake went
somewhere to buy me a gift.
Tell me what you did with Finn
and Jake and our poop.
] - Ay!
(GROWLS)
Ay!
Amo, look at my face!
You gone too far!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Byel!
(BEEMO PANTING)
You can't escape the birthday boy!
(GROANS)
Too high.
BEEMO: Hey!
Talk, Amo!
You want to know where Papa is?
Here is all that remains of him.
His memory backup drive.
Oh.
AMO: I was returning from a long pilgrimage.
I came to confront Papa,
for I had discovered terrible
things about myself.
He was dying.
"Amo, dear child,
"my body is conking out."
(MOE COUGHS)
"Take this.
"It is who I am.
"Send my mind into space,
"so I may spend the eons among the stars
"and other brilliant gasses."
AMO: His hands were as cold as clay.
Our papa never loved me,
so I ignored his last request.
I used his knowledge
of the factory and its Moes
to destroy them.
- DMO: Is that you, Amo?
- They didn't love me, either.
Where you been?
(CHUCKLES) What are you doing?
No!
AMO: Then I learned about you
and your new family.
I wanted a taste of that melon.
People in my life don't love me.
I'll obliterate, y'all!
You cheat. Give me those memories.
(GRUNTS)
Beemo, I don't want to look at you!
(PANTING)
Tough nuts!
For Moe!
(EXPLOSION)
(POWERING DOWN)
ALLMO: Beemo!
Hey.
We caught the tail end of what happened.
- Are you okay?
- No.
Well, T don't like that.
Beemo, will you live with us
back at the factory?
With Moe gone, you can be our leader.
I don't think I can.
I'm not grown up. Or I'm too grown up now.
I think I just killed someone.
I need to have some time alone,
but you're all really nice.
FINN: All right.
JAKE: Sorry your birthday was weird.
That was the craziest thing
that ever happened.
But I guess, after all that,
I do feel a bit more grown.
Except that the mission
was just some made-up lie.
So who knows if I will ever grow up at all.
And Moe is gone now.
So if there is anything he wanted to teach me,
it better be in me already.
I guess all I can do is
listen to the heart Moe gave me.
Except that's what Amo did,
and he turned out bad.
So what if I turn out bad, too?
Amo could not think outside
his programming and was blinded.
But your imagination lets you
see the world how it could be.
But I am different.
It's not just Moe up here,
it's me, too.
And if I cannot trust in Moe, I can trust in me.
Oh, boy.
It sure is confusing being grown.
I miss you, Moe.
What a day!
(SMACKS LIPS)
(YAWNS)
I'm gonna miss you, too, Beemo.
I feel so very, very proud of you.
(SMACKS LIPS)
(YAWNS)
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
We can wonder through the forest
And do so as we please
Come along with me
To a cliff under a tree
This party is so crazy!