(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
(QUACKS)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
(HUMMING)
BEEMO: One free-range Humpty Dumpty.
Sorry.
Fine aged Cheddar man.
Homemade ketchup.
(GAGS)
(SWISHING)
(GROANING)
A fresh pepper fart.
(FARTING)
Dance, parsley.
(SQUISH)
Face bread.
Special sentient sandwich.
(CLICK, WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHING)
(CLICK, WHIRRING AND WHOOSHING STOP)
Mmm... Is that special sentient sammich?
Bingo!
Made by the Beemo.
Beemo, you're my little cherub.
You know that?
You made all this for me, right?
Aaahhh.
Not so fast, Jake.
No. (GROANS)
The sammiches are yours...
For a price.
What?
I need you to be my tiny horse for the day,
so I can do my live-action
cowboy role-play adventure.
No way. Poo deal.
I'll do 20 minutes.
It took me over six hours
to prepare this nosh, Jake.
Not to mention the time it took
acquiring the ingredients
through the "special market,"
putting my safety
and my reputation on the line.
Okay, fine, fine.
Three sammiches for every hour I'm a horse.
Mmm...
One sammich per horse-hour,
six-hour minimum.
Deal.
Yippee-ki-yay!
Om! Mmm.
(MUNCHING, GULPS)
Oh, yeah.
It tastes alive.
(MUNCHING)
(THUD AND SPURS JANGLE)
Steed yourself, partner.
Okay.
Hmm. (GULPS)
(CREAKING)
'Kay.
Oh, come on, man.
You didn't even try.
I did try. Horses are hard.
(CREAKS)
(STRAINS)
(GROANS)
How's that?
Eh, it reads.
(SPURS JINGLING)
Steady, girl.
- What...
- (SHUSHING)
I'm going to mount you now.
Hup!
- Good girl.
- (GROANS)
So, what's the plan anyway, Beemo?
The plan is to punch the toads to the stump
and bring justice to the peeps!
Oow!
Oh, and by the way, Jake,
from now on, you can call me..."Angel Face".
- Hyah!
- Youch!
I used to be a guy who ran from glob
with the wind at my back
and the devil on my shoulder.
Now I'm the guy chasing those guys,
yet the devil is still here,
sleeping in my couch.
Beemo, that hurt when you dug your boots
into my side belly.
Are you gonna apologize or...
Horses do not talk.
Over there! Hyah!
- (SPUR PLUNGES)
- (GROANS)
Whoa!
Jackrabbit Johnson.
(SPITS)
This guy's wanted for stealing piglets
from their mothers while they are feeding.
Makes me sick.
(CHEWING)
He was last seen in Dead Goat Gulch.
What do you say, girl?
Want to catch this donkey
and split the reward?
(SMACKS)
You have 45 minutes left
before my next sammich.
Time's a-wasting!
- (SPURS PLUNGE)
- Yee!
(LAUGHS)
Hmm.
(PANTING)
(GROANS) Beemo, I'm tired.
Looks like my horse needs a rest.
Slow down, horse.
(SIGHS)
(HUMMING)
(SINGING) Being a robot cowboy
Is a lonely job
But somebody has to protect the piglets
(ALL GASP)
I got nobody but my horse
And my friend the Cactus Guy
It's okay because I like them a lot
That's okay,
I like being a robot cowboy
(HUMMING)
- (CHOMPING)
- (HUMMING)
(HUMMING)
BEEMO: Be careful, Jake.
This is where Jackrabbit Johnson's
gang of lowlife bandits lays low.
(GASPS) Hyah!
Bang! Bang!
Put them up, partner!
Hyah!
Pew, pew.
Pew, pew, pew!
I want answers!
(AS SOCKS) "You can't do this to us."
No answers, eh? No use to me!
How about you, Frisco?
(AS FRISCO) "I'm not going to talk."
Why am I talking to you then?
(GRUNTING)
(CHEWING, CHUCKLES)
(YELPS, GROANS)
Beemo, what did you do?
It's Jackrabbit Johnson's
right-hand man, Tumbleweed Turk.
I spent the last three months
building all of this.
Oh, that's where you been?
Mmm-hmm.
Beemo gave me a Finn cake.
Don't talk to my horse, Tumbleweed.
- (BEEMO GRUNTS)
- (TUMBLEWEED GROANS)
Where is Jackrabbit Johnson?
I know you know where he's headed.
I don't know.
Tumbleweed Turk's always the last to know.
It's just like I told the other
bounty hunter, I swear.
I don't believe a word you say.
Now, take a message to your compadre.
Tell him his old pal Angel Face
is itching to get together.
Tell Jackrabbit Johnson
to meet me at Dirtwater Flats,
just like the old days!
IS
Okay.
(WHIRRING)
Sock citizens of Dead Goat Gulch,
we can rebuild!
(WHISTLES)
(NEIGHS)
- (SPURS JANGLE)
- (GROANS)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(SNARLS)
(GALLOPING)
Uh...
I don't remember where Dirtwater Flat is.
Better stop for the night.
We can make a campfire here.
And we will talk about
what we will do with the reward money.
No.
It's been fun, Beemo,
but it's time to go home
because there are no more sandwiches.
But I want to finish the adventure.
Which direction is the house?
I'm not sure.
(GASPS) Get down!
Getting kicked out of the Guild of Assassins...
Check.
Capturing my first bounty...
Check. (MUNCHING)
Going to Finn and Jake's treehouse
and getting revenge...
Unchecked.
JACKRABBIT JOHNSON: Finn and
Jake's treehouse?
Mmm-hmm.
Who are you,
and why do you want to get revenge?
I am Me-Mow!
Me-Mow? Whoa.
You've gotten bigger.
Have we met before?
JAKE: Finn, is that you?
That's Jackrabbit Johnson!
Finn?
It is Finn!
Tricked again!
Look, it's Me-Mow, Beemo.
I don't care. That's my bounty!
- (EXCLAIMS)
- (GROANS)
Jake, transform... Horse!
Whoa! Did you have a real gun all this time?
I am old enough to vote.
ME-MOW: (THINKING) Hey, Jake, if you
can hear my internal monologue,
I'm going to Kill you.
(CHUCKLES EVILLY)
(BLOWS)
(RATTLING)
(RATTLESNAKE GROANS)
(WHIZZING)
Your daisy days are over!
I am the whaler 'round these parts!
Huh.
(SIZZLING)
(GUN CLICKS)
Sounds like you're out of ammo.
No, you heard incorrectly.
Bang, bang, bang!
(LAUGHS)
I'm coming for you.
(WHIZZING)
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
(GRUNTS)
(BLOWS)
Blast you, Finn and Jake and Angel Face.
This prison cell's not going to hold me.
Oh?
Hey, Finn and Jake! I'll get my revenge!
You hear me?
ME-MOW: Revenge!
Hey, Beemo, are you sure you took down
all the wanted posters?
Yes.
- Stick 'em up.
- Huh?
This bounty belongs to me.
Get out of here!
(SCREAMS)
Thanks, Beemo.
(IN TOUGH VOICE) You're welcome.
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!