(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
BEEMO: Football, you don't mean that.
FOOTBALL: I do, Beemo.
I don't say things I don't mean.
You look very smart
and very handsome today.
Oh, Football, thank you.
I love you so much.
I love you, Beemo.
Ring, ring. Hello? Football?
This is Beemo.
Oh, hello, Beemo.
What a wonderful surprise. What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Just wanted to say that I love you.
I love you, too. Goodbye. Click.
Can I tell you a secret?
Of course, Beemo.
You can tell me anything.
I love you.
Oh! (GIGGLES)
Now you tell me a secret, Football.
I wish I could spend just one day
on the other side of the mirror.
Well, let's switch places for the day.
Oh, Beemo, you'd do that for me?
Yes, Football. Because I love you.
Oh, Beemo.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
Oh! (LAUGHS)
See you back here tomorrow, Football.
(GASPS)
Oh! Oh!
Ah! Whoo.
(MOANING, BUZZING)
Hello. My name is Football.
And you are Carlos,
my best friend since college.
(QUACKS)
Carlos.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, let's not leave it
so long next time, Carlos.
(QUACKS)
(LAUGHS)
Hmm?
Jake, get out of my fruit, man!
- (LAUGHS)
- You're cute, but you're dirty.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (FOOTBALL GASPS)
(EXCLAIMING)
Ooh. Ah!
What are you doing on the floor,
you bad baby?
Yes. Shh. Yes. I understand.
Oh, baby, don't turn around.
But Finn is set right over there.
Hello, my name is Football.
Very nice to meet you, Football.
How'd you get the name Football, Football?
- Beemo gave it to me.
- Is Beemo your little papa?
(GIGGLES)
Uh, so where do you live, Football?
- The mirror.
- Oh, yeah?
What's it like there?
Cold.
Empty.
It's... Lonely.
Weird.
Very weird.
(DOOR CREAKS)
Hello?
Football, are you okay?
It's weird in here.
I'm not going back, Beemo.
Come closer, Football.
I can't hear you.
I'm not going back, Beemo.
I'm staying on this side. Forever.
Football. Football!
No! No! Football, no!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTS) Hyah!
Yes!
Send another g-fruit to the slaughter, Jake!
- JAKE: You got it.
- Myah!
(PANTING) Family meeting!
- Hmm?
- What's up, B... Oh!
- (THUD)
(CHUCKLES) Sorry, man.
OVEN: Did somebody say
"Family meeting?"
- What's up, Beemo?
- No, I'm not Beemo.
I'm Football.
- Oh, yeah.
- Hi, Football.
Yes. Hello.
I'm here, and I am Football.
And I will always be Football.
Because, Beemo told me to tell you
that he has gone away forever.
- (SOBBING) Beemo.
- (OVEN DINGS)
"Take my place, Football,"
is what he said.
(CHOMPING)
It was such a hard decision for him to make.
(SNIFFLES)
He says for you guys to treat her...
I mean, me.
As nice as you treated him, Beemo.
We all need to stay strong,
so the best thing everyone
can do is forget about him.
Remember, if you guys miss Beemo,
I miss him more.
- That's great, Beemo.
- Football.
Oh, right. Football.
(SIGHS)
Hey, Football.
Grapefruit for your troubles?
Uh... (CHUCKLES) Oh, boy! Thanks!
- Life is great!
- Yeah?
You sure you're doing okay, little pal?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Listen, B... Football.
You seem like you might be feeling, uh,
a little donked up in your head
or your heart or both.
And that's okay.
Everybody feels some type of
soul nausea like that sometimes.
- BEEMO: Football.
- Beemo?
I know how to follow you, Football.
- How did you get in the spoon?
- I figured it out!
I'm going to get you, Football!
Did all that make sense?
(SCREAMS)
Yeah.
(PANTING) Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
- (PANTING)
- (BEEMO GROWLING)
I'm going to get you, Football!
Ahhh!
Ha! (PANTING)
Ha-ha!
This is the way it has to be... Mo.
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
Oh, my gosh!
Football! Football! Football.
I'm sorry, Beemo.
(GROWLS)
- Football.
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
BEEMO: Don't do it!
(FOOTBALL GRUNTING, PANTING)
Argh!
(YELLS)
(PANTING)
Beemo, what is going on in here?
- Beemo?
- (GROWLING)
Beemo! Ahhh!
- Beemo, why?
- (YELLING)
(HUMMING) Huh?
- Ow.
- Ahhh!
BEEMO: Football?
Football, I know it's you.
We are both walking backwards
holding shillelaghs.
Football?
(SCREAMS)
Uh...
(GROWLS)
I'm gonna get you, Football!
- Ahhh!
- (THUD)
Ah!
FINN: All right, hand over
the shillelagh, Beemo.
FOOTBALL: No! No! No!
Hey, Jake, Beemo went all
hog wild in the bathroom.
JAKE: Gross!
- Not like that.
- Ohhh!
Why you gonna be
so destructive today, Beemo?
Are you doing robot puberty or something?
Jake! Jake, help me! Jake!
(SIGHS)
All right, Football, you know what time it is.
Sooner or later, you're going to
slip on some spaghetti,
and I will be waiting on that shiny floor
to drag you into your worst nightmare.
Beemo, you've seen where I live.
You know why I don't want to go back.
But we made a deal,
and where I come from, a factory,
breaking deals means
you have to go to the dirt hole.
That's where you are going, Football,
if you don't switch places with me.
No!
You're going to the dirt hole, Football.
- Dirt hole!
- No!
I'm going where you will never find me.
JAKE: Aw, Football!
FINN: Football! Beemo?
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Beemo, what the heck?
I am Football! And I am safe up here!
Come on, man, we're worried about you.
Come back inside.
No, no, no, no, no! No!
(PANTING)
I'm safe up here.
No reflections. Safe.
BEEMO: Football.
(GASPS)
Dirt hole!
Ahhh!
(GRUNTS) Ahhh!
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
Football?
(GASPS) Beemo, this place.
It's beautiful here.
- All my friends are here.
- (QUACKS)
Carlos is here.
It's all I ever wanted.
Hmm.
About what I did...
It's okay. I know why you did it.
I didn't like your bathroom much, either.
There is no beauty in the bathroom.
Will you still visit me?
Yes, Football, because I love you.
I love you, Beemo.
(QUACKS)
Beemo! You okay?
Oh, Finn and Jake! I am back!
I am back! I'm really back! (LAUGHS)
Oh!
Put that traffic cone back
on your head, young man.
(CHUCKLING) Yes, I'd love to!
I've missed my traffic cone so much!
(GIGGLES)
Hooray!
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!