(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
(QUACKS)
Adventure Time
Come on, grab your friends
We'll go to very distant lands
With Jake the dog
and Finn the human
The fun will never end
It's Adventure Time
So, then Melissa's like,
"What do you think of him?"
And I'm all, "Well, he's no
ray of sunshine or whatever."
(JAKE WHOOPING)
You know these people you just
get, like, neggy vibes from?
Yeah, like bad jubies or something.
Totally.
They just put everyone in a wack mood
with their bad jubies!
(LAUGHTER)
Whoops.
Oh, man. My body feels weird.
Uh, dude, that's 'cause you just got
glide-sliced by the ice duo. (LAUGHS)
Yeah, my body feels weird, too.
- Here, Finn, feel this.
- BEEMO: Ah!
- (ALARM BLARES)
- Whoa!
Too much electricity to the noggin, bro.
- He'll be fine.
- (BEEPING) Oh!
- JAKE: See? Fine.
- (LAUGHS)
That was...
(DISTORTED) weird.
MAN: This is a storm alert
from the automated weather service
in effect for the grasslands
and all surrounding areas.
Residents must evacuate
or seek shelter immediately.
Wait, what?
- (CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
- MAN: And now your local forecast.
(MAN READING)
How long's this gonna last, man?
A whole week?
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (GLITCHES)
- (NORMAL VOICE) What do we do?
My dudes, check it.
Super-sweet underground bunker time!
But we got to build this thing fast.
I'll collect building materials.
Beemo, you stock up on water.
LSP, you gather food.
And Jake, you... Where'd he go?
Jake! (SIGHS) Hey, man.
Whatcha doing up here?
We need help building
the underground thingamajiggy.
I think I just need a little time up here
for a minute, dude.
What is it, man, nervous poots?
Uh... Naw. Naw, man, nothing like that.
It's cool, man. Just come down soon.
We're gonna need your help.
Hmm...
(FARTS)
(GRUNTS)
Aw, man! This is gonna take me all day.
Where you getting all that food, LSP?
I took it from that guy's house.
- What?
- Chill, homie. Nobody's there.
It's, like, abandoned or something.
Yeah? Oh-kay...
(HUMMING)
Beemo, what is the deal with Jake?
Oh, he's down by the river.
But shouldn't he be helping us?
My arms are already, like, super-tired
from carrying all those bags of chips.
This isn't fair!
- (WHISTLING)
- Oh, okay.
The Beemo will talk to him.
Hmph!
(SINGSONG) Water bot!
I am the water bot!
I have a water body!
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- Oops! (GIGGLES)
I will never know the pleasures
of skinny-dipping.
Jake!
Hey, there, buddy.
- (CHIRPING)
- BEEMO: Jake!
Jake! There you are!
The storm is getting closer.
Look! (BEEPING)
We need your help.
Well... (SIGHS) The thing is,
I've been working on this thing,
and I've been collecting, like, lots of stuff.
Um, I just can't really show anybody yet.
But trust me, man, it'll be great, I promise.
But... But Jake, I don't see anything here.
You're thinking too much with those eyeballs,
not enough with your mind hole...
Or whatever computer thingy
you got up in there.
I'll catch ya later, man! Don't worry.
(ALARM BEEPING)
(RIBBITS)
Nailed it.
Lousy Finn and cans...
Jake... Making me put
these cans up on the shelf...
(GRUNTING)
- (CLATTERING)
- (SHOUTING) That's it!
Is Jake staying in this bunker or what?
I mean, of course. It's for everyone.
But he hasn't lumping done anything!
Oh, but he said he was
working on something.
Get real, Beemo!
That fool needs to get schooled.
(GRUMBLING)
Oh, heck no! Unh-uh!
Excuse mel
Are you not aware that we are all working
our steamy butts off down there
so we don't get wiped out
by this crazy sky nightmare?
Whoa, whoa. Hold up.
I'm working on something up here. It...
I see nothing! You're working on nothing!
Look, LSP, can we just take a moment
to appreciate this moment?
Look at this crazy sweet sunset.
When's the next time
you're gonna see a sunset like this?
Or any sunset, really?
Who knows how long we'll be down there?
(EAGLE SCREECHES)
(SCREAMING)
I obviously love sunsets and cute animals,
but we don't have time for this right now!
- But I...
- You know what?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
I just can't with you right now.
- Can't what?
- (WHOOSHES)
(SCREECHES)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Jake! He hates lightning.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Ah, Jake, you're back.
- Yeah. Heh.
- So, what'd you bring, man?
Heard you were working on something big.
Well, I've been jotting some
stuff down in my notebook.
Oh, cool. Like survival tips and junk?
No, not really. It's more like, um...
It's a surprise.
Oh. So, you didn't bring anything.
- (THUNDER RUMBLES, CRASHES)
- Oh, snap!
Got to seal the door!
- Beemo, light this baby up.
- Ooh!
- (ELECTRICITY HUMS)
Okay. All boarded up.
Now we wait.
We just wait? That's it?
Can we at least play a game or something?
I'm already bored.
Sure. What game?
Spin the Bottle.
- Yee!
- Sorry, LSP. Ain't got no bottles.
(GULPING)
Yes, we do. (BELCHES)
Yo, what gives? We got to ration that water!
I have needs, Finn!
- (BOTTLE SHATTERS)
- Just sit there, then.
I'll be texting Brad
until you change your min...
(CELL PHONE CLATTERS)
And that's why you should
never rely on technology.
No offense, Beemo.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah, I think she's already asleep.
(SNORING)
(YAWNS) Hey, you guys hungry?
- JAKE: Mmm-hmm.
- Hungry...
Yo, LSP, throw me some chips.
(MUNCHING, MUFFLED) No more chips.
How about some of them bean-beans?
No. No more.
Looks like we've got a can of,
like, beet... Something.
Wait, what? Is that all that's left?
I was hungies!
You ate all the food? I can't believe you!
Whatever, Finn. I'm not here to make friends.
- (WIND HOWLING)
- I'm here to not die.
- (THUD)
- (GROANS)
(ALL GASP)
Finn, the door!
You were supposed to secure the door!
Beemo, you saw me do it!
That wood must be bunk or something.
Yeah, I think this food's bunk, too.
It expires in...
Twenty-nine years ago.
Oh, glob! (SCREAMS)
I knew raiding that house was a bad idea.
Well, maybe... Maybe I could've
built something better
if I had some help from, oh,
I don't know, my best friend!
- (SCREAMING)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
No!
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
- JAKE: Beemo!
(LSP GRUMBLING)
(BEEPS)
What'd I miss?
Why is it dark now?
Yeah, I broke it. Whatever.
Guys, I think this storm is more than just
some scary clouds and weather junk.
We've been treating each other like
ding-dongs since we've been down here.
Duh! This bunker is the worst!
Nah, nah. I think this storm's carrying
some major negative energy or something.
Bad jubies.
It's making us all go nanners!
I think I can help, though.
Let me show you what I've been working on.
Ahem.
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
(IMITATES BIRD CHIRPING)
(IMITATES STREAM FLOWING,
FROG CROAKING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(IMITATES BIRDS CHIRPING)
It is so beautiful!
(CHIRPING, CROAKING CONTINUE)
(CLEARS THROAT, GASPS)
(WHISTLING, CROAKING RHYTHMICALLY)
(BEATBOXING)
(ALARM BLARES)
Holy tornado twins!
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Peek-a-boo! I'mma hurt you!
- No!
- Don't hurt us!
But I only feel good about myself
when I knock other people down!
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
I told you, man,
this storm's got an attitude problem!
Jake, you gotta help us
get back to our happy place.
The only way to fight bad jubies
is with good jubies!
(BEATBOXING, CHIRPING, CROAKING)
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
- (SHRIEKS)
Finn, I can't keep this up solo!
But we can't make all those sounds!
No time to be self-conscious, man!
(ECHOING) Get on this beat! (BEATBOXING)
Swish! Swish! (BEATBOXING)
- Swish! Swish!
- (CHIRPING)
Caw! Ca-caw! Whoal!
Tweet! Tweet! Tweet!
What are those noises?
The sound of good vibes!
Yeah, the dope beats of life!
- (RAIN POURING)
- It makes me feel some type of way.
How about you pause that stormin' for a sec
so you can hear the rest of it?
(RAIN, THUNDER STOP)
(IMITATES BIRDS CHIRPING)
Wait. Wait, wait. That one. What's that one?
(CAWING)
No, no, no. That "tweet-tweet" one.
- (IMITATES BIRDS CHIRPING)
- Yes! Ohh...
I haven't heard that sound
since I was a baby breeze.
What? You forgot what a bird sounds like?
No wonder you're depressed!
You know, you should really stop
and slow down more often.
Yeah. You get to hear life happening.
Makes you feel good.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(DEEP SIGH)
You're right!
I've been a freaky storm for so long
that I forgot it's okay
to be a breeze sometimes.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm going to explore
the rest of this beautiful day.
Wait! Here, man. Take my notebook.
It's got the sheet music to my jam.
Really? You would do that?
Yeah, just take it.
(WIND HOWLING)
Thank you so much, stretchy dog.
This is one of the nicest things
anyone's ever done for me.
Outey!
Yes! The sun!
Hoo-hoo!
I am sorry we doubted you, Jake.
Ditto.
Proud of you, man.
- (EAGLE SCREECHES)
- (SCREAMS)
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!