[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
So...if that's where we started
and this is the water
and this is where
the humans are,
then we must be aroooound...
here.
JAKE: Oh, no!
Giant Finn hand straight ahead!
[Imitates crash]
Jake!
That's not how
you navigate, man.
Yeah, I know.
But what do you expect?
I was afraid of the ocean
for, like, forever.
Relax.
I'm a regular sea dog.
Just gotta measure
the angle of the sun
using my pocket sextant.
Then do some super-complicated
calculations...
[Mutters]
...and some plotting.
And, voila!
We got a course.
Straight through
the Sea of Sure Death.
Susan, we've got a course!
Whoo!
BOTH: Whoo!
ALL: Whoo!
Susan feel alive.
Ahh!
Mm.
-[Dolphin chatters]
-[Laughs]
Cool.
J El-le-fly, el-le-fly,
emerge from the chrysalis &
s Flyyyy 7
[Screaming]
Someone!
[Gasps]
Majestic animal in distress!
Let's go! Let's go!
Turn left!
That's gonna take us off course.
Uh, helping people comes first.
[Screaming]
-[Angry grumbling]
- We don't like you!
You make us uncomfortable!
Susan does not think
this is a good idea.
- What?!
- Yeah, Susan.
What if those people need
to slay lizard to feed babies?
Yeah, man, then it'd be like
you're the slayer of babies.
[Sighs]
So, it's up to Finn
to stop that ship
all by his self.
Catapult me, Jake.
[All shouting]
Sea lizard make
scary storm magic.
[All screaming]
We're gonna die!
We deserved that.
See?
Not good idea.
Hello!
Yoo-hoo!
Hi.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry about your boat.
I was just trying
to get rid of those weirdos.
Sorry.
My name's Whipple, by the way.
Um, I'm Finn the human.
Susan.
And I'm the bad boy, Jake.
Were they after
your shiny, shiny pelt, Whipple?
No, they said I was annoying.
TOGETHER; What?
That is so mean.
I don't know what it is.
I mean, I see those guys around
all the time.
I thought they were cool.
Uh-oh.
I lost the sextant.
Does that mean we're lost?
It means I can't determine
our current posi-
Ooh! Ooh!
Let me see!
You trying
to get to this island?
Pssh, I know where that is.
I can totally get you there.
Without instruments?
I got fish senses.
Yeah, okay.
That sounds good.
Good lizard.
[Gasps]
You guys are so cool!
You're cool, Mr. Navigator.
[Giggles]
Whipple, you're the greatest.
WHIPPLE: Okay, so, but here's
the really clever part, okay?
Squirrel girl wakes up
and realizes she's alone.
Squirrel boy never existed.
It was all a dream.
Cool, right?
Whipple, you suck so much.
WHIPPLE: And I'm thinking
the next novel in the series
will center around a married cat
who has an extra-marital crush
on a handsome ape, Stanley.
Or maybe Stanley's
too close to "Dan Lee."
That's from my screenplay
about a hot turtle couple
who go on a cross-country
road trip as a last resort
to save their marriage.
But then they find out
they're actually gophers.
Anyway, I'm really excited
about my kids' book, too.
It's kind of a sad story
about these anthropomorphic
salt and pepper shakers
who've been BFFs for life,
but Pepper starts
developing feelings for Salt,
and basically, Salt never
[muffled] returns them
and ends up marrying
[normal] another guy, so Pepper
[muffled] starts writing stories
to try to distract himself.
It's semi-autobiographical --
Stop!!
- BMO?!
You stowed away?
Who cares?!
Give me the earplugs!
BOTH; Shh!
Wait. Are you guys
wearing earplugs?
Uh...I| mean, we were,
but it was 'cause of the engine
noise, not 'cause of you.
It is because of you!
- BMO.
- He needs to be told.
No one wants to hear your ideas!
I see.
I thought you guys
were my friends,
but you're all just
a bunch of haters!
[All screaming]
Nice one, Jake.
I don't want
to be the boat, though.
Well...you're the boat.
Yeah, I know.
Might as well go
full sloop, then.
All right.
Jake-boat away!
- Away!
Uh, dude, I got no idea
where to head.
BMO, don't you have
some kind of navigation app?
(\\[o
Oh, wait.
Yes, I do.
[Puma]
FINN:
What next, BMO?
BMO: Cap'N Nav app says
to look for a rock
shaped like a chubby cat.
SUSAN:
That looks like cat.
Full steam ahead.
[Fart!]
-[Laughter]
- Not like that!
[Gasps]
Mom? Dad?
ALL: Whoa!
Jake, this is the wrong way!
What are you guys
doing out there?
Jake-boy, you gotta save
your pop from the deadly sea!
I don't care for this
cocktail party one bit, Joshua.
We got to save 'em.
What are you looking at?
Don't you see Mom and Dad?
FINN: All I see is sea weeds.
You must be imagining it.
I'm not imagining it!
Uh-oh! We are heading
towards a scary thing!
Susan, help me push the boom.
[Both grunting]
No!
[Strains]
Use your core!
BOTH:
Aaaaaah!
No!
Remember we love you!
Even though you're
really letting us down.
Aah!
Hmm?
Yipes!
Jake keep talking about dog-mom.
His belly's swarming
with weird jellyfish.
They must be jacking up
his perception.
[Both gasping]
Mommy, I'm coming for you!
Huh?
What happened?
[Gasps]
Who are you?
Hope you like to fly!
You okay?
Uh...Susan's head hurts,
but Susan's head
always hurting these days.
All right.
Just another minor setback.
BMO, which way?
Finn, I want to turn back.
What? We can't.
The annoying dragon
wrecked our boat.
I got poisoned by jellyfish
and saw our dead parents.
I don't see things deescalating.
It's just a small bump.
A-A bunch of small bumps.
No dumb island
can be worth the risk.
Maybe not.
But I can't turn back.
This trip means
a lot to you, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, but why?
Do you want to find some humans
and ditch us?
No! It's just...
[Sighs]
Okay, look.
I'm really happy in Ooo.
I love our mom and dad,
but I don't know squat
about humans.
If I don't see this through,
part of me will always be stuck
to that boom boom leaf where
Mom found me...still alone.
I know exactly how you feel.
ALL; Aah!
You were here all this time?
Yeah, I was here all this time.
Sorry I broke your boat.
Sorry we said you were annoying,
or sorry for not telling you
you were annoying earlier.
If you're still set
on going to that island,
you should know that
that way is crazy dangerous.
I'm...I'm ready.
ALL: Us, too.
Then I can use my air bladder
to blow a mighty wind,
a real big wind that'll
carry you over all the dangers.
How come you didn't
do that earlier?
I thought we were having fun.
Also, they say no one's faced
the island's colossus and lived.
What colossus?!
Beware.
Beware the colossus of the deep.
FINN: That's not really
an answer, but we will.
WHIPPLE:
Here we go.
-[Inhales deeply]
- Wait a minute!
Byeee!
JAKE: Whoal!
BMO:
That's not right.
FINN: Aah!
JAKE:
Spooky.
But at least I don't see
no colossus of the deep.
[Nervous laughter]
FINN:
Oh, my Glob!
[All screaming]
This party is so crazy!