[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
s "Adventure Time" &
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
[Imitating siren]
[Creak!]
[Screams]
- BUBBLEGUM: Okay, how about now?
-[Clang]
FINN: Yeah, I can feel it.
But there's a little delay.
BUBBLEGUM: Hmm.
- How about now?
-[Clang]
Now I felt it
before you hit me.
Whoa! Really?!
Ha ha!
Just kidding!
It's fine.
Come on, now.
This is serious.
And expensive.
I've been working
on this new arm
since the last time
this happened,
so please don't blow it up
so fast this time.
[Chuckles]
We'll see.
Honestly, though, this doesn't
even feel that weird now.
I mean, maybe it's 'cause it
already happened once before,
but I don't know.
It feels like normal, I guess.
[Banana Guard clears throat]
FINN:
I mean, I know it's "serious."
-[Susan groans]
- FINN: Jake and Susan
and Rattleballs
all got pretty banged up.
But for me, I guess it's like...
I don't know.
It feels right or something.
What's weird, though,
is that grass guy.
Kinda rubs me
the wrong way, that one.
Yes, the mysterious grass guy.
Tell me again what happened with
the two of you this morning.
[Inhales exhales deeply]
Okay, so, as you know...
after Susan had gone crazy
and kicked Jake's butt,
my grass arm got steamed
and kicked her butt.
Then it ran off and merged butts
with my Finn Sword...
and turned into this guy,
and he starts talking smack!
ELRIRYEEEEERL
What?!
Mah! Mah!
Hey, man, you stay back!
Eeyuh!
Muh eeyuh!
- Muh eeyuh!
- Hey! I-I said stay back, man!
I seen what you did to Susan!
[Susan groaning]
[Straining]
Susan's...cells...are on fire.
Susah!
Susah?!
Hey!
[Panting]
Stop!
[Both grunting]
BOTH: You leave her alone,
you weirdo!
Susan's my friend!
Fruh...freh...
- Friend.
- What?!
Huh?
I said, "What?"
What did you say?
llWhu?ll
Oh. Okay.
My ears weren't working before
for some reason.
Or my mouth.
[Chuckles]
Sorry about that.
Also, why are you
dressed like me?
Get a life, man.
What?! You're dressed like me,
man! Geez!
Anyway, you just keep your hands
off of Susan, guy.
Susan?
Can you hear me?
It's Finn.
Susan?
Owwww!
No touch.
-[Gasps]
- FINN: Oh. Sorry.
[Susan groaning]
You keep your hands
off of my friend!
What are you on abou-
Aaah! Whoal!
-[Thud]
- Oof!
Don't worry, Susan!
[Both grunting]
All right, all right!
Enough!
Truce, truce!
[Groans]
[Both panting]
Sorry, dawg, but I can't
let you hurt Susan.
[Growls]
I wasn't gonna hurt her!
I was protecting her from you!
Me? But...I'm Finn Mertens, man.
I'm 100% hero.
Everyone knows that.
What?!
I'm Finn Mertens!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Sorry, man.
I mean, I'm flattered,
but...come on.
No, you come on!
JAKE: Finn!
Hold on, buddy!
I'm coming!
[Inhales deeply]
Jake! Boy, am I glad to see you!
This bozo keeps saying he's me.
Why don't you set him straight
and tell him
who the real Finn is.
That one.
What?
Yeah, I don't know what you are.
Some kind of
demon-plant thing, probably.
ButI --
Beating up on my poor brother
like some kind of demon!
-[Gasps]
- FINN: Yeah!
Show us your true form, demon!
Yeah, show us!
BOTH: [Chanting]
Show us! Show us!
[Chuckles]
[Grunts] Oof!
Whoa!
Yeah, it's a real mess out here.
We're gonna need
the huge ambulance.
Yeah, no.
(\\[o
No, the huge --
Put Banana Guard number 2
on the phone.
Well, go get him!
All right, all right.
I think I've heard
just about enoughhhhh...
to know that I need
to hear that all over again.
Why don't you
take it from the top?
Okay, so, as you know...
GRASS FINN; Hey, BMO.
[Screams]
[Gasping, whimpering]
[Rapid footsteps]
BMO?
[Pop!]
Oh, hey!
My nose is back.
[Sniffing]
Mmm!
Stinks good in here.
[Sniffs]
It's got that "big boy" musk.
Socks, trash, butt,
all the stinks of home.
Hal
Hey, what are you doing?
Get out of here!
Ha!
Man, I remember that day.
That was when BMO
lost control of the tank.
[Chuckles]
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Ha!
Aw-.
BANDIT PRINCESS:
Hey! Give me that!
What the crease?!
You gonna get it now, dude!
That's the Grass Sword!
Hyah!
What the hey?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
[Groans]
I hate this.
I liked it before.
SPIDER;
J Is waiting for the rising &
Who are you?
SPIDER:
Oh, you know, a curse.
An emissary from beyond.
Some kind
of grass octopus spider.
[Screams]
Grass Demon!
You're making me nervous, dude.
\ No!
0, no, no!
SPIDER:
Don't worry about me.
[Straining]
I am worrying about you!
Dude, stop this!
SPIDER: It's okay. I just
gotta do something here.
One sec.
FINN: Okay, just one more
[Muffled] second.
So, how are you today?
I'm good.
I want out of here, though.
I've pretty much done
all I can do in here.
You and me, we could do
a lot better out there.
I want out, too.
Let's do it.
Wait, do you mean out of the
sword or out of the cocoon?
[Chuckles]
Okay. I get it.
When we get out of here,
let me do the talking.
[Groans]
FINN: And then you asked me
to take it from the top.
So...that guy is definitely
an alternate-reality
evil doppelganger, right?
Huh.
(\\[o
He's not even
from a different timeline.
Finn, he's just you.
Yeah, you say that, but I'm me.
- So he's --
-[Telephone rings]
BMO?
-[Glass shattering]
- News flash, hotshot.
You're in the house,
and you're made out of grass,
and you're breaking my china,
and I'm scared!
What?!
This grass guy's scaring BMO!
Let's get him!
\WEEEEEEEEELL
I've got a crush on Jake.
[Old-timey music playing]
Oh, no, no, no.
I...can't...get...
anything right!
[Screams]
[Music continues, muted]
[Music slows]
JAKE:
Hey, weedy!
Hey.
Just let me suck around
a bit, okay, man?
No way, buster!
You're hurting BMO!
I'm okay!
Geeeeeeet outta here!
Come on, Finn!
Jake, uh, I'm still
processing all this.
JAKE:
United front!
Okay.
[Groans]
You scare BMO.
You muck up my mom's records.
You waste my br--
You waste my breakfast syr-
Breakfast syrup!
Hey!
Look at me when I'm mad!
Look at my eyes!
They're mad!
And they have to look in your --
Hey! They have to look
in your eyes!
Take my anger into your face!
You're a fraud!
You think you can fake Jake?
You can't fake Jake!
Cake, rake, lake,
hamburger steak!
Oh, man!
[Inhales deeply]
Oh!
[Panting]
You're a chum-bait!
Jake, no!
It's for fishing, BMO!
It's something
that fishermen use!
And he is onel
He's a chum-bait!
FINN: Hey!
Grass-me, do you want
a Finn cake?
But...
only Finns get Finn cakes.
That's true.
[Sniffs]
Wait.
[Sniffs deeply]
That's that good sugary trash,
like a big boy likes.
Oh, geez.
I really
fell off the horse here.
Maybe I'm not who I am.
Sure we are.
[Chuckles]
Weird days, man.
Give me a minute to catch up.
[Sniffles]
Hey, you gonna eat
that BMO cake?
[Tink!]
[Kch! Kch! Kch!]
My hands are still tacky
from breakfast syrup.
Hey, do you think
Grass Finn's loco?
I think he'll be okay.
He just needs a place to crash
while he figures some stuff out.
Okay.
[Shoring]
J Is waiting for the rising... &
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!