[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
[Gulls squawking]
[Rumbling]
[Groans]
[Coughs]
Jake?!
Susan?!
BMO?!
[Coughing]
Oh, hey there, fellas.
Have you by any chance
seen a cool dog
or a giant, smelly lady
come through here?
[Claws clicking]
Uh, are you guys being weird,
or is that normal crab stuff?
[Clicking]
Stupid crabs.
[Plunk!]
[Wind howling]
[Grunts]
Jake?!
Susan?!
Hello?
Burlap sacks.
Seed packets.
Oh.
[Exhales forcefully]
Now I can look like an idiot
while I freeze to death.
-[Howling stops]
- Woof.
Actually, these sacks
are really working a treat.
I'm sweating like
an everyday Susan in here.
Oh, I see.
That works, too.
What the...
Neat.
It's like the border to
the Ice Kingdom but not really.
[Wind howls]
Tush!
Coming down hard again.
I better head back.
[Wind howling,
electricity buzzes]
Shack?
Shack.
Sack?
Shack!
Ow! Oof!
Oh! Oh! Aah! Ohh!
[Thud!]
Ohh.
[Birds chirping]
[Animal squeaking]
Ruh-roh.
Looks like someone's
still living here.
[Chuckles]
Look at you.
You're thick as heck.
You're thicker
than a normal Susan.
Whoa!
Good grief, man!
Were you in on this?!
That's shady.
Do your parents know
what you do all day?
I mean, honestly.
[Leaves rustle]
[Heavy footsteps]
Giant bear?
Come on!
I fought The Lich at the edge
of space-time, man.
You're out of your depth.
You best just roll on, brah.
[Sniffs]
- Heyl
-[Growls]
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[Growls]
[Grunts]
[Groans]
See?!
I told you!
ALVA:
Stop! Nej, nej, nej!
[Speaking Swedish]
Bzzt!
[Buzzer]
FINN: Oof!
[Speaking Swedish]
Come, Albert.
[Water trickling]
Hmm.
FINN: Hey!
You're a human, right?
Do you know
where my friends are?
A dog, a robot,
and another human who smells --
and I've been saying this
a lot -- not great.
Does this mean I made it
to the human place?
-[Egg Whistling]
- Did you send for me?
Are you the mayor of here
or like the tribe leader?
I-I mean -- Agh.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'm saying.
[Whistling continues]
Hi.
Hmm.
Bzzt.
[Buzzer]
[Whistling continues]
Thanks.
Can I have
my backpack back...pack?
Huh?!
[Growling]
[Clicks tongue]
[Grunts]
Lady!
[Growls]
Lady, you can't just --
- Hmm...
- FINN: Oh!
[Yawns]
[Smacks lips]
(\\[o
No!
One last time, have you seen
my brother anywhere?
He looks like this.
This guy.
His name is Jake.
En hund!
Mnh.
Oh.
What?
You want me to draw you?
Oh.
I didn't draw
that picture of Jake.
I don't know how to draw,
really.
Banana Guard 16
tried to teach me once,
but it didn't stick.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
[scribbling]
[Sighs]
[Speaking Swedish]
-[Thunder crashes]
- Oh!
[Wind howling]
Ooh! Ooh-ooh.
Ooh. Ooh!
Het, het, het, het, het!
Het! Het, het, het!
What, a-are you folks afraid
of thunder?
[Screams]
Lady! I know a lot
about living in trees,
and this thing's not going to...
hold.
[Beep]
This place is teched out.
I should have known, I guess,
since you talked
to that net earlier.
You can't understand me,
can you?
Somethings been bubbling up
inside me.
I really want to say it
out loud,
but I've been embarrassed.
Okay.
Are crabs robots?
In what way
isn't a crab a robot?
I guess I understand
that BMO's not a crab,
but I don't understand
why BMO's not a crab.
Shh!
Lady, where did everyone go to?
Shh.
FINN: Hey, that's you!
Your name's Alva.
Hi, Alva.
Oh.
So that's it?
That's humans?!
We came all this way.
[Sighs]
It's just you and me, Alva.
And Susan, I guess,
if she's okay.
I don't know.
-[Howlin
g stops
- Huh? Pel
Hmm?
Sounds like the storm stopped.
[Objects rattle]
Hunden!
Hmm.
No sign of him.
BELGEECEIS
Jake!
Hyah!
[Electricity buzzes]
[Grunting]
FINN: Jake!
Hey, Jake!
Oh, hey, buddy.
Man, am I glad to see you.
Hold on a second.
[Grunts]
Man, this place sucks!
I got attacked by 19 giant crabs
in just the last 30 seconds.
Yeah, man.
I almost got eaten by this --
Hey, that's awesome.
Now let's get
the heck outta here.
Are they coming, too?
I'm not sharing my rations.
What?
No, this is Alva.
I-I think she's human.
Alva?
Have you seen my friends?
BMO and Susan?
JAKE: Oh, stuff, man.
That's the slow shake.
That's the universal
death gesture!
ALVA: Nej, nej!
[Speaking Swedish]
Oh, shoot, man.
More islands.
BMO and Susan must've washed
all up on one of all up of them.
Well, it looks like
there's only three more.
This shouldn't be too hard.
Right?
WAITER:
Sir BMO?
[Classy piano music plays]
Another Finn cake, sir?
Oui.
Ah, this is the life.
I wish you guys could be here,
too, on the moon.
And Susan, too, I guess.
She seems...fine.
This party is so crazy!