[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
J "Adventure Time" 7
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We're going to
very distant lands &
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end 7
J It's "Adventure Time" J
[Shoring]
[Snoring loudly]
[Snoring lightly]
Oh, it's you.
Meh.
[Slow motion]
Hi, everyone!
My babies!
[Power saw whirring]
[Crickets chirping]
Mashed potato?
Pie pie?
[Shoring]
[Snoring lightly]
TREE TRUNKS: [Laughs]
Okay, bye!
Hey, where'd you go?
I think I was visited
by aliens again.
Every few years, they stop by
and show me my hybrid children.
[Laughs] What?
Don't be jealous
of my alien consorts, Mr. Pig.
I love you the most.
[Chuckles]
All right, sweetie. Thank you.
[Smooches]
You gonna come with me
to Princess Bubblegum's
fireworks show tomorrow?
No, she vvizzed on our wedding.
I'm sorry, but she's
a fat fish in the sand.
I want to see
free fireworks, though,
and I want you to come with me.
Eh, all right.
[Smack! Squeal!]
[Up-tempo music playing]
[Music stops]
Science rules!
Here's some proof.
[Camera shutter clicking]
I'm doing the right thing.
[Warbling]
Free fireworks!
Right! Here we go!
[Applause]
[Whirl]
[Whistle!]
[Laughing]
Whoa-ho-ho-ho! Whoa!
Whoa-ho-ho!
Hey, where's my wife?
[Slow motion] What's that?
Meh.
[Hiss!]
[Chattering]
[Beatboxes techno beat]
Oh!
Hey, you blind, cream-faced,
lonely lighthouse keeper.
Stop hurting my space men
with your goo!
What?
How did you --
Keep your probes
out of my star children.
Tree Trunks, you don't know
what you're talking about.
TREE TRUNKS:
Don't you condescend to me,
you false idol.
You probed the wrong famiglia!
[Twinkle!]
Wake up.
The fireworks show
is a secret space war.
Get your goo out of my UFO.
Dude, this town
is full of kooks.
Save the galactic chitlins!
Oh!
"Meet Starchy
in that alley over there."
Cacaw! Cacaw!
I'll just ask this duck.
Excuse me, but --
STARCHY:
Don't be alarmed.
I am the disembodied voice
of the people,
and I have witnessed your fire.
If given the opportunity,
would you lead a small group
of resistance fighters
straight into the hornet's den?
You bet your wet booty.
Behold!
It's me, Starchy!
Oh.
[Whirl]
BOTH: Aaaaah!
Unh!
Starchy always screams.
TREE TRUNKS:
This is very elaborate!
Hello, everyone.
We have a new member
with us here tonight.
Please welcome Train Tracks.
ALL:
Welcome, Train Tracks!
Clap! Clap! Clap!
Clap! Clap! Clap! Clap!
Veritas Brigade!
Train Tracks has her own
incredible story to tell,
so let's let her talk.
Hi, Train Tracks.
lam a conduit for
an alien entity known as Booshy.
There's a 50/50 chance that
Booshy will speak through me
during this meeting.
[Gasps]
Oh, my gosh, it's happening.
[Grunting]
I love when Booshy shows up.
F-- F-- F--
[Deep voice]
It's Booshy. Hello!
ALL:
Welcome, Booshy.
On my planet, we speak in colors
instead of words.
Aw, stuff it, Booshy.
We've got a real experiencer
in our midst.
[Clicking tongue]
Do y'all have any guns?
Nope.
Raaah!
I don't have time
for campfire stories.
I'm a mother of six,
and they're in trouble
because Princess Bubblegum's
probing them.
Will you help me raise a ruckus?
ALL:
Of course we will!
Let's stink it up!
What in the --
Oh, my gracious.
A full-scale galactic invasion?
Well, let's see how well you fly
without your thing.
Aaaah!
[Whirl]
Oh, good night!
You're the devil's
hot little helpers.
Come get extinguished!
BUBBLEGUM:
What the funge, Tree Trunks?!
Girl,
you just crossed the big line!
Well, this is the people's
justi-i-i-
Holy!
...i-1-ice.
[Slow motion]
What should I do?
Booshy's only prison
is this wicked planet.
Yeah, well, join the club.
[Whirl]
[Slow motion] What?
Tree Trunks!
What is this place?
You already know.
[Gasps]
TREE TRUNKS: See?
They refuse to fight back.
[Retching]
[Grunts] What?
What?! What?!!
See, I told you.
What?!
Space men.
I'm really sorry, Tree Trunks.
I never meant to hurt anybody
with my space program.
It was supposed to seed
new candy kingdoms
on uninhabited planets
in case Ooo0 goes
straight-up dongbongles.
'Cause, like, confidentially,
there's a lot of ways
that could happen.
And when it does,
maybe I won't look so crazy
after all, you know?
I can help you find
a space for your goo.
You would do that?
You and I will never be friends,
but we can respect each other
as mothers
and as fellow believers
in the infinite promise
of the cosmos above.
Sure.
[Crickets chirping]
Oh, hello, darling.
Hello.
You can talk?
Yeah, there are websites
that teach you.
I wanted to tell you
that I did what you said.
We're going to fly
Princess Bubblegum's probes
back to our abandoned
home planet.
They'll have
all the space they need
to start
their new Candy Kingdom.
But our galaxy is so far away,
I won't see you again
for at least 40 years.
Take care of our alien babies.
Who the slop is this?!
This is my alien husband.
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!