[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
s "Adventure Time" &
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
FINN: When we catch that bandit,
I'm gonna be like...
[Grunting]
Then I'm gonna give him
just a wicked noogie,
then a lecture
on personal responsibility.
Then another noogie, like,
"Get that knowledge in there."
Yeah, dude,
but it's getting pretty late.
We might
got to catch him tomorrow.
Aww.
What do you think, Finn Sword?
Should we stay out
a little longer?
Should we do a sword trick?
Is that a better idea?
No looking.
I bet you can't do that
behind your back.
Like this?
Sword trick!
What a sword trick.
Finn Sword,
are you just loving this?
Oh, oh! I bet you can't do that
and freestyle some bars.
I can do that!
Hyup!
[Grunts]
[Rapping]
J It's the boy 7
JI-I'm a boy &
Whoa!
Aah! Finn Sword!
Oh, man.
[Panting]
Dude, we got to call it.
He's got to be around here
somewhere.
Finn!
[Echoing] Finn!
See?
Is that even an echo?
There's no way to tell.
Uh, swords don't talk.
Come on.
We can find you a new sword.
We do that all the time.
You don't understand.
That sword is like me.
Like a sword me.
I don't think I'm totally
scooping what you're pooping.
I'll make you a new sword
that looks like you.
We got a bun-ton
of arts and crafts stuff
lying around at the house.
BANDIT PRINCESS: [Sighs]
Yeah. Yeah.
That's that good-good.
Now Kkiss.
Mwah!
MERCHANT: & Pay it in the front,
pay it in the back 7
& Pack that dollar
in the dollar sack J
J They call me badfoot money
when I step in the street
Huh? Someone there?
I must just be nervous.
Probably because
I'm carrying around
these succulent money bags.
Got to go get these muchachos
in a bank.
Aah! Please, I'm so rich!
[Screams]
Waking up screaming again.
- FINN: Jake! Jake!
Breakup? Lich?
Me dying? You dying?
Other breakup?
Growing up?
Never growing up?
- Or spiders?
- It was a totally new nightmare.
I was in the woods and --
and I was gonna rob this guy.
Aw, that sounds like
a nasty guilt dream.
Here, this'll cheer you up.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do!
Take a look at this!
Dooooo!
What's this now?
JAKE: It's a sword
just like your old one.
I couldn't get your mouth right.
Sorry.
Thanks, dude.
SCIENCE CAT: Yo, Finn!
Hey, Science Cat.
It's time for
the daily brawl, remember?
[Sighs]
I don't think
I can make it today, guys.
But we came all the way here.
This is why Spearbear
even owns a watch.
It's fight o'clock, Finn.
It's fight o'clock.
Okay, okay, I'll come down.
[Grunts]
Aha!
Yah!
[Laughs]
Bye, guys.
Thanks for coming.
SCIENCE CAT:
Your heart's not in it, Finn.
He's right, isn't he?
Did I take Finn Sword
for granted?
Maybe I take a lot of people in
my life for granted, you know?
Talking to inanimate object.
Get a load of this guy.
[Humming]
[Yawns]
- Hey, man, you're still up?
- Yeah.
I'm afraid of having
another scary guilt dream.
Okay then.
Let's stay up.
We can put on
some up-tempo music,
and I'll set you up with
a brainy modern video game.
Here you go, buddy.
Have some tea.
FINN: Thanks.
This'll be fun.
Like the opposite
of a sleepover.
And TI'll stay up
with you all night if --
[Shoring]
Night, dude.
Hmm.
You kick open the chest.
It's a trap!
You've awakened the Demon Queen!
Fight the Demon Queen!
The Demon Queen cackles
and swats your arrows away?
Modern games are so intense.
How do I check my stats?
[Grunts]
Lady, you can't
come in this bank.
My whole job is
you can't come in this bank.
Oh, it is on.
[Grunts]
Don't kill me.
I've never known true love.
[Screams]
Oh, my Glob!
I wasn't even asleep that time.
- Jake!
-[Snores]
I think Finn Sword is trapped
in the village of Spiky People.
We got to go rescue him.
What?
Why come you know that?
That sword is me.
He's been sending me
psychic Finnmails
of sadness and fear
to my Finnbox.
We got to go save him.
It's really important to me.
Aah!
Do you ever take those off?
[Explosion]
[All screaming]
Oh, Glob!
What happened
to my peaceful world?!
It's Nacho Island Tuesday.
[Coughs]
Nacho bros, can you hear me?!
It's Kurt, nacho bros!
- FINN SWORD: Stop!
- Aah!
A talking sword?
I was keeping it on the DL,
but, yeah, I'm Finn Mertens,
a.k.a. Finn Sword,
a.k.a. sick of
your non-irie antics.
You can't be using me
to rob banks.
Hero use only.
CAMERON:
Bandit Princess!
I, Cameron,
mayor of Spiky Village,
along with the trustees
of Spiky Village Bank,
ask politely
that you put our gold
back where you got it
in exchange for
a pre-approved home loan
with 0% APR
for the first six months
and [coughs] APR
for the next 30 years.
Monthly processing fees apply.
What do you say?
-[Whispers indistinctly]
- You know what?
I just spoke to Ruby G,
who owns the bank,
and he said that we can out you
a bigger break on that loan.
I mean -- pfft! --
of course, right?
How about
we out you a break, huh?
I'll be cutting
and breaking you, Mr. Mayor.
[Laughs]
Oh, no!
I'm toast!
Aah!
OMG, you've ruined my life,
Bandit Princess.
Mine, too.
You've trashed my hero streak.
And T'll keep trashing it
over and over and over
until you can't remember
ever having done a good deed
in your life.
Why would you do that?!
I was born with rabies,
and my parents didn't love me
because they both had mono,
so now I do stuff like this.
-[Laughs]
CAMERON: Call my wife!
This is terrible.
Oh, we're gonna do so many
terrible things together.
It's gonna be hilarious
to watch you cry, Finn Sword.
Cry as you end lives
and steal from the weak.
- Bandit Princess.
- What?
I will find a way to kill you!
Hey, take a time-out, dude.
We got a lot of lives to ruin.
[Laughs]
Finn /2, if you can hear me,
this gray area wet wipe
is using me against my will.
Please find me soon.
Find me and use me
to slay this bleeble.
That's what I saw in my vision.
[Cries]
Finn and Jake,
you've come in my time of need.
Sharon, what's going on here?
A princess of bandits
stole our gold reserves,
and with a mighty sword,
she took off
with my husband's head.
- Mayor Cameron?!
[Wailing]
You guys got swords.
Why didn't you do anything?
Oh, this isn't a sword.
It's a massive hangnail.
I got one, too.
It hurts.
Can you hear me, Mr. Mayor?
Can you sense where this
bandit princess took your head?
ALL: Whoa!
FINN: We'll get
your husband's head, Sharon.
And the gold, please.
You think he knows
where he's going?
He made it seem that way.
Yeah, but maybe
he's like a chicken
when, urn -- when, you know.
When what?
What happens to chickens?
Uh, I forget.
Never mind.
FINN:
Like our chicken Lorraine?
- Finn and Jake!
- BOTH: Whoa!
Thank you for escorting me
back to my head.
Mr. Mayor, did you see
where Bandit Princess went?
That way towards Box Kingdom.
- Let's close the gap, Jake.
- You got it.
Good luck, yous two.
Oh, shoot!
Don't forget
to bring back my gold!
Dag!
Sharon's gonna be real upset.
BANDIT PRINCESS:
[Grunting]
[Cats yowling]
Ugh!
[Grunts]
Ha! ha!
Box Prince!
[Yowls]
[Laughs evilly grunts]
I'm gonna need all these boxes
to store my gold.
Give up now or join your prince
in the recycle bin.
FINN: Wait!
No recycling!
Hm. You looking for this,
| suppose?
- You okay, buddy?
- No, man.
This creep show
made me prey on the innocent.
Ooh!
This is freaking serious.
Jake, no matter what happens,
don't step in.
JAKE: [Gags]
Give me back myself, dude!
I'll slay you
with your own body!
Give this tranch
acute arthritis!
FINN: You gonna get
bopped in the brain!
- Dag! Useless.
- Eat it!
[Grunts]
- Finn!
- Stay put!
[Groans]
[Grunts]
Hey, gimme that!
What the crease?
You gonna get it now, dude.
That's the Grass Sword!
[Grunts]
Yah!
-[Shatters]
- Aah!
[Laughs evilly]
Finn!
Hang on, man.
I'll take care of this.
[Bandit Princess laughing]
Keep your busted sword.
Pfft!
Jake, why does this thing
happen to Finn?
BMO, it's a wooly bully world.
People be acting crazy always.
You mean some people are just
pure city sidewalk boom-boom
from a rat donk
and that's all there is to it?
Um, I don't know for sure.
Here's the sticker I made
of Finn's sword's face.
Thanks, BMO.
Yo, that's a spot-on drawing.
BMO: Did you notice
I got the mouth just right?
JAKE:
Uh, yes, I did.
Come on.
Let's get some air.
BMO:
Okay, I like air.
[Door closes]
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!