[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
Susan? I mean, Kara?
Seems like you're leading us
somewhere.
We're taking a ship
to Founders Island,
because judging by the state
of these facilities...
...Hub Island has been abandoned
for over a decade.
Dang, I missed big words.
This island is where I trained
to be a Seeker.
So, wait, why are we going
to Founders Island?
I'm taking you back to your mom.
BMO, would you talk
to this console?
I can't access it
without my implant.
Um...you knew my mom?
You're gonna just drop that?!
Her name is Minerva.
- She's a Helper.
-[Ding]
Oh, thanks, BMO.
Now let's try
and start this sucker.
[Horn honks]
What's happening?
Are we being arrested?
Don't worry, ladies. I'll get
you to your senior swim class.
TOGETHER:
Thank you, Dr. Minnie.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
[Gasps]
[Tires screech]
[Muffled voice] Hey,
it's not a crosswalk, ya know!
It's -- It's not a...
[Groans]
MAN: The end.
You have been listening
to "Wizards Way."
So I hear you guys wanna do
some explorin"?
Canteens. Cool.
So what do you got for me?
Credits?
I don't take credits.
I want gadgets.
See this gum?
It used to be a book on tape.
Gadgets.
Hmm.
[Whirring]
[Gasps coughs]
Hey, not bad.
I'll take it.
Get down to Basket Beach,
and I'll meet you at the boat
in 30 minutes.
-[Beep]
- Hey, there.
Uh, you got a couple of Hiders
headed for Basket Beach.
You're welcome. Bye.
Yah!
You startled me.
[Laughs]
We understand that you can
get us past the Seekers.
Yeah, but you just missed
today's boat.
We understand
that you like gadgets?
I do like them.
[Click]
Hello. Hello. Hello.
I don't like it.
I love it!
Tell ya what, get yourself
down to Basket Beach ASAP.
You're not coming with us?
Once I determine
you haven't been followed,
I will join you at the boat.
We insist you join us now.
Let's go to the beach.
DR. GROSS: Bring back
those Hiders, y'all!
[Alarm blaring]
Aah!
What do you got for me, Kara?
A sad ol' Hider
with two busted legs.
Oh, I love busted legs!
[Groans]
When will he be at full health?
Tomorrow morning.
Okay, I'll have a transport
here in the morning
to shuttle him to re-ed.
Re-education.
Oh, you're awake.
We set both your legs.
They were broken.
Other than that, you only have
psychological problems.
Well, I could've told you that.
- You don't look like a Hider.
- I'm not.
It was a wrong place,
wrong time type of deal.
It's true!
I love it here!
So. . .white hat.
- You're a Helper, huh?
- Yes.
I think that fella's
still alive.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Very funny.
If I don't see you before
tomorrow, enjoy re-education.
- You're leavin?
- I have things to do.
What am I gonna look at
when you leave?
Leave some flowers or somethin'!
These are in the trash?
- I think someone died.
- Oh, that's great!
You're trying to escape?
No! I'm --
Wrong place, wrong time?
No, no. I have to, uh...
- [crunch]
- Aah!
Aah!
- [Clank]
- Uhh!
Aah!
This is kind of a setback.
But nothing
a good night's sleep can't fix.
You're not sleeping tonight.
You've got a serious concussion.
- And I'm not sleeping tonight...
- [Click]
...because apparently you need
a babysitter.
- I'm not a baby.
- Okay.
Aah!
Keep those elevated.
I have to figure out a new
lineup for the JV curling team.
You wanna sign my cast?
Which one?
[Chuckles]
You're all right, Doc.
Hey, you know I'm not going
to re-ed tomorrow, right?
Oh, yeah?
I'll tell 'em this was
just a misunderstanding,
and then I'll glide out
the front door a free man.
Free to have dinner...with you?
If you wanted to.
I mean, I-I want to.
So what are you,
a con artist or something?
Yeah, you make it sound
so glamorous.
How about me?
How would you con me?
I wouldn't con you.
I wanna have dinner with you.
[Laughs]
Okay, but if you had to,
how would you do it?
Um, okay, you like
helping people, right?
So I'd get you
to feel sorry for me.
I'd act real pitiful.
I don't think that would work.
I mean, you're number one
at number two, after all.
-[Laughing]
-[Laughs]
You saw my underwear!
You're -- [Laughs]
MINERVA: Oh!
- MARTIN: You're all right, Doc.
[Pounding on door]
SEEKER:
Open up!
Sure thing.
Just a --
Give me a boost, Doc!
[Door clanks]
Oh, uh, hello, Dr. Campbell.
Prepare for re-education,
Mertens!
You got the wrong man, fella.
I've been helping beefcakes like
you catch Hiders for months.
We know you've been playing
both sides.
You think that's not hurtful?
Uh-oh. That was kind of
my only plan.
[Sobbing]
You finally ran out of quarters,
didn't you, Marty?
[Sobbing]
Poor little Marty!
[Sobbing continues]
MINERVA:
Hold up, guys!
Hey, I'm so sorry about this,
but I was completing
checkout forms for Mr. Mertens,
and it turns out
he's medically unfit for re-ed.
He's got a rare condition
called garbage body.
Uh, that sounds completely fake
coming from anybody but you,
Dr. Campbell!
[Laughs]
See you at the Fun Run!
That was breathtaking
con work, Doc.
So you gonna buy me dinner
or what?
J I heard that you loved me J
J But only for two weeks J
J To be hopeless or not to be [
s I'm weak with indecision J
J Could we begin again 7
J On a terrible date 7
J It would be
greatly appreciated by me 7
J I'll wear my normal shoes
this time &
J Then maybe you'd like me 7
J Better in the sunlight &
J If I built a raft &
> Will you stay with me then 7
J And fall in love
all over again? J
MINERVA:
Oh, I'm so late!
[Cooing]
I'll be home by 7:00.
Mwah!
Hey, can you run a load
of laundry?
You got it.
Should I order us
something for --
Veggie thali and a mango lassi!
[Tires screech]
[Crickets chirp]
[Laughs]
Yeah, that's Mr. Bear.
Pretty interesting guy, huh?
Where the heck is
Mommy's Indian food, huh?
[Laughs]
Hey, look what you got.
That's one of my old gadgets,
the breadstick wand.
-[Crying]
-[Running footsteps]
- That must be the grub.
-[Growls]
End of the line, Mertens!
We're here for vengeance!
- [Chirps]
- Ha!
J Hot breadsticks is
what we bake 7
; We don't bake pie
and we don't bake cake 7
- & Breadsticks... &
- You pathetic man.
Uhh!
Don't worry. Daddy's got a raft
stashed around here somewhere.
-[Door opens]
- MINERVA: Hey, guys!
-[Light switch clicks]
- I'm ready for that thali --
Martin?
Finn!
[Growls]
Mertens!
Phew!
Let's give Mom a text.
Yeah, I guess we'll just circle
around the island and see if --
[Thunder crashes]
-[Crying]
Freaking Back to Nature Island!
Let's -- Let's just wait out
the storm, and then...
Aah! The Guardian!
No, I'm not trying to leave!
-[Crying]
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Don't worry.
Daddy's always got a plan.
[Lights clank]
- Finn, I'll be back for you.
-[Ding]
Here comes the rascal!
Oop! Wait, wait. Wait! Uh-oh.
Aah!
- [Thud]
- Uhh!
[Glass shatters]
-[Beeping]
- Hello. Hello.
Hello.
J Hot breadsticks
is what we bake J
; We don't bake pie
and we don't bake cake 7
I can't believe that of all
the hundreds that have tried,
the gallbag that finally
makes it past the Guardian
is Martin Mertens!
[Voice breaks]
I don't understand.
[Whirring]
- [Thud]
- Aaayyy!
[Whirring]
Hey.
Oh. Hey, what's up?
Nothing. I just haven't
said anything in a while.
This party is so crazy!