[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
s "Adventure Time" &
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
Hmm. "Make more friends
with sing-talking."
J; Hey, there, Finn J
; Whatcha reading? &
It's @ manuscript about
the legend of Dead Mountain.
Supposedly,
if you get to the top,
there's a treasure
that will change you
into the person
you always wanted to be.
[Laughs]
That's a dumb story.
I love dumb stories.
What would you change
about yourself
if you got that treasure?
Fix your weird cursed grass arm
so it wouldn't be weird
and cursed?
Nah.
I'd like to be taller.
How tall we talking about?
I don't know.
Like, couple of inches.
Say, tall as Princess Bubblegum?
Oh, I see.
Jake, how would you change
yourself on Dead Mountain,
if only the legends were true?
I wouldn't change anything.
I'm the whole package.
Whoa!
Hey, there's a big warning
about Dead Mountain in here.
See?
It says some kind of evil hermit
guards the mountaintop.
"Don't let him look at you, or
something horrible will happen.”
That seals the deal.
The twin temptations of getting
to grow a couple of inches
and battling an evil hermit
sound like a pretty perfect day.
Let's go!
Shh!
[Whispers]
Let's go.
BOTH:
[imitating whooshing]
Gear up for battle!
You smell like cattle!
You smell...like cattle!
Monsters that get you by
looking at you are so "doomb."
Everybody knows all you need
iS @ mirror.
They ought to get a new gimmick.
[imitating whooshing]
There's the evil hermit's,
uh, what is that? A hut?
No, it's a yurt.
BOTH: Yah!
-[Rats squeaking]
Rats!
[Both groan]
Is that the hermit?
We don't get to fight
the hermit.
Hey, look.
What is it, boy?
The treasure.
Okay, here it goes.
Oh, great treasure,
make my taste buds think
they're tasting fried chicken
even when I eat
my fruits and vegetables.
I don't have any fruits
or vegetables on me.
I guess I'll find out later
if that worked.
Your turn.
Oh, great treasure,
I want to be approximately
11.5 inches taller.
Gross. It's leaking.
[Rats squeaking]
This place is depressing.
And I'm not growing taller.
There's nothing going on here.
[Echoing]
On top of Dead Mountain!
We should have known better
than to trust a book.
Yeah.
He makes one cool skeleton,
though.
These shades...
Let me check out these shades.
[Rumbling]
[Zap!]
Aah! Ohh!
-[Glass shatters]
- Finn!
[Groans]
Huh? Jake?
You're awake!
Oh, I was so worried.
I've been waiting
with a bowl of soup.
It has hoops and loops
and maybe some goop.
What happened? I don't remember
getting into bed.
Don't worry.
You're gonna be fine...
...iIn no time.
Thanks for taking care of me.
You're the greatest
big brother ever.
W-Why are you doing that?
I'm not.
You're awake! You want some tea?
Or saltine crackers?
BMO, you're my little angel.
[Gasps]
I'm a real boy!
With wings!
And a halo!
[Laughing]
Oh!
What's happening?
I don't know, but it probably
has something to do
with your weirdo eyes.
Something is wrong with my eyes?
Aah! Hermit eyes!
Dead-hermit eyes!
Heh, it's fine.
Do you think
the hermit did this...
to punish me
for grabbing his shades?
I think maybe the eyes
are the treasure.
So, then, am I making people
what they want to be?
No, because I don't want to be
this awesome sweater bro.
But maybe that's how you see me.
Hey, dudes.
Nice eyes, Finn.
What's the word?
What's the haps?
[High-pitched voice]
What's your major?
[Laughing]
Whoa!
Do you see Shelby
as a bookish nerd?
SHELBY::
You're a nerd.
I don't know. Maybe.
Is that bad?
[Telephone ringing]
Hello?
Hi-ya, PB.
What's up?
You need help with your speech?
An emergency?!
On our way.
Let's roll, varsity Jake.
Ah, ah.
Before we go...
Until you figure out
how to use them,
keep those peepers covered.
BUBBLEGUM:
What to wear for my speech.
Boss next door or hot president?
Is this
what you needed help with?
No, I think I got this.
Oh!
Hi, Finn and Jake.
You guys look...cool.
You trying out a new look?
Anyways, I'm preparing
for a very important speech
about the benefits
of candying vegetables,
and I need you guys to take care
0-0-0-0-0-f that.
Help Starchy set up chairs?
No, no, no.
That.
Oh, boy.
We're on it, Princess.
It's probably nothing.
He's been good lately,
but it's a big speech, you know.
[Chewing]
Ohh. Ah.
BOTH:
Hey, Ice King!
Aah!
I'm not doing anything Wrong.
I was just lady-watching.
[Zap!]
- Ow!
Oh, no.
Where'd my muscles go?!
I'm a scrawny-armed loser!
[Crying]
That's how you see him?
That's beautiful.
Sure, I-I mean, it's --
it's hard not to sometimes.
Where'd those glasses go?
There.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Starchy!
Give those back, you thief!
Huh?
No Way!
Starchy looks good!
Starchy, you butt!
Ohh!
Oof, sorry.
What's going on here?
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Can you explain this?
I don't know.
I'm not a psychiatrist.
Come on.
Let's get you home, dude.
Peebs, good luck
with the speech.
But...
[Sighs]
Teen boy heartthrob it is.
Okay, at least now we're safe
from you donking up
any more of our friends.
Nobody got hurt.
Have any of you guys seen BMO?
[Screams]
Did I kill Neptr?!
You turned him into a microwave.
So...yeah, you kind of did.
But -- But -- But that's not
howl| see Neptr, is it?
I like Neptr.
He's like my half-son.
If I was a better person,
would I be turning my friends
into better things?
Am I uncaring, judgmental...
Uh, Finn.
FINN:
...self-centered, monstrous?
I'm--I'm...
I'm a huge wa-a-a-a-a-d!
Finn!
You're being melodramatic!
[Sighs]
FINN:
I know it's you.
Hey, buddy, I figured
you'd come back here.
FINN:
Don't look at me, Jake.
I might turn you
into a microwave.
Baloney!
You turned Neptr
into a microwave
because he's a microwave.
But that doesn't mean
that's all he is to you.
I know you think Neptr
is an interesting person,
and I know that "microwave"
is just one part
of his personality.
I mean, maybe your eyes
are just bad
at describing things, you know?
Like, how you feel about people,
what they mean to you,
that stuff's in your guts.
Eyes can't grok that...
unless you have the eyes
of, like, a trained artist
or something.
But you don't.
I'm telling you, man,
you're not a bad dude
like this skeleton bro,
or you'd be turning everyone
into rats and plops.
[Farts]
[Finn breathes deeply]
JAKE: Now, come on.
Look at me.
Jake, you're so wise.
What?!
[Stammers]
Well, at least
you're listening to me.
And wise, old Jakey got a plan.
P.B., you want to go first?
He may not be
the most cunning soldier,
but one thing about Finn
is that he always puts
other people first,
and that makes him a true hero.
Finn helped Starchy fart once.
[Chuckles]
What a lifesaver.
Finn's a mean, old party pooper.
Oow!
But he is the hottest guy
in Ooo0,
so he can kind of do
what he wants.
Finn's just the best guy
to do bro stuff with,
like lying on the grass
and talking to bugs
or baking
chocolate chip cookies.
Finn's just a good friend.
[All talking at once]
I'm me again.
These balls are going nuts.
[Ringing, clacking]
- Uh..
-[Dlng']
My son.
[Warble!]
[Ding!]
Eye piel
ALL: Ew!
Good job, Neptr.
You saved the day.
Neptr! Neptr!
ALL:
Neptr! Neptr! Neptr! Neptr!
Yay!
[Whistle!]
I just had
the most wonderful dream.
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!