[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
[Sharling]
DR. GROSS: Kara.
Kara. Kara!
Yes, Dr. Gross?
That's quite
a scenic landscape out there,
but was it always so lush?
No, it used to be
a desert island.
Very good, Kara.
It was once barren,
but we intervened.
Like all of the islands,
we helped it grow.
And do you Seekers know why?
J We had to leave our place
because &
J; The world was dyin' &
J And everyone
that wasn't dead »
J Spent all of their time
cryin' J
J Our ways had failed,
nature had failed 7
J We made a lot of errors J
s The Founders had
some new ideas J
J That made everything better &
s The Founders dreamt
of this island 7
J Our ships landed
on its shore &
J They built
our wonderful Guardian &
J To keep destruction
from our door &
s The Hiders
fear these new ideas 7
J But do your best
to help them 7
J 'Cause just outside
is darkness and death 7
J Disease, monsters,
and problems ;&
J So come out
of your hiding place &
J Come out of the darkness &
J And we'll find a new way 7
J To live by the light
of the Founders &
Let's get to today's lesson.
[claps]
[Whirring]
Please load lesson 38B.
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
Educating. Educating.
-[Ding]
- Lesson uploaded.
Yes, power up!
DR. GROSS: All right, Seekers,
remember your homework.
50 deadlifts by tomorrow.
KARA: So how's your Experimenter
classes going, Frieda?
Eh. It's all intro stuff
for kids.
Look at this janky thing.
[Babyish voice]
I'm a dumb toy for babies!
[Normal voice] Experimenter
stuff's just boring.
Boring can still be important.
It's all part
of the Founders' plan.
Are you freestyling
your own verse
to that nerdy Founders song?
No, but that song
is deeply satisfying.
Chillax, K-Bot.
You're getting big and hunky.
Yeah! Being a Seeker's great!
I love my beefy...bod.
Heh.
TOGETHER; Aah!
FINN: Oh hey,
I think it...stopped!
-[Thud]
- Uhh!
Aah! Ohh!
- BMO: Wheel
- Aah!
BMO: Huh. This was more fun
in my dreams.
FINN:
Dudes, I found Susan!
Susan!
JAKE:
Susan.
What's up with her, man?
I think she's sleepwalking.
Let's just find out
where she's going.
[Haltingly]
Find them, catch them.
DR. GROSS:
Find them, catch them!
Bring back those Hiders, y'all!
Your implants have made you
stronger and better!
Wait! I'll help you!
- Hey there! Wink!
-[Ding!]
Hmph.
You didn't think that was cute?
Hatcha!
Come on,
I'm innocent, I tells you!
I'm just a handsome bystander!
[Thud]
Aah!
Ooh!
[Whimpers]
ALL:
Kara! Kara! Kara!
Find them! Catch them!
Help them!
Find them!
Catch them! Help them!
MAN ON P.A.: New patient
for Dr. Minerva on Deck 3.
What do you got for me, Kara?
A sad ol' Hider
with two busted legs.
Oh, I love busted legs!
[Chuckles]
When will he be at full health?
Tomorrow morning.
Okay, I'll have a transport
here in the morning
to shuttle him to re-ed.
[Yawns]
[Joints POP]
[Door whooshes]
[Mattress creaks]
JAKE:
What's she doing?
I think she's, uh, getting ready
to sleepwalk-sleep.
Man, this island is nasty.
Who'd want to live here?
[Being]
You know, there are people
on the other side of the world
that are never gonna see
these stars.
That's bunk, Frieda.
We're the only people left.
The islands are like
a beautiful safe haven.
I've read all the old stories
about 'em, you know?
About other places and people.
I'd like to see those places
one day and meet those people.
They can't all be monsters.
You can't say that, Frieda.
Oh, relax.
I'm just globbin'.
Hey, watch this.
[Beep]
[Static crackles]
[Laughs] That's not
what I look like.
Yeah, it is!
Come on, flex!
[Laughs] See?
-[Static crackles]
- Wow. Am I really that buff?
I look great!
Don't you just love this place?
Yeah.
[sigh] Yeah.
Okay, class,
before we start today's lesson,
I need to announce
that we're missing
a number of contrapulators
and an expensive
unilateral phase detractor.
If you're using these items
for personal projects,
you need to first equip them
in your character file, okay?
Since today is Founders Friday,
we're going to sing
our Founders Song.
I have to go pee!
DR. GROSS: Kara!
[Panting]
-[Metal jangles]
- Frieda?
Frieda, no!
What are you doing?
Go back to class, Kara.
You didn't see me.
- Stop running!
- Stop chasing!
- KARA: Omph!
- FRIEDA: Aah!
[Loud thud]
[Groaning]
Frieda, are you trying
to leave us?
Leave me?
I was gonna write a note.
Listen, someone might see us
out here.
We can talk in that cave.
Wha--
No, you don't have to carry me!
[Gasps]
Uhh!
KARA:
What is that?
It's a foolproof way outta here.
But why?
We're safe here.
We have no freedom, Kara!
I want to see what's out there.
It's all just bad stuff
out there.
- You're only gonna get hurt.
- Maybe.
But maybe getting hurt
isn't the worst thing there is.
I want to be me.
And that's never
gonna happen here.
- Frieda, I'm sorry, I just --
- But you can help me!
I'm only missing
the engine now, see?
And you're so strong,
you can carry it in one trip.
This is...
I have to go...think.
Uh, okay.
I'll be here.
Hey, Kara. You're not gonna
tell on me, right?
It's gonna be okay.
Dr. Gross?
Kara! My teacher's pet.
And you know I mean that
in @ good way.
Listen, um, sorry about
running off earlier.
When you gotta go, you gotta go.
But that's not really what
you wanna talk about, right?
Well, you know how
you always say
that humans will find
the best way?
The Founders get credit
for that bit of wisdom.
If someone found a way
that's, uh, different from ours
but seems to work for them,
couldn't that also be
a good way?
Ah. You've heard some
Hider preaching, haven't you?
Well, listen, kid.
We tried exploring
the outside world,
and we were almost destroyed!
We're the last humans,
so it's our responsibility
to stay here,
and it's your responsibility
to help these misguided Hiders.
Right.
[Loud clank]
- Your engine.
- You just broke it!
- What?!
-[Laughs] I'm kidding.
It must weigh, like, a ton.
How would you have done this
[Grunts] without me?
I don't know,
maybe roll it on tubes
or find
some hunky Hider somewhere?
Mm, you better hurry.
I'll give you a push off
so they don't hear the engine.
Come with me, Kara.
Frieda, I'm --
DR. GROSS: Kara!
Thanks for the tip,
my loyal, faithful Seeker.
Go fetch.
[Electricity surges]
Kara?
[Robotic voice]
Target acquired.
Aah! Kara, no!
Stop! Ow!
- Initiate grabbing.
- Ah!
Eliminating transport.
No! Stop it!
Don't! No!
[Crying] Why?
Oh, Kara, why?
No. [Sobbing] Why?
DR. GROSS:
That's enough, X3-7-7.
Let's go home.
[Humming Founders song]
JAKE:
I'm pretty sure she's awake.
She's got that "focused stank"
about her.
Susan, are you okay?
Kara.
My name is Kara.
[Wind Whistling]
This party is so crazy!