[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
KARA: We're closing in on
Minerva's brainwave signature.
We should touch down
in just a few minutes.
Whoa.
So, that's what my mom's
thoughts look like.
They look good.
I think.
Hold on.
Whoa.
That's her?
KARA: Mm-hmm.
Dr. Minerva.
She looks nice.
[Beeping]
We're here, Finn.
Buckle up.
I'm gonna take us down.
FINN:
Humans.
There's so many.
Are they friendly, Kara?
The people here?
[Chuckles] Don't worry.
You're gonna fit right in.
KARA:
Finn? Finn?
Hey, listen.
I remember enough
about my old life
to know that there were
some dangerous people here.
So let's stick together, okay?
And let's all try
to keep a low profile.
Minerva! Minerva!
Hey, you, where's Minerva?
Wha! Geez.
You scared me
with that costume, citizen.
Don't change the subject.
Now, where's Minerva?
And does she have any chips
or crackers or anything?
I'm getting real tired
of picking batteries
out of these BMO cakes.
Where's Minerva?
Man, that's
a pretty weird question.
Minerva's everywhere.
Additionally,
everyone knows that.
Just look around for
somebody who needs help,
and Minerva will be there
helping, obviously.
"Where's Minerva?"
[Chuckles]
- Thanks.
- She's everywhere?
You hear that, man?
Minerva's into helping people,
just like you.
She must've gave you
her helper genes as DNA
up in her womb
with your placenta.
DN-what-what?
Mister? Can I rub
your dog's tummy, mister?
He's got a cute yellow tummy.
Shoot, kid,
you don't even have to ask.
Just scooch right up
and get busy.
[Gasps]
You're a talking dog!
Teesa, Meeka, Gee-gee,
come look!
A talking dog!
Are they gonna help
with the tummy rub?
-[Kids giggling]
- Finn, look.
Oh, geez.
I didn't think
we would find her so fast.
We can come with you
if you'd like.
Nope.
[Breathes rapidly]
Finn only.
Hello, young man.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
[Breathes deeply]
This is gonna sound weird,
but...
And I don't mean
to put you on the spot.
But, uh...did you...
Did you lose...
a son?
Careful, citizens.
Litter can be unattractive
but dangerous, as well.
- Uh...
- Hello, young man.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
This is going a lot different
than I pictured it.
JAKE:
Come on, now.
Are you telling me none of you
has ever seen a talking dog
before?
That's crazy.
That's even crazier
than the old lady
who lives alone
on that Weather Island.
[Laughter]
[Laughs]
No, but seriously,
if you think this is impressive,
you should've seen me
at the flea circus.
I really stole the show.
[Laughter]
[Chuckles]
Nah, but seriously,
y'all should really
meet my friend BMO.
[Whispering] Jake.
JAKE:
He's a talking calculator.
Now's not the time.
JAKE: Now, there's a friend
you can really...
- Whoop!
- JAKE: ...count on.
[Laughter]
Frieda.
JAKE:
Wow, listen, you guys are great.
I got to get going
and find my friends,
but, man, what a great crowd,
though, seriously.
One more joke.
- Yeah, come on!
- Yeah!
[Chuckles]
That's all I got.
I don't know any more jokes.
ALL:
Awww!
Wait, wait.
I can do other stuff
besides jokes.
Like, um, oh.
[Inhales deeply]
Pbbbbbbbbbht!
Huh?
- Mutant!
- Mutant.
- He's a mutant.
- Is he a mutant?
What? No, no, no.
I'm just a regular dog, see?
-[Pants]
-[Gasps]
- He's a mutant.
- A mutant!
- Minerva!
Minerva!
FINN: I guess this must be
pretty shocking.
Oh, are you in shock?
Do you need help?
MAN:
Minerva!
Hey.
- Minerva!
- Minerval!
- Minerva, help!
Oh, hey, Minerva.
Finn, I found Miner--
Uh, disregard.
You are creating a disturbance.
Please help let us help you
help us to sedate you.
I'm not a mutant.
I'm magic.
I think.
- Although, now that you men--
-[Poke!]
[Groans]
FINN:
Stop! He's my brother!
- And I'm...
-[Poke!]
...your suhhh...
[Thud]
Son!
What's this?
[Grunts]
You can't get them off.
I tried a lot already.
I love you, but your mom's
a hundred robe-clones.
Those things aren't my mom.
Maybe they look like my mom
because they did something
to her, right?
I'm going to get out of here
and I'm going to rescue her,
and I'll hug her, and -- and --
I've had weirder fights
than this.
Where the bones?
Thas muh hand.
[Whirs]
[Click!]
[Ding!]
[Gasps]
[Both gasp]
[Horns honking]
Uh...
[Pop!]
BMO:
It's a toy store!
Are you going to buy me a toy?
(\\[o
Well, maybe.
I have to talk
to my friend first.
BMO:
Mm-hmm.
I made a mistake
a long time ago.
My friend got hurt.
I don't know if I'm allowed
back in her life.
BMO:
Mm-hmm.
Where are we going, man?
[Splashing]
What is this?
Am I dreaming?
Who are you?
Uh, my name's Finn.
Are you my m--
It is you.
Oh, my gosh,
I can't believe you're alive!
Minerva-bot, hug my son.
You're beautiful.
[Laughs]
My My, baby Finn!
Oh, you're so big.
Last time I saw you,
you were 6.875 kilograms,
and now look at you!
Mom...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm babbling.
Yes, darling?
What happened to you?
You've been gone for so long.
When you and Martin
disappeared,
I was left
fragile as an eggshell.
Martinis a Hider.
He left with our baby.
Dr. Gross was resolute.
She immediately activated
her most powerful Seeker
to bring you back.
But years went by.
You and your father
were never coming back.
Dark days grew darker.
I went into myself,
and while I retreated,
Dr. Gross's work turned
strange and dangerous.
Aroo?
Dr. Gross's actions
unwittingly led
to the release of
a terrible virus.
[Glass shatters]
It was the most
catastrophic event
that had happened to our
species in 300 years.
We tried to consolidate
and quarantine everyone
on Founders Island.
The fatality rate in the
general population grew to 62%.
But the fatality rate
in Helpers,
those who faced the virus
daily, was 100%.
Or nearly.
I was only one Helper
and in no condition
to do my job.
[Coughs]
I made my decision.
With my brain-map
uploaded to the web,
I could be hundreds of Helpers.
And humanity needed help
above all else.
Since that day,
I have protected
and cared for all my people
the best I could.
[Sniffles]
But that all doesn't
matter anymore.
You're back!
And now you can live here
in safety.
Oh, but I can't necessarily --
For the rest of your life.
This party is so crazy!