[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
s "Adventure Time" &
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
[Sighs]
Poor Finn Sword.
I'm sorry, man.
Everything's broken.
No, it's not!
This is still good.
Five seconds rule.
I don't know what to do.
This is hecka serious.
Did you try making
"feel better" waffles?
Yeah, but he just keeps dropping
them on the ground,
and we're all like,
"It's still good. Look."
Well, yeah, five-second rule.
[Sighs]
Jake, I think it's time for you
to activate plan C
[Gasps]
Plan "C"?
Are you sure?
BUBBLEGUM: Yes.
He's all jefferied up
in the dome piece.
We can't let it spread
any further.
You're right.
Plan activate.
[Sniffs 989%]
Plan "C," Plan "C"...
Aha.
Bingo. Hm.
[Telephone rings]
Hello?
JAKE: What's plan again?
Something about music?
[Sighs]
Poor Finn Sword.
- I'm sorry, man.
-[Soft majestic music plays]
What the heck is that?
It's gonna distract me
from my sword staring.
Better track down the source
and kill it.
J I'm gonna fly &
J Fly like an eagle J
J; With the power of myself &
J Constant pain J
J I'm gonna climb 7
J Every mountain &
J Get the dust off my shelf &
s Ohhhh 7
Oh, hold on.
Hold on.
Can Susan get more bass
in the monitor?
You got it, "Sooz."
Oh!
Oh '
, hey, buddy!
We are going live in five!
What is this?
A concert?
Even better.
It's a Battle of the Bands!
And guess who the special
celebrity guest judge is?
Donny?
No, you are!
[Chuckles nervously]
BOTH: [Whispering]
It's working.
Good afternoon
and welcome to plan "C" --
I mean, Battle of the Bands.
[Cheers and applause]
Now, let's all give
a warm welcome
to our celebrity guest judge!
[Chuckles nervously]
-[Camera shutter clicks]
- ICE KING: Hey.
Yo, my man, no photos.
Please welcome our first
contestants to the stage,
Emcee Neptr and Flame P.
-[Hip-hop beat plays]
- BOTH: Yo, yo, yo, YO, YO, Yo.
Battle of the Bands.
What up?
Make some noise!
[Cheers and applause]
- Turn it up!
- Turn the music up!
[Rapping]
J Hey, yo, my name's F.P., J
J And I came to take names &
-[Rapping] & Take names ;&
FLAME PRINCESS;
J I'm nice with the mike &
BOTH: & And I'm spitting
straight flames [
J These other emcees
be spitting &
- BOTH: J Straight lies &
-2 I'm a mac on the track &
> I'm known to bake pies &
J Bake pies [
BOTH: & When we come through,
respect the emcees 7
s The name of the crew's
Neptr and F.P. J
J Everybody knows
we not gonna stop here J
J 'Cause we got the freshest
album of the year &
[Cheers and applause]
Wow.
I wonder how long
they practiced that.
Don't forget to check out
our merch table.
FLAME PRINCESS: Yeah! We have
CDs and T-shirts for sale.
Oh, nice.
Hey! They're trying to bribe
the celebrity guest judge!
So much talent here today.
Please help us welcome our
next contestant to the stage,
Marceline the Vampire Queen.
[Cheers and applause]
[Drum beats]
[Guitar strums]
[Mid-tempo rock music plays]
J I don't know
what to do without you 7
;I don't know
where to put my hands J
J I've been trying
to lay my head down ;&
J But I'm writing this
at 3:00 a.m. J
J I don't need the world
to see J
J That I've been
the best I can be J
J But I don't think &
s I could stand to be [
J Where you don't see me J
[Guitar twangs]
- My pick!
-[Music stops]
I am not playing without it.
[Inhales deeply]
Ahhh.
This song is incredible.
Unless something amazing
happens,
I do believe we have a winner.
Huh?
Dude, I slew a freakin' bone
demon for that thing. Come on!
Hey, sooner you find it, sooner
we can get on with the show.
[Soft majestic music plays]
Where is that music coming from?
Hey, Marceline.
Where's that beautiful music
coming from?
Uh, what music?
They're still looking
for my pick.
You mean you don't hear that
right now?
Are you all right, dude?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
We're not gonna get points
deducted for this, are we?
[Violin plays]
J Everyone stuffs their buns &
J Empanada, mandu, wonton J
-[Humming]
J 'Rogi, dumplings,
stuff your face &
J Same food, different place &
Guess the song wasn't coming
from them.
JAKE:
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be
judging the bands. Hmph!
- Do you guys hear that?
- Hear what?
It's like a beautiful voice
singing with itself.
An entire universe vibrating
in harmony.
BOTH: HmMmm.
[Speaking Korean]
Yeah, are your ears ringing?
Yeah, guys.
Hold that thought.
Wait, Finn!
[Spectators
shouting indistinctly]
Just play something already!
Find my pick, ya scrubes!
Ohm!
[Spectators shouting loudly]
All right, all right, everyone.
Calm down!
I'm yelling.
I'm yelling up here.
Simon, what are you doing?
Crowd control, ma'am.
ALL:
Wenk, wenk, wenk, wenk!
Control the scene!
Oh, boy.
[Soft majestic music
continues]
- Hey, Finn.
- Yeah!
Oh, hey, Jakey, Lady.
- We're coming with.
- Nice!
Can you guys hear the song now?
Uhhhhh...
[Spectators
shouting indistinctly]
[Bubblegum humming]
Oh, excuse me.
[Gasps]
Yo, Marcie!
Thanks, Peebs!
[Rock music plays]
J And autumn comes
when you've not yet done J
J With the summer passing by [
- PENGUINS: Wenk! Wenk!
Aah!
Wenk!
J But I don't think &
s I could stand to be [
J Where you don't see me J
[Cheering]
[Chuckles] Nice.
So, what'd you think, Finn?
Did we slay, or did we slay?
[Spectators
shouting indistinctly]
Aw, what?
WEELY
Lady, how are we doing on time?
Can we make it back in time
to judge the bands?
[Speaks Korean]
Look, I bet if we just walk
a little farther -- [Gasps]
It's so close!
[Soft majestic music
continues]
It's herel
-[Gasps] Ooh!
- Finn!
[Echoing]
Oh, my Glob.
Finn, you okay?
I can't believe I almost fell
into this...hole.
It's a face hole.
This is where
the song's coming from.
MUSIC HOLE:
[Clears throat]
Oh.
Nice pipes.
MUSIC HOLE: Wait.
Can you hear me?
I've been hearing you,
like, all day.
You're a lovely singer.
MUSIC HOLE: [Giggles] Really?
No one's ever said that.
- Shut up.
- FINN: It's true!
MUSIC HOLE: Well, I've, uh,
had a lot of practice.
1,000 years give or take.
Say What?!
MUSIC HOLE:
Yeah, I've been here singing
from the very beginning of Ooo.
Since I can't move
from this spot,
singing is my only outlet.
I can neither participate in joy
nor prevent disaster,
so I sing.
Is this like
one of those patterns
that's supposed to have
a 3-D image in it,
and everyone can see it
except you?
Well, why can't they hear you?
MUSIC HOLE: Only two kinds
of people can hear my song,
those who see the world
with pure, childlike wonder
and those with a deep sense
of loss in their hearts.
To everyone else,
I'm just a period in a sentence
in the book of Ooo.
I don't know about child eyes,
but I have been going
through a rough patch.
And it sounds like
you have, too.
MUSIC HOLE:
Yeah, I guess so.
[Spectators
shouting indistinctly]
Now's our chance.
- [Disco music plays]
- & Boogaloo 7
- Hey!
-[Shouting stops]
J You keep on dancin'
through the night
J You never, ever get uptight &
J You know
that everything's all right J
J Because you've dancing J
J You had a boogie-woogie day ;&
-[Shouting resumes]
J And now it's time
to make a play 7
J You got to find a better way 7
J You've got to do the,
do the, do the, do the ;&
] [M- Ooh!
usic stops]
MUSIC HOLE: You know what?
I envy you.
I've always wanted
to be heard by everyone.
That's what friends are, right,
just people to observe you,
people to enjoy your song?
Hey, bud.
Yeah.
I'm lucky.
Jake, I've selected the winner
of The Battle of the Bands.
[Clears throat]
The winner is
a very special someone
who I just met,
last name -- Hole.
She'll take home this handmade
potato-chip-bag crown.
MUSIC HOLE:
Oh, my gosh!
I've never won an award before.
BOTH: s With the sorrow
in our hearts J
J We can may J
J And I look up to you ;&
J And we hear different sounds
than the heartless do J
> Wakeful at night looking
everywhere for you J
s Why do I look up to you? ;&
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!