[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
J "Adventure Time" 7
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We're going to
very distant lands &
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end 7
J It's "Adventure Time" J
Elderolio, why are there
only six crumb piles?
Mole children, soon, my body
will explode from exhaustion.
Please place my bits
[coughs] in trees,
where they will be reclaimed
by nature.
[All crying]
Elderolio!
Yes.
Cry and hug me.
JAMES BAXTER:
James Baaxter!
James Baaaxter!
Jaaaames Baaaaxter!
Huh?
[Laughter]
JAMES BAXTER:
James Baxter!
Yay! He makes me
so haaaapppy!
Jaaaammes Baaaxxxteeerrr!
[Laughter]
[Laughs]
Thank you, James Baxter.
Now I can explode
a happy mole man.
James Bax--
[Pop!]
Noooooo!
[All crying]
James Baxter?
Uh..
Oh, JakeI
Stretch into a ball
so James Baxter can ride you.
Um...
What if I...
[Grunts]
He's doing it!
BMO:
Oh, Glob, no!
Finn, this ain't gonna work,
not without this.
James Baxter's an artist.
He needs the proper equipment
to work.
And if we don't help him,
no one will ever be happy again!
BMO:
Oh, no!
We have to save
this precious unicorn.
Come on, BMO.
You're going with me.
'Cause your sadness
is not gonna help James Baxter.
I'm going to find a patch
for this beach ball.
Uh, o-okay.
I'll watch over James Baxter.
JAKE:
Try to cheer him up, man.
Cheer him up.
James -- uh, I mean,
Mr. Baxter, can you walk?
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
[All crying]
Sorry it's so cold in here,
Mr. Baxter.
Does that, uh --
Does that feel better?
[Gasps]
Your hooves are soiled!
I'll be right back
with a washcloth and herbal tea.
Yip-yin!
Oh, my Glob.
James Baxter is in my house.
-[POPI!]
- Hey, Finn.
You -- You look
a little nervous.
That's James Baxter out there!
He's an artist.
What if I say something dumb
and he's like,
"Man, that dude is so dumb.
Why am I even here?"
Just treat him
like a normal guy.
That's what people want,
even great artists.
- Okay. Yeah.
-[Kettle Whistling]
Normal. Normal.
[Whistling stops]
Normal, normal.
[Deep voice] So, uh,
you got any weekend plans?
You doing anything fun
for the weekend?
You're really bad at this, man.
Surely we'll find a patch here,
here in the big trash pile.
RAGGEDY PRINCESS: Uh, you mean
the Rag-and-Bone Kingdom.
[Singsong voice] Hi.
Raggedy Princess!
[Grunting]
Can you patch this beach ball?
Looks like that ball
requires a rubber patch,
and rubber is the most difficult
material to work with.
Most adhesives
don't adhere properly.
But in my kingdom,
everything can be found
if you poke around enough.
[Chuckles]
So [chuckles]
there's a pristine,
undamaged beach ball
here somewhere.
Here.
Have some poking sticks.
Bless you, Raggedy Princess.
Come on, BMO!
BMO:
For James!
Mmm. Sandwich good.
Would you like
another one, sir?
Hmm?
[Gulps]
FINN: Good!
[Coughs]
Oh, my Glob!
I am so sorry!
[Coughs]
[Sighs]
[Horns honking]
[Grumbles]
Neigh, neigh.
Neigh, neigh, neigh. Neigh.
[All neighing]
Pbbbt. Neigh?
[Sighs]
[Twinkle!]
-[Whimpering]
- Huh?
[Snhorts]
[Sobs, squeaks questioningly]
[Crying 1
[crying 1
[Snhorts]
[squeaks]
[Neighs happily]
Wheel
[squeaks]
James.
Baxter.
[Chuckles]
James.
Baxter.
[Laughs, smooches]
James Baxter!
[Muttering]
James...Baaaaaxter.
James...Baxter.
Beach ball!
Whoa!
What is it?
JAKE:
Beach ball?
[Both scream]
Oh, hey, you guys.
I was just working on
some new poems.
They're a little rough,
but as long as you're here
just poking around...
[Clears throat]
"A transfixed world surrounds me
like a monarch
with her open wings
held in place with tiny pins."
-[BMO crying]
- A lifeless Uh...
Is it that bad?
No, it's just really sad.
You remind me of James Baxter
because you are like
his opposite.
And since he lost
his artist tool, he cannot work.
He will never make
anyone happy again!
-[Crying]
- There, there, BMO.
A fellow artist in crisis?
I've been a creative blockhead.
Jake! BMO!
Balls!
[Rumble!]
[Boom!]
BOTH:
Hooray!
We are saved!
[Groans]
Truly, this is a fine kingdom.
Jaaaames Baxxxxterr!
[Crowd cheers]
Yeah! All right!
Jaaames Baxterrr!
James Baxter!
[Crowd cheering]
[squeaks]
[Sobbing]
[squeak-squeak]
Want some soup?
I made it
out of ice-cream sandwich.
You're still being weird.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
You got to slap him, dude.
- Wha?!
- Slap him with some real talk.
- Oh.
- Stab him.
What?!
With a giant syringe...
Wha?!
...of respect.
Ohh.
Okay.
[Breathes deeply]
Yo! [Neighing]
Jaaames Baxteeerrrr!
You're a wonderful, genuine,
one-of-a-kind hooooooorse!
And you make so many people
happy just by being yoouuu!
So let gooo
of what's loooost, man.
It's time
for Jaaaaaaaaames Baxter
to make James Baxter happy!
[Smooches]
-[Normal voice] James?
-[Door opens]
BOTH;
We did it!
All the beach balls
you'll ever need!
All for you, James!
[Chanting]
James! James! James!
What?!
We're too late!
[Thud]
The world is crud.
[BMO crying]
JAMES BAXTER:
Jaaaaames Baxteeer!
James Baxter?!
Jaaaaaames Baxterrr!
Oomp-oomp-oomp-oomp!
Jaaames Baxterrr!
Who's he doing that for?
I think -- I think
he's doing it for himself.
Jaaames Baxterrr!
Jaaaaaaaaaames Baxterrrr!
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!