[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
s "Adventure Time" &
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
FINN: Ugh.
Mm.
Ugh.
Blugh.
Eww!
The Sea Lard's in my bed again.
Gross.
Dude,
that's like the eighth time.
Why don't you
just get rid of it?
I don't know
what's gotten into it lately.
It's gross as butts, man.
We're taking care of this
right now.
I can't believe
we never thought of this before.
The pond is the perfect place
for a Sea Lard.
See ya Larder!
[Splash!]
Huh.
Is he, like, okay?
Well, seeing as Sea Lards
are saltwater fish
and the pond
is a freshwater environment...
[Inhales sharply]
...N07
He's a stenohaline fish.
Haven't you guys
ever heard of osmoregulation?
Allow me to explain.
WEEEEEERL
Sorry, Shelby.
Got to save the Lard.
[Inhales deeply]
[Splash!]
- Tharl!
- Wha...
J Smashin' frogs &
J Making bull-frog hot dogs
J Smash the frogs 7
- FINN: Whoa!
- Finn and Jake!
J Smash the frogs 7
Yo, Finn and Jake are here!
J Smash the frog ;&
- Hil
So, this is Where you guys live?
TOGETHER; Yeah.
We're the guardians
of this grotto.
You guys want to stay for lunch?
We're making hot dogs!
BOTH:
Hot dogs?!
Oh, wait.
We dropped our Sea Lard
in the pond,
and we got to save it before
it dies from the freshwater.
He's a stenohaline fish.
You do know
Sea Lards are mammals, right?
Uh...l definitely knew that.
[Whispering]
I'm gonna murder Shelby.
Well, hey, you guys
should stick around.
I'm gonna go finish cooking.
BOTH:
And we got to mash more frog.
I can't believe I just believe
Shelby 'cause he's a nerd.
I know.
It's in his tone.
Dude, it's the Lard!
Hey, get away from there!
[Whirl! Whirll Whirl!]
[Gasps]
Bad Lard!
Lard!
Huh?
Don't go near there!
It's too dangerous!
Got to save this dang Lard!
Whatever you do,
don't touch the purple stuff!
Whoa!
[Coughs]
What did she say?
Don't touch the purple?
[Groans]
What happened to the pond?
And how 'bout our treehouse?
The house part's a-gone!
What the butt?
I guess we went through some
portal to the past or some biz.
Was stuff the wrong color
in the past?
[Warbling]
It's weird as carbs here.
The Sea Lard!
There it goes!
Lard!
[Lap! Lap! Lap!]
-[Bubbling]
-[Giggles] Hello, friends!
FINN: Lard!
Lard!
- Lard!
-[Smooches]
J La, la, 13, la,
la, la, la, la &
JLa, la, la,
la, 1a, la, la, la &
J Laaaaaaard J
You are crazy.
You are so crazy.
Everything's, like, wonky here.
-[Chomp!]
- It's familiar but weird.
[Chomp!]
I like it.
I don't know.
Kind of makes me feel naked.
[Gasps]
J La, la, la, Lard! 7
Gotcha!
Finally, we can take you home.
- BOTH: Huh?
-[Humming]
J A-one and a-two J
J I'd rather be anything
but me J
& A leaf on a tree f/
-fl Oooh, oooh &
J A bug or a bee J
J Oooh, oooh ;&
J I just want to see the sea 7
J I want to be free
from this body 7
J This flower body &
Please don't change.
You're perfect
just the way you are.
Oh, I know.
I just like to write sad songs.
BOTH; Ohhh.
[Both chuckle]
Wait.
Hey, Jake,
what were we just doing?
FLOWER MARCY - & Chasin' the fish &
J Chasin' the fish &
J And it's getting away 7
Get that Lard!
Byel!
You guys are writing this down,
right?
Why does the Lard
keep running away?
We're trying to get it home.
Yeah.
This place ain't safe.
LSP: & Bummrn,
bum, bum, bum, bum, bum 7
P. PURPLE PATCH: [ Little
purple, you're a catch J
J Ilove
your pretty purple sash ;&
J We're a perfect purple match 7
; Welcome to my purple patch &
I'm Princess Purple Patch,
and this is
my little special purple.
Mwah!
[Snuggles]
Hi, Purple.
I'm Ginn and he's Fake.
Hm.
That's not right.
He's Ginn, and I'm --
Wait.
I'ma call you Purple Face!
You want to come play
in my purple place?
WATER NYMPH 51:
Don't touch the purple stuff!
Weren't we supposed to
not do something
with the purple things?
Mm?
Oh, you want purple?
Here, take some for the road!
[Ting! Ting! Ting!]
BOTH: Aaah!
[Sighs] Oh, dear.
I've purpled you.
[Sniffles]
Why do I always do this?
- Later.
-[Sobbing]
Heh!
What a great gal.
Yeah.
Purple!
Wait.
What were we just doing?
We were -- We Were...
Who are We?
I don't know, man,
but I like these things.
Foon. I'm -- I'm Foon.
[Groaning]
Fine.
-[Grunting]
- Huh?
Ja-- Ja-- Jaaaump!
Hello.
Are you a lost dog?
I am Boy.
Uh, maybe?
We are Boy and Dog.
I'm petting the ground, Boy.
Looks like fun.
And it smells like toast.
[Sniffing]
A-bloo, bloo, bloo!
Crying.
Long nose.
Investigate!
[Sighs]
Miss, your crying indicates
you're in need of help.
What?
[Sniffles]
Yes.
I've lost my rolling pin.
Understood.
What's your name, miss?
I'm Bush Boots,
the little apricot anteater.
[Sobbing]
J-lugs!
The hugs helped my crying,
but it didn't help me
find my rolling pin.
Boy and Dog will find
your rolling pin.
Where did you last see it?
It was rolling around here
not too long ago.
[Gasps]
Oh, there it goes.
Come back,
you bad little rolling pin!
[Rustling]
Bush Boots,
let's sneak up on it.
[Rustling]
[Gasps]
Am-boosh!
[Splat!]
Oh, you caught it!
Wonderful!
Uh...uh...uh...
Come on, now.
Just roll the dough.
[Squishing]
[All gasp]
Oh, it's getting away again!
Ma'am, I think that rolling pin
is sentient.
Yeah. I don't think
it wants to be a rolling pin.
Dog, we have to
save that rolling pin
from this sweet lady.
Where'd it go?
-[Splat!]
- Rolling pin!
We want to help!
[Clacks]
[Train whistle blows]
No more...slime.
Rolling pin trail has gone cold.
[Buzzing]
A bee.
I see.
[Buzzing]
A poem by me.
J Listen for a sound and look,
look around ;&
J Unless egress is sought,
smiles will be not found [
- Hmm?
It's a metaphor.
[Buzzing]
A pink pond.
FINN:
Pink pond?
Pretty!
[Giggles]
Hello, friends!
The pond has a face
and is talking to us.
Yeah.
- Dive in.
-[Swirling]
I don't feel comfortable
diving into a face.
Dog, let's go back
for apricot pie.
Yeah, pie!
-[Thwap!]
-[Grunts]
- Oof!
FINN:
Whooooa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[Splash!]
JAKE: And there was, like,
a PB puddle, a Marceline plant,
and a little bee that looked
like you, BMO!
You know what?
We didn't save the Sea Lard.
The Sea Lard saved us.
Yay, Sea Lard!
Wow.
What an adventure.
And there was even a purple lady
kind of like you, Ice King.
She even sounded just like you.
She sounds magnificent!
How'd you say you got there?
We didn't.
Beat it, creep.
I'll figure it out.
But, Simon, if you go there,
you'll lose your memories.
What memories?
I'm like a goldfish over here.
In what way, exactly?
Hmm?
Oh, hey, Jake.
Where am I?
Comfy, dude?
I bet you ran away 'cause
we didn't appreciate you
and called you gross and stuff.
But you're not gross.
[Smooches]
Good night, Sea Lard.
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!