[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
CANDY CHILD: "Mom! I wanna
play outside with Consuelo!"
"Cool your jets!
It's super dangerous outside.
Little kids have to stay
in the castle."
"But I'm rowdy!"
"Yeah, well, but look.
See what happens?
You want a playdate with death?
That's why you have to
stay inside!
And 'cause Consuelo's mom
is a pain in the neck."
[Gasps]
In the heat of the sun, you burn
like a pink little baby!
CANDY CHILD; Aah!
- What?
- Oh! A scweam!
Aah!
Well, now, what seems
to be the trouble?
I saw something in the water!
And I was like, "No, thanks!"
Out of my way, muffin man!
How rude.
Well, whatever that little girl
saw will be a mystery forever.
SHIP: Transport for Seeker
XJ-7-7 "Strong" has arrived.
Please verify identity
as "Strong."
Oh! Trust me, I'm strong indeed!
Pow, pow!
[Chuckles]
Ah? Not enough?
You need to feel them guns?
Verifying.
Whoa!
Well, hello, frisky!
[Giggles]
Todd, I'm right here!
Identifying dangerous mutant.
Initiating defensive mode.
[Splashing]
Seeking human.
-[Screaming ]
- Human, come home to safety.
Seeking human.
Human, come home to safety.
FINN:
Hey, Jake, what about this one?
[Laughs ]Great.
We're gonna look so great
for this funeral.
BMO:
How do you like my bandeau!
I was too embarrassed
to get a bra fitting.
I know they are professionals,
but it's just too intimate.
You look great!
Settlement detected.
Continuing search for XJ-7-7.
BANANA GUARD:
Get him! Attack! Attack!
TOGETHER: Aaah!
Hostile cylinders detected.
Release countermeasures.
TOGETHER: Aah!
[Muffled]Ahh!
Hostile cylinders immobilized.
Engaging hostile bobbleheads.
Neutralizing.
Please do not turn your system
off during neutralization.
[Crash! ]
FINN:
Holy mud!
It took out the gumball guards
like they was nothin'!
BMO doesn't like it!
We gotta chop this thing
into smashaghetti.
Yaaaaaaaaaa!
I'll take you out
with these hug nubs!
Yaaaaal!
I'll help you, Finn!
Aah! Help me, Finn!
Oof!
Hostile mutant neutralized.
[Gulps]
[Thinking ]
You got this, Finn Mertens.
You're a buff
little bionic baby.
Rush!
Ruuuuussshhh!
[Grunts]
Aaahhh!
SHIP: Verifying.
Human identified.
Infant PG-8-7 "Mertens."
-[Whoosh! ]
- Aaah -- Oh.
[Whirring]
PG-8-7.
Uh...you mean me?
You will assist this transport
in locating Seeker XJ-7-7.
PG-8-7 "Mertens,"
please climb aboard.
Please climb aboard.
Come on.
"Mertens?"
Wait, do you, like, know me?
Got it! Great work
distractin' 'em, Finn!
You okay, dude?
I feel like that ship
might've been important.
But I'm fine.
Yeah, my hands are a little sore
from smashing,
but I'm fine, too.
Eeeeeeeyaaaa!
Ha! Ha! Once again
BMO comes out on top!
- Bzzt!
- BMO!
BMO, you okay?
Signal received.
XJ-7-7 requests transport.
BOTH:
[Gasps ]Susan!
Hey.
Hi, Finn.
Uh, sorry again
my grass arm busted you up.
It's okay.
At the time,
Susan was gonna bust you up.
Where's Jake?
Is he okay?
He's outside.
He's bringing the ship over.
The ship?
On. Ship.
BMO:
[Humming]
How about it, Suze?
Does any of this look familiar?
Me and Finn took this whole
bad block down ourselves!
Took a bit of finagling, but I
never hunt what I can't catch.
[Whoosh! ]
[Drumbeats]
[Whirring]
[Crashing]
BUBBLEGUM:
Hey. Looking for this?
I've been holding on to the
remnants of your cranial implant
since you kidnapped Finn
and almost killed Jake.
You remember that?
I'm running a comparative
mass spec test now.
-[Ding! ]
- Yep.
Looks like both your implant
and the ship
have the same
technological origin.
Human technology.
-[Beep]
- BMO: Finished.
Looks like
BMOQO's finally downloaded
the ship's last commands.
BMO:
Signal received.
Proceed to extraction point.
Return Seeker XJ-7-7 and cargo
to Founders Island, home.
BMO, can you give us printouts?
Yes, okay.
Printing.
Hmm. Man, this island's
way far out there.
Susan needs to go back here.
To this island.
Not sure why.
Susan having crazy week.
I don't know, Susan.
It's so far.
Even I don't know
what's out there.
It's a pretty risky
solo mission.
I'm going, too.
I mean, we gotta find out
where this ship came from.
There could be more of them.
And if this is human-made,
then there might be
other humans on that island.
That'd be cool to see, right?
I'll come, too!
And so will we.
No, we won't.
Oh.
Well, it sounds like
you're all determined.
You should borrow my boat,
though.
This thing is trashed.
We don't need a boat!
Have you forgotten?
With a little imagination...
J I can be anything
that you could ever... &
Oh, I lost focus.
Hey,yeah.
Can we borrow your boat?
Are you up here, Fern?
Hey, thanks for letting me crash
on the roof.
It's nice up here.
Stay as long you want.
I came up here to ask a favor.
I might be gone
for a while on this trip, see,
and I need someone to, uh,
cover for me here in Ooo.
Are you sure?
I mean, hero biz
is your whole thing,
and whatever I am, I'm not you.
You can just do your own thing
with it.
Like...if some huge
gross monster's
gonna do murder
on a buncha innocents,
uh, kill it.
But Kill it you-styles.
Just don't go nuts.
Okay, I can handle that.
Thanks for trusting me.
No, thank you, Fern.
I better go pack.
- Eh. Let's figure out...
- We should figure out...
-...something better.
-...a better thing.
Hey, Dad?
JAKE: Charlie! Hi, it's me!
It's Dad!
I have to go on a sea voyage,
honey! I wanted to say bye!
That's cool.
Hey, you can't see this shirt,
right?
This shirt has like four
different breakfasts on it.
JAKE: I can't hear anything!
Bye, love you! Mwah!
Mm-kay, Dad!
I'll tell the other pups!
JAKE:
And I'm telling the other pups!
Aww, I'm gonna miss you
so much, Lady.
[Speaking Korean]
Finn, did you bring
your nail clippers?
Uh...l think so.
Cool, I forgot to.
Bye, treehouse!
Goodbye, creator!
Now me and BMO
can really "out loose!"
Look, BMO! I am pretending
to trash a hotel room!
BMO?
BMO:
[Softly]Ouch.
Thanks for seeing us off, guys.
Yeah, of course.
It's my boat.
And we care about him,
you dingus!
Come on!
Sorry,
Marcy is up past her bedtime.
No, it's true.
I want you to be
really careful out there.
Don't worry.
We've got Susan.
That's not what I mean.
Finn, I get the sense that this
trip's more important to you
than you're letting on.
I mean,
if you make it to that island,
you might find out
some pretty heavy stuff.
About the humans
and where you came from.
About yourself.
Alls I'm saying is,
you have to promise me --
promise me --
that you'll come home safe.
- Hi, Bonnie!
- BOTH: Ah!
I'm Fern.
I kind of already know you.
I have a lot
of fuzzy half-memories
from when I was this guy.
Well, just keep the ones
where she's our boss
and forget everything else.
SUSAN; Finn?
Hey, good morning.
Boat's loaded, ready to go.
- Ahh! I flinched!
- It's cool.
We'll be back soon, I promise!
Bye, kids!
Don't be naughty!
BUBBLEGUM:
Bye! Good luck!
He'll be safe.
Hey, aren't you that dude that
totaled Starchy's motorcycle?
[Waves crashing]
This party is so crazy!