[Growls]
[Dolphins chatter]
[Screeches]
J Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
> We'll go
to very distant lands 7
J With Finn and Jake
and Susan Strong J
J And possibly BMO 7
J It's adventure time 7
[Plunk, plunk, plunk, plunk,
plunk, plunk, plunk, plunk!]
[Both laugh]
[Pops lips]
[Whirring]
Smeemo, mo, mo, mo?
Boosan, san, san, san?
Where's all the dirt?
Yeah.
And what are those balls?
The coffins of the future?
Is this whole place
a fancy human graveyard?!
What are you doing
with that egg?
I don't know yet.
Hup, hup, hup!
Mmm. Egg in me.
BMO:
Dance, baby, dance.
- Mama, dance.
- BMO!
- BMO: Shake.
- Yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh,
yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh,
yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh!
- Yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh!
- BMO: Mama.
- I'm your mama.
- FINN: Yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh, yuh!
Cluck cluck, peck.
- Scratch, scratch, baby.
- Yooch!
BMO:
J Hatch into my heart, yogurt
BMO, we found you!
BMO!
[Pops lips]
Huh.
Bold claim.
Do it.
BOTH:
Whoaaaaaaaaa!
Choose your avatar!
FINN: Oh, wow. This place is
objectively interesting.
You look crazy.
""[Thud N
[Grunts]
Yo, param-zero yah hit-box,
system dumps!
- I corrupted...
- Who's a system dump?!
- He targeted my booty disk.
- LOL.
- 0011010.
- Whoa.
WOLFPRUD3: Rip, those avies
are older than my "A" drive.
[Chatter]
Get big phone.
Yeah, I'd like to request
a mod, please.
Yeah, there's a couple
of system-dumps
in the pizza romance RPG
mega-quadrant.
On server eight.
Yeah, WOLFPRUD3, with a 3.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Hokay!
Get cup!
Get cups!
Get peas.
WOLFPRUD3:
Aw, yeah, here comes the mod.
Y'all are in trouble.
- BMO!
Ban!
[All scream]
Y'all want to see my dance club?
- Yeah!
-[Laughing] Yeah!
[Dance music playing]
- I love your skin, BMO!
- I want to have your virus!
Thank you.
Dance responsibly.
Well, look who it is!
Welcome back to your palace,
your majesty.
Hi, Vinny!
Who's Vinny?
I thought I was hereby known
as "Get in heeyah!"
I deserve that.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
I've just been so zip-zopped-out
over the bip-bops.
[Beeping]
- What?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Who let these two system dumps
into the chat room?
Know what I'm saying?!
Yes, I do, Vinny.
BRB.
I'm gonna go deep dope
my ping-pong zilp-zorch.
What?
BMO: Vinny,
can you hook my friends up
with some BMO brand avies?
[Singsong voice]
What's the magic password?
Please, Vinny.
You got it, boss!
This super-skin costs
15 million crypto-coins.
Give it to me, Vinny.
[Beep]
I'm beautiful.
BMO?
BMO!
Dang it, Vinny!
I told you I would BRB!
We still don't know
where Susan is.
Have you seen her?
Oh. No.
But that's really easy
to search for.
[Whirring]
The island chain brain frame
has located her
32.7 miles east of here.
Well, this is great.
Now we can go find her.
Come along, BMO.
(\\[o
I think I need to stay here
forever.
Ha!
Cha cha cha cha cha!
[Gasps]
I'm gonna just go yank off
his goggles.
[Electricity crackles]
[Growls]
They thought of everything.
But who is "they"?
Who's running the show?
[Wings fluttering]
[Computers whirring]
Humans!
[Laughs]
Get broadsword.
[imitating electric guitar]
[Slurps]
[Electronic music plays]
So, you really don't want
to come with us?
You sure you don't want me
to milk you up
a fresh new style?
No, I'm used to it now.
Why don't you want
to come with us?
I mean,
I do want to go with you.
But I am a beautiful,
big man here.
All of my instincts are in sync
with this computer world.
I'm really comfortable here.
Yeah, but it's all fake.
What's real?
Your eyeballs think
the sky is blue,
but that's just sun rays
farting apart through the barf
of our atmosphere.
The sky is black.
Oh, yeah!
Here it comes!
[Music tempo quickens]
[Crowd Whooping]
[Music stops]
Ha ha!
I'm the best!
[Sobbing]
BMOQ's pretty upset with you.
Why'd you tell him it was me?
You want me to lie to him?
Yes!
He's our son!
Get magic staff!
[Grunts]
- Get katana!
- Get scimitar!
- You did this!
- I lost my game.
- Get big phone!
-I'd like to report...
[Humans groaning]
Now we're the system dumps!
Yeesh!
Jake, you turned
the whole thing off?!
I saved the world!
We gotta turn it back on,
not just for the sake
of this depressing off-shoot
of my species, but for BMO!
[Sobbing]
What?
[Sniffles]
- Get battle axe!
- Get saber!
- Get awl pike!
- Ooh, y'all play violent games.
BMO?
BMO, is that you?!
Vinny?
Give me one of your patented
super skins
made out of blip bloop cheese
or something.
I can do nothing for you
in this reality, Vinny.
No! BMO!
Vinny!
Geez Louise!
You really flipped out in here.
Anyone got some sticky tape?
BMO?
I will save you,
"A Better Reality."
[Static crackles]
JAKE:
Don't worry, BMO.
Daddy's just gonna
kiss everything in here,
and that will make it better.
[Wings fluttering]
Mwah, mwah, mwah!
Oh.
[Loud whirring]
Ha ha ha.
Get infinite hot dogs!
[Laughs]
Ah!
My beautiful avie!
[Laughter]
- We're back!
- Oh, we're back!
Get baseball bat!
Get broadsword!
- Get jet pack!
- Get bikini babe!
Hey!
You don't kiss me.
I kiss you.
They are giving you
this other pod
to take you safely
to the next rad island.
I will be returning
to my dance club.
BMO, I'm sorry
I smashed up your world.
I smashed it up
because I love you.
Please don't go.
Well, m-maybe I could visit.
Oh, Jake, hug me tighter!
Okay!
Of course I won't go!
I would miss you guys too much.
I tried to make a Finn and Jake
in the goggles world,
but they were scary.
I love you, too, BMO.
[Grunts]
I can't fit!
Are you still carrying that egg?
Yeah, it feels good.
Get rid of it, man.
I can fit.
I just need to --
[Chirping]
[Laughs]
Finn, did you see?!
Get in the pod.
This party is so crazy!