[ Quacking ]
[ Warble, zap! ]
[ Roars ]
J "Adventure Time" &
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We'll go to very
messed-up lands 7
J With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty 7
s Who knows how it will end? J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
;7
[ Indistinct chanting ]
Flame Crowd:
Smash the nerds!
Nerds, nerds,
smash the nerds!
A nerdless world
is the best kind of world!
Nerd, nerds, no more nerds!
[ Grunting ]
Heh... hah...
Heh... hah... hah...
Finn!
Fight, fight, fight.
Finn, stop.
What happened to getting the
fire jewel and saving Oo007?
Is this about you ex?
This is about
the purity of battle.
Okay, but you usually have
a reason for fighting.
The fiery heartbeat of battle
is its own reason.
No, that's stupid.
-Yah!
- Oh, Glob!
Just listen to the beat
of your hero heart.
I only hear
the drums of war.
[ Grunts ]
What drums?
No!
[ Grunts ]
Finn!
You're hurting me
physically and emotionally.
[ Grunts ]
Oh.
Fight, fight...
Dang it, Finn.
Becoming a crazy,
fiery bad boy
has made you
even more of a babe.
Ice King:
Check it out, LSP.
Wha?
It's a real
magic flying carpet.
I feel just like
Scheherazade.
Lump creature,
did you get the fire jewel?
No. Flame Princess
freakin' ate it.
And now the fire guys are
attacking the Candy Kingdom
because they took everything
I said the wrong way.
And that's totally on them.
But also, we lost Finn
to the flames of war!
Okay.
I'll go find him.
Finn?
Oh, where are you, pal?
[ Gasps |
It's Gunther.
He's in flames, too.
We have to rub soothing lotion
on Guntzy.
You got any lotion?
Your skin is so hydrated.
Fun: Hmm.
Got any...
Caramel Crunch Pies?
[ Groans ]
[ Laughs ]
Yes!
Oh, man, I don't
think you should play
this game ever again.
You're too good at it.
What is that sound?
[ Drums beating in distance ]
Ooh, company's coming!
;7
[ Both cheering ]
Whoo!
-Whoo!
- Yesl!
Mm! Look at all
these thirsty customers!
[ Ding! ]
Ooh, the pies are ready!
Mm! Ice-cream pies
for all our hot new friends!
Aah!
[ Sizzling ]
[ Both laughing ]
Whoal!
Mm!
;7
[ Sizzle! ]
Maybe they don't
like lemonade.
[ Laughs ]
;7
Gunther,
your ride is here.
[ Foosh! ]
Gee, who sneezed
in your corn flakes?
He's gone.
The fire has taken his mind.
Is this true, Goontz?
Wenk! Wenk! Wenk!
[ Flame Crowd grunting ]
Look, weird lady,
I don't know you and
you don't know me,
but we're the only
sane people left
in this crazy,
mixed-up world.
Or maybe the world's fine
and we're the ones
losing our marbles.
Either way, it's up to us
to save the day.
Simon.
So, let's get in there
and mash their potatoes.
You got any mashed potatoes?
I'm hungry.
[ Both scream ]
Nerds.
[ Panting ]
I have to hurry.
All this chaos and mayhem
is just -- ugh!
Finn!
You have to stop this.
Think of Jake.
How are you going to fix him
if you're a fire bozo?
And if not for Jake,
do it for me.
Aah!
Oh, my side.
Flame Crowd: [ Chanting ] Nerds,
nerds, smash the nerds!
A nerdless world
is the best kind of world!
Nerd, nerds, no more nerds!
[ Bubblegum humming ]
My children
have come home.
We've come for you!
Oh, a dragon, how fun!
I can do a dragon.
Look.
[ Roars ]
I see you've been playing
with matches.
Fight me, nerd!
[ Giggles ]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Are we wrasslin'?
Fun!
[ Giggling ]
[ Grunting ]
Aah!
Stop having fun!
Huh?
[ Gasps |
Finn, no!
Yah!
This isn't you!
[ Grunts ]
You're being
a very naughty boy, Finn!
Oh, Glob.
Everyone I know is spazzing
out on each other.
They're spazzing each other
to death!
[ Foosh! ]
Is this the end?
Will I be the last witness
to the glory of this world that
I chose above all others?
[ Marshmaline giggling ]
Tickle, tickle, tickle.
[ Giggles ]
[ Gasps |
Marceline!
I got you!
[ Splat! ]
[ Groans ]
I got burned.
[ Laughs weakly ]
Oh, Marcy.
I don't think I can
save the world on my own.
I'm more of an aspiring hero
than a real one.
I got, like, the morals and the
charisma and the good looks,
but I lack field experience!
Why couldn't I just get morphed
like everyone else?
Curse these superior genes!
[ Laughs ]
Have some marshmallow,
dude.
It'll calm you down.
Mm.
[ Slurps ]
Mmm.
[ Munches ]
[ Inhales, exhales deeply ]
[ Softly ] Your face
tastes like my happy place.
Fire Finn: Rah!
[ Sword swings ]
[ Gasps |
Ahh!
Fire Finn rules!
[ Grunting ]
Hah... hah... hah.
It's time
to go professional.
Hah...
hah...
yah.
Finn!
My little sugarplum.
You've returned to accept
your sweet fate.
I ain't sweet!
I'm a pure warrior
with guns,
and I'ma murder you
for funs!
Rahhh!
No!
You can't stab
a person you love, Finn!
I'll stab you!
-Aah!
- Oof!
Hmm.
I'm sending you
to your...
happy place!
[ Sizzle! ]
[ Sniffs, snorts ]
;7
Here, take it,
you cutie.
Rawr!
LSP: [ Echoing ]
I said your happy place.
Happy place!
I wish
I could stay like this.
[ Foosh! ]
[ Sizzle! ]
I've enjoyed
just -- just hanging out.
Me too.
[ Soft sizzling ]
You did it, LSP.
I'm human Finn.
There's no time for romance,
Finn.
We got to get that jewel.
Oh, yeah.
Hup!
I'm bringing you back,
Bonnie.
[ Giggles ]
That's sweet.
Hup.
Aah!
Sweet,
but not sweet enough.
[ Both screaming ]
[ Giggling ]
Eeh!
Ugh!
[ Rumbling, Bubblegum grunting ]
This charade
has run its course.
In your hearts,
you are all sweet.
J Let me call you sweetheart 7
JI'min love with you &
Wenk.
J Let me hear you whisper &
[ Gasping ]
Let my impervious bod
be your shield!
J That you love me, too 7
Mmm!
[ Screams ]
J; Keep the love-light glowing &
No!
[ Gasps ]
Flame Princess!
J In your eyes so true J
[ Coughs ]
Phoebe?
J Let me call you sweetheart &
[ Candy rattling ]
[ Gags ]
JI'min love with you &
The final jujubee.
Betty: Finn!
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
[ Gobbling ]
Purple clump,
you are a sour anomaly.
Whuh?
[ Muffled ]
What'd you call me?
[ Cand
y rattli
Aah! "o ]
Give me them jewels, Finn.
We're out of time.
Give me, give me, give me.
Here.
[ Cackles ]
Now, let's grab LSP and get
the buns out of here --
Hoh.
Huh?
[ Cackling ]
[ Ting! ]
I've been betrayed.
I've been Betty-trayed!
[ Rustling ]
[ Screams ]
J Let me
call you sweetheart &
Together:
> I'min love with you 7
J Let me hear you whisper &
J That you love me, too 7
[ Screams ]
All: & Keep the
love-light glowing 7
J In your eyes so true J
J Let me call you sweetheart 7
JI'min love with you &
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!