[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Screeches ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We'll go
to very distant lands ;&
s With Cake the cat
and Fionna the human 7
s The fun will never end J
J It's adventure time &
;7
These ghoul dudes
take the form
of whatever
you're thinking about.
[ Chainsaws buzz ]
An angry --
no, shy shark baby.
What if life was always just
constant fun times on the river?
Let's never do
anything boring ever again.
Yes, let's never do anything
boring ever ag--
[ Beeping ]
Time for Ice King's
boring book reading.
Aw, come on!
He's just gonna read
those weird stories
that are basically
about us.
I kind of dig getting
loosely adapted.
Ice King: Fionna spoke with the
voice of an angelic choir.
"You can have the rest of the
screaming chili cheese dip
if you want," she said.
[ Sniffles ]
"It's totally fine."
The end.
I said "the end"!
[ Applause ]
[ Chair squeaks ]
Let's get
some questions.
Where do
your ideas come from?
They're beamed
into my melon at night --
same as everybody else.
Next!
Woman: I have more of
a criticism than a question.
I am very open
to criticism!
Your story was
completely wrong.
And how would you know?
I know...
because I am...
[ Stick clacks ]
Fionna!
All: [ Gasps ]
I can show you
what really happened.
It's all on this tape!
All: Ooh!
Jake: What format
is that?
[ VCR clicks, whirs ]
According to this map,
we're very close.
-Hey. Hey.
- Hi. Hey.
There's the door.
[ Door knob rattles ]
Aw, it's locked.
I'll getusin
with key... eye!
Bam!
"Eye" got it.
You get it, Fionna?
Yeah, but it's a stretch.
[ Laughter ]
There I am.
[ Door creaks ]
Fionna: [ Sighs ]
Next time we find a map
lying in the backyard,
we should think twice.
Cake: At least we get
this fancy coffin.
How's it look?
It's a decent addition
to the treasure vestibule
but still kind of
a letdown.
You know what's
never a letdown?
Cookie sauce
review party.
Yeah!
Cookie dip.
Screaming chili cheese
versus sriracha ranch.
[ Lid creaks ]
[ VCR clicks, whirs ]
[ Light switch clicks ]
Was it real?
Who was filming all that?
Wenk, wenk.
Needs more hunks!
Dude, I literally have
one bazillion questions.
Uh, excuse me,
Miss Fionna...
where did this video
come fr-o-o-om!
Fionna!
I always knew we'd meet one day
and become best friends.
So, uh, remember that time when
Cake caught Ruse Goose,
the notorious goose
pickpocket?
That was
such a long time ago.
But during trial,
you realized she was framed
'cause it was actually
Abracadanielle pretending
to be a goose
all along!
[ Hisses ]
Can I also ask
a question?
Besties only.
I was just gonna ask if we could
see more of the tape.
Oh, yeah, can we?
I don't think so.
All right,
just a little more.
[ VCR clicks, whirs ]
[ Lid creaks ]
[ Yawns ]
Oh... my... glob.
It's a mummy!
That's right.
I'ma mummy!
Aww,
Yeah, you are.
And a real cutie, too.
I'm not cute!
I'm horrible!
[ Groans menacingly ]
Want to hang?
[ VCR clicks, static crackles ]
Okay, that's enough.
Both: Aw!
I want to see more.
I don't want to wear it out.
It's my only copy.
And it's
very important to me.
Library closes in five.
Click, click, click.
[ Light switch clicks ]
So, where you heading now?
Guess I'll go back to the dump
under the bridge where I live.
I'd invite you over,
but I don't have a sofa
or TV or anything.
It's literally a dump.
I have a TW.
My crib is equipped.
Oh, really?
Hey, you should move in!
Please live
with me, Fionna.
This is the sweet spot.
My roo-- Oh!
I wasn't expecting guests.
[Chuckles] Not that you mind
a bit of dirt, right?
Nice, huh?
So, this is my room now.
Only the best for Fionna.
Ice King: Oh, yeah.
I like this room, too.
It's where I do
all my deep thinking.
Man, I still can't believe it --
the Fionna in my bathroom,
touching my toothbrush,
throwing it
into my little trash can.
Fionna taking charge!
That's what heroes do.
You're a so much better hero
than Finn.
I know.
Plus, don't tell Jake,
but I've always been more
of a cat person.
Where is Cake the Cat?
Cake?
Cake is gone.
Some years back, there was
an adventure mishap.
I don't feel comfortable
talking about it.
Oh, okay.
Hey, you still haven't
shown me where you keep
your Fionna-and-Cake
tapes.
Sorry, no can do.
What?
Don't you have tapes?
Oh, yeah, I got loads of tapes,
but they're super private.
Maybe you'll change
your mind
once you see more
of my mummy adventure?
Yay!
I'll get snacks.
[ Static crackles ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Groans ]
Hey, what's wrong?
I have... a curse!
Oh, no.
How can we save you,
tiny mummy?
The curse can only be broken
by strong black coffee
and fancy muffins
from Breakfast Kingdom.
I know that place.
It has a really long line
on weekends.
Yes!
That sounds like the one.
Be a hero and fetch unto me
the sacred breakfast.
Don't you worry,
little guy.
We'll save you!
[ Laughs ]
[ VCR clicks, static crackles ]
Okay, that's the end
of the tape.
Really?
My stories usually get
wrapped up neater.
[ Chuckles ]
Wrapped up -- mummies.
Yeah, well,
there's no more, so...
You wouldn't know this,
but old heroes need
a lot of sleep.
I did know that.
See you in the morning.
[ Tape clicks ]
[ Click echoing,
ominous tone plays ]
Okay.
Fionna?
You awake?
I made you
a midnight snack.
[ Snoring ]
[ Munching ]
[ Sighs, snores ]
[ VCR clicks, static crackles ]
Mummy, we're home.
[ Gasps ]
I knew it.
Where did it go?
Maybe it had to go back into
its coffin Dracula-style.
Mummy?
We got your breakfast.
Hmm.
[ Coins rattling ]
Shh! What's that?
Nyeh.
That's our treasure!
Stay away.
You'll get cursed.
[ Groans menacingly ]
I take the curse off of me
and put it back on you.
You understand nothing
of mummy curses!
Our treasure!
Our muffins!
Uhh... do not look
upon a naked mummy.
It's bad luck.
Both: Queen of O007?!
That's right.
I snuck in here to pretend
to steal your stash
and teach you
a valuable lesson.
Never invite strangers
into your home,
no matter how cool
they seem and are.
You should be
thanking me really.
[ VCR clicks, whirs ]
Of course.
She didn't want me
to see the end of the tape
because she's not Fionna.
She's... a mummy!
Aah!
[ Ominous music plays ]
[ Whimpering ]
Other Fionna: Come on.
They're all just him?
Imposter!
Reveal yourself!
Aah! [Gasps]
Knock it off!
You're the knock-off!
What?
You're not Fionna!
How did you --
Show me your true form!
Aha! Huh?
What kind of mummy
are you supposed to be?
No kind!
I'm just an old lady.
Who likes to dress up
as Fionna?
It makes me feel
confident, okay?
Plus, I look really good
in this outfit.
Look, I used to be
very shy...
tinkering with my tech
stuff all night,
sleeping all day.
But one evening, I intercepted
a strange signal.
I was mesmerized.
I watched that tape
like 100 times
before I finally stepped
out of my cave a hew woman,
determined to find
more Fionna and Cake.
I roamed Ooo for years
with no luck.
But then, I found out
about you,
and I hatched a plan
to steal your tapes.
What?
I don't have
any Fionna and Cake tapes.
I know!
All of your tapes are filled
with embarrassing diaries.
If I met them,
I'd definitely record it.
Fionna and Cake
aren't real, you ding-dong!
They're just, like, a TV show
from the past or something.
You're the ding-dong, lady!
You tricked an old,
defenseless Ice King.
[ Crying ]
Look, I didn't mean
to hurt you.
You lied to me.
Fionna would never lie --
never.
Oh, glob, you're right.
I'm not like Fionna.
I'm the mummy!
[ Wailing ]
[ Crying ]
Wenk.
Huh?
Well, that was
disheartening.
[ Echoing ]
Forgive me, Fionna!
[ Yawns ]
Fionna: [ Echoing ]
Cake, what time is it?
Wenk.
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!