[ Duck quacks, wind whistles ]
[ Zaps ]
[ Roars ]
J Adventure time,
come on, grab your friends »
> We'll go to
very messed up lands 7
J With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty 7
s Who knows how it will end? J
J It's adventure time &
[ Ship horn blows ]
Jake: Heck, yeah!
We're home.
That was definitely
the longest adventure
we've ever done.
What about when you got trapped
in @ mind dungeon
for a buncha years?
This trip was longer
in emotional time.
Yeah, I'm burnt out. No more
adventures for a while, okay?
'CHRGCGHRGH
[ Babbles loudly ]
B-b-b-b-b-b-b!
Let's go take hot showers.
Hey, look at this fish.
[ Squish ]
It's... gummy?
[ High-pitched voice ]
Hello!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Hey!
[ Laughing ]
Well, that's weird.
We should defs
check it out after
we hit up the
tree house.
Yeah, we gotta get to the bottom
of this hot shower.
Hmm.
Does everything seem...
pinker to you?
Home always looks different
after a long trip.
You're seeing it with fresh eyes
and newfound wisdom.
And sometimes there's also a new
strip mall or something.
So everything being pink is
probably not a big deal.
And also, I'm tired.
I like the pink.
Why you worry so much,
worry baby?
Ha, ha, yeah! Why you worry
so much, worry baby?
Don't worry, Finn.
We're only teasing you
because you're a baby.
Whoa!
What the heck happened
to the tree house?
Candy...
Fern?
[ Squish ]
[ Dripping ]
Oh, I do not like this.
;7
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Because I love it!
Finn: Huh?
Big Baby root beer?
No one buys this brand.
It's too sweet.
Hello?
[ Both gasp ]
Aah!
Hey! You look like me!
Fern?!
Who's Fern? I'm Fun the Human.
And I'm Nectr,
the little robot!
I'm Shelby the Worm...
the gummy worm!
Welcome, strangers.
It's so cool that you're
inside our house.
Dude, when did you guys
turn into candy?
We've always been candy,
you silly billy bean!
Ohh, okay. I get it.
We've obviously stumbled into
another alternate dimension
where everyone's a different
version of themselves.
Yawn.
But we haven't gone through
any portals.
BMO would know.
Hello!
Neptr is so cute now!
I'm going to start treating him
as an equal.
You were supposed to take care
of Ooo while I was gone.
What happened with that?
What?
You used to be this volatile
plant boy. Remember?
Really? Well, I'm candy now.
And I'm in control
of my emotions.
I'm in control, too...
of my body!
[ Laughs ]
Wow, gummy Shelby's
a lot of fun.
I think I'm okay with
Candyworld.
No way. Let's talk to PB.
I'm sure this is all one of her
experiments gone wrong.
You seem upset, friend.
The tower will fix you right up.
The what now?
[ Gulping ]
[ Bell dinging ]
Oh, boy!
Let's run outside!
[ Bell dinging continues ]
[ Nectr whirring ]
[ Wheels squeaking ]
Hello! It's me!
Lemonpink!
He was inside the lemon.
Mm! Drink up, babies!
[ Splat ]
Squeeze!
[ Laughing ]
I used to have a lot of fear
and sadness,
but now I'm fine!
Hey, I want some of that.
No. That is body juice.
Hmm? What's that?
Do you spurn my fluids?
(\\[oR
Maybe someone's feeling
a little sour!
Wuh-whoa!
You know what sours get.
Sours get the tower!
Candies: Sours get the tower!
[ Splat ]
Sours get the tower!
Come on, Jake.
Let's go see Bubblegum.
[ Screaming ]
Stop striding!
It just keeps you agitated!
I'm freaking out, Jake.
This place is weird.
What I'm hearing is
you're stressed out
because everything's candy.
Aren't you?
Not really.
Lemongrab's always been
a weirdo.
At least now
he's helping people.
[ Rumbling ]
And Fern is, like,
laughing and joking around.
Maybe they don't need you
to fix them.
Hmm.
I always believe you when
you use that voice.
[ Crying in distance ]
[ Crying continues ]
Sweet P?
[ Sniffles ]
Hey, buddy, what are you
doing out... uh...
Hey! You're meat!
Yes, I'm meat. [ Sniffles ]
But everything else is weird.
Wow, Sweet P, that's
almost exactly
what I've been
saying.
Sweet P, do you remember
what happened?
One day, the candy came
and turned Mommy and Daddy
into something... different.
Tree Trunks and Mr. Pig:
Sweet P!
There you are!
We've been looking for you
everywhere!
We just love ya
so much, son.
You're gonna get into
a great college!
Tee-hee-hee-hee!
Tee-hee-hee!
They look so happy,
like dogs.
Don't worry, Sweet P.
We're headed
to the Candy Kingdom
to see Princess Bubblegum
about all this.
She's not in the Candy Kingdom.
She's in the Terrible Tower.
Look!
Come on, Jake.
That's kind of weird, right?
I think it's magnificent!
Sweet P! Yoo-hoo!
We brought some rollers
and a bucket
of sweet juicy caramel.
Let's get you back to normal.
But, Mama, I am normal!
Just sit tight there
like a windowpane,
and you'll be back to normal
like a windowpane.
[ Echoing ] Back to normal.
Hmm. Okay, you're right.
This is pretty freaky-deaky.
I'm gonna go now. [ Crying ]
Jake and Finn:
Sweet P, come back!
[ Tree Trunks laughs ]
Uh... let's get to the tower.
;7
And never be
the guy with no phone, Finn.
You'll think it'll make people
wanna talk to you more,
but people just forget
to invite you to things.
You've convinced me.
Plus, I like
late night bedtime calls
when you're sleeping over
at Lady's.
[ Sniffs ]
Ooh. Somethin' smells nice.
Nice and toasty.
[ Roars ]
All: S'more!
Stay back, S'more!
Jake: Get it! Get it!
Get it! Get it!
[ Growls ]
[ Laughs ] Whoa, dudes.
I was just playin'.
All: What?! Marceline!
[ Giggles ]
No, it's Marshmaline...
the Campfire Queen.
Mar--
Marsha--
Marsha-- Mars--
Marsha --
Marcine.
Mar-- Mar--
Marsh-- Marshmi--
Marshman-- My--
Would you like to hear a song?
I've written just the ditty
that'll cheer up anyone
that's overwhelmed with work
or responsibility.
Yay! I love Marshmaline songs!
No time for tunes.
Do you know where Bonnie is?
Of course! Follow me.
[ Humming "Greensleeves" ]
[ Humming continues ]
[ Humming ends ]
Marshy... where's PB?
She's everywhere.
[ Rumbling ]
Good tidings to you,
my friends.
[ Gasps |
Yahoo!
What -- what happened to you?
Oh, this? [ Giggles ]
I've become what I was always
meant to become --
a pure candy elemental.
[ Vomits ]
[ Laughs, cheering ]
[ Belches ] 'Scuse me.
What about Tree Trunks
and Lemongrab
and Marceline
and everyone else?
I fixed 'em, obviously.
Fixed 'em?
But they're your friends!
Those aren't
mutually exclusive concepts.
That means it's fine.
No, it's not fine.
Don't fret.
I can fix you, too.
[ Squishing ]
Aah! Aah! Aah!
I can feel my bones
turning gummy!
Me, too!
We gotta get out of here
before --
Oof!
Hugs!
I'm connected to all candy
throughout all the galaxies.
Once you're candy,
you'll be part of me, too!
No! That plan sucks!
[ Speaking indistinctly ]
Oh, my gosh!
Aah! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Oow!
Skyhooks!
Ice King?
Hold on to me, bro!
No!
Wait, we forgot... BMO!
Goodbye, boys!
It's better this way!
[ Beeping ]
[ Sighs ] Oh, well.
They'll be back.
[ Snaps ]
They have nowhere else to go.
[ Both screaming ]
Yah!
Ooh!
[ Groans ]
Are we in...
Cloud Kingdom.
Looks like we got away
before the candy curse
became permanent.
That's right.
My skyhooks saved the day.
Thanks for getting us out
of there, Simon.
Aw, I can't take all the credit.
It's all thanks to my skyhooks.
Hey, why are you even up here?
We live here now,
me and the skyhooks.
Finn, you gotta see this.
[ Gasps |
Oh...
my...
but...
Ice King: Skyhooks!
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!