[ Squeaks ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Screeches ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We'll go to
very distant lands [
s With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ;&
s And the fun will never end 7
J It's adventure time &
Jake: [ Shouting ]
Finn?
Finn: Yo.
Oh, hey.
Me and BMO are heading over
to the vuvuzela store
in the music kingdom.
You want to come with?
I got to get
a new vuvuzela.
Somebody keeps smashing
my old one.
[ Blows raspberry ]
[ BMO screams |
I can't bear this burden
any longer!
It was me!
I'm the vuvuzela smasher!
BMO, how could you?
Neptr: No, it was me!
I'm the vuvuzela smasher.
Neptr?!
Finn: No, I'm
the vuvuzela smasher.
All right, all right.
Well, I'm still
getting one.
You coming?
Nah, me and Fin--
Fern are supposed
to clean out
the chicken coop today.
And if anyone
tries to stop me,
I'll slash
their flipping faces off.
True, true.
Okay, well,
I'll see you later then.
Come on, BMO.
BMO: Jake, I'm sorry!
I really am the smasher!
Jake: Ah, don't sweat it,
buddy.
[ Laughs ]
Holy cow!
Fern, that was perfect!
Hyup!
You're getting new powers
like every day now.
Let me see you do Jake --
no, wait, Ice King!
Do Ice King!
Ha, nah, man.
[ Brrrb! ]
Imitating uncool people
infects you
with their loserishness.
Oh.
Yeah, that rings true.
It's too bad
you didn't develop any
coop-poop-scooping skills.
That coop
is incredibly disgusting.
Actually, about that,
I was thinking that,
instead, maybe you and I
could explore
some secret ruins I found.
Secret ruins?!
Sweet!
Maybe we can still catch up
with Jake and BMO!
Or maybe Neptr
could come!
Hey, Neptr, you want to go
on an adventure, buddy?!
Neptr: Oh, my glob!
Hold on!
Actually, I was thinking
maybe just you and me
would go.
Spend some quality time
together --
Finn and Fern style.
Yeah, okay.
That actually even
sounds like something
Jake would want us to do.
[ Chuckles ]
Forget it, Neptr!
J Dungeon surprise J
J Right before my eyes [
> What a surprise 7
J The dungeon surprise ;&
Finn and Fern:
One, two, three -- shoot!
Rock!
Scissors!
[ Chuckles ]
This is so weird.
I can't tell if it's boring
or fun.
Well, T can --
it's boring!
I want the thrill
of victory!
Who wants to be the same
all the time?
Come on, man!
You know you love it!
Come on!
One, two, three...
[ Sighs ]
Both:
One, two, three -- shoot.
Paper.
Rock.
What?!
Whoal!
I won this time.
What?
But that's not fair!
[ Growls ]
Why is nothing
ever fair?
Hey, Fern,
it's just a game.
Don't be so weird.
Don't!
Don't call me that.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Sorry.
Ah, it's okay.
That stuff won't
mean a thing.
I mean, that stuff don't
Hey, come on,
we're almost there!
Whoop, whoop, whoop!
Hey, wait up!
Whoop, whoop!
Whoop, whoop, whoop!
Whoop!
Look, we're here!
Where?
I just see a bunch of rock,
swear to glob.
But check this out.
Whoa!
Magic key!
I had to chop up a bunch of
stubborn so-and-so's
to get my hands
on this baby.
Dang!
You been busy.
Wow, would you
look at that!
They hid a ziggurat
in the cliff side.
Amazing!
Yeah, I poked around in there
a bit, but --
Dut, dut, dut!
No spoilers!
No, I know.
I didn't go past
the first level.
I was saving it
to do together.
Sweet.
Whoa, what is that,
a fitness pole?
Hey ya, hey ya, hey ya!
Come on.
This way.
Hey, Fern, wait up.
Hey, I just want to say
that it's really cool
that you're into
this stuff.
You know -- that we have
so much in common.
It feels almost like
we're real brothers, right?
Or even closer.
I think that's the treasure
chamber down there.
Why don't you
go check it out?
I want to study
these interesting carvings.
Hmm.
Fascinating.
Oh.
Uh, okay.
I guess just holler
if you need me.
[ Sighs ]
Hey, what's this?
Contemporary chair,
contemporary trash,
contemporary meatloaf.
Hey, bad news, Fern.
It looks like we've got
a squatter situation here.
I think they got
the treasure,
but they left
some meatloaf behind.
The good news is I know
a meatloaf dealer--
[ Muffled ]
What the?!
Fern?
[ Grunting ]
Uh, Fern?
I think maybe the wind
blew the door shut.
An "act of nature,"
I would presume.
I'm sorry. I don't actually
know how to make meatloaf.
That's just
a pan of dirt.
Well, that's okay.
I don't know how to,
either!
Fern, please
open the door.
This is where you live now.
You'll be fine.
What?! Fern, what about Jake
and BMO -- my home?
It's been your home
long enough.
It's Fern's turn.
I think I'm going to be
a really great Finn.
Hey, do you know who
my favorite is?
It's Neptr.
I'm a Neptr guy!
I'll be back in a month
with a new bucket of trash.
Later!
Fern!?
[ Grunts ]
I've been double-crossed
by grass Finn!
I don't like being abandoned!
I'm sensitive to it!
[ Groans ]
Mmm!
[ Sighs ]
It's too hot!
[ Groans ]
[ Muttering ]
There's got to be
something useful in here.
[ Screams ]
Oof!
You'll be back in a month?
With a new bucket of trash?
It's hot!
There's no air in here!
I need air!
[ Whirring ]
Wha?
Oh!
A microphone.
There's some dried ketchup
on it.
Uh, hello.
[ Beeps ]
Hi, Finn!
You're still asleep
after your fight with Susan.
But when you wake up,
I'm sure you'll have fun
discovering everything
your new arm can do.
And, Finn, sincerely,
thank you for defending
our kingdom again.
Oh.
Someone else wants
to thank you, too.
Thank you, Finn!
[ Laughs ]
I don't know.
Okay, um...
Welcome, Finn!
Huh.
Yes!
[ Buzzing ]
Huh?
You donked up!
[ Screams ]
[ Brrrb! ]
How did you get out?
[ Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
Whoa!
Hey!
[ Grunting ]
What do you think
you're doing?!
I'm weed whacking.
You've been Finn
long enough!
It's my turn.
[ Growls ]
Fern, smarten up!
Nuh-uh!
What are you?
A weed whacker!
[ Hissing ]
[ Grunting ]
Nyuh!
[ Hisses ]
My belzer!
[ Grunting ]
Whoa!
[ Panting ]
[ Laughs ]
Fern, if things
are going down the way
I think they're going down --
please tell Jake
I love him.
That doesn't matter.
I love him!
I know you do, Fern.
Listen, we can stop this
and just go home together.
All this lying
and fighting,
it doesn't have to end
like this.
Today doesn't have to have
this kind of...
finality.
Fatality!
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
Hey, boys!
Y'all have fun
out there?
Wait, what happened?
I know that look.
You just killed someone.
[ Blows horn ]
Almost done, champ.
There you go.
You looking for an uncle?
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!