[ Quacking ]
[ Warble, zap! ]
[ Roars ]
J "Adventure Time" &
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We'll go to very
messed-up lands 7
J With Finn and Jake,
Ice King, and Betty 7
s Who knows how it will end? J
J It's "Adventure Time" &
Give me them jewels, Finn.
We're out of time.
[ Cackles ]
Now, let's grab LSP and get
the buns out of here.
Huh!
[ Laughs ]
J Let me hear you whisper &
Aah!
You left my friend Finn
down there.
I'm sorry, but we don't need
him anymore.
But don't worry,
I've got a new plan.
A plan where nothing that
happens here matters.
Okay, but we should
turn back still.
Finn loves me.
He sees me as, like,
a handsome older brother.
Mm, no.
I'm doing the right thing.
Can't go around it,
got to go through it.
J That you love me, too 7
Uh, guys?
Getting a little too close.
J Keep the love-light glowing &
Uh... uh.
J In your eyes so true J
J Let me call you sweetheart 7
[ Screams ]
Finn, it's me,
I'm saving your tight butt!
[ Grunts ]
Whoop!
Don't worry, my children.
I will send my joy out
unto all of them.
"Bonbon ballad."
s Underneath the mountain 7
s Overlook the sea J
J I find my sweet friends
waiting J&
J And bring them close to me /&
J La-da-da-da, la-da-da 7
J La-da-da-da,
la-da-da &
Lumpy Space Princess,
you were buried in candy and it
didn't change you at all.
Why doesn't this elemental
stuff affect you?
I'm a tough tranch!
People don't tell
me what to do,
I tell them what to do!
Okay, but it has to be
more than that.
Like, you're not from around
000, not really.
Maybe you're not made of
the same stuff as us.
Hmm.
Lumps! Lumps are the subspace
molecular lattice
that binds together
the scientific and magical
forces of Ooo --
more powerful than
any one element,
it's the force that
orders reality into
its true shape.
And, LSP, this part is very,
very important --
Grrr!
No more learning!
[ Car horn beeps ]
Hey, Michael!
Let's get married.
Wait, what?
Michael.
LSP, This is important.
I think they were trying
to tell you --
you're the anti-elemental.
Fire, Ice, Candy, Slime and...
Lumps!
[ Gasps |
[ Hums ]
Huh?
I must have dozed off...
and bound myself.
Ouch!
[ Clears throat ]
People say you shouldn't
live in the past!
But I say, "Why not?"
I love it.
This book is strange,
but when you puzzle it out,
it's mostly all charges
and frequencies.
Instead of fixing Ooo,
I can use these jewels
to make a portal
to take me back in time
and find Simon
before he discovers
the crown.
Uh-huh.
This time I won't
let him put it on.
I'll drop it in a volcano
before that happens.
Things will be back to being
just me and Simon,
and you won't exist!
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
No more Ice King,
no more magic Betty --
maybe I can even stop
the Mushroom War!
[ Laughs ]
Cool.
Now where do I come in?
You're not listening.
My wonderful Simon will never
become this sad,
pathetic creature
strewn before me.
Wait, what?
I thought I could do it,
but I can't.
Being with you is like looking
at my old life
through a funhouse mirror.
[ Laughs ]
It's driving me mad.
Goodbye, Ice King.
[ Machine whirs ]
Okay, I think this is a pretty
good breakdown
of your components.
We just need to figure out a way
to tap into your pure
anti-elemental essence, LSP.
[ Sighs ] Don't tell me
what to do, Finn.
Yeah, like that.
Pb is undiluted sweetness now,
and Slime Princess has never
been slimier.
I think you might need to be the
most you that you've ever been.
You just have to believe in
yourself.
I do believe myself.
I'm a blossoming debutante
on the war path.
Wenk!
Ahhhhh!
Wenk! Wenk-wenk! Wenk, wenk,
wenk, wenk.
[ Purrs ]
See?
It's working.
Ugh!
You okay?
Just relax, you'll be
obliterated soon.
Really? Lady, this Simon sounds
cool, but I'm Ice King.
I, uh, I guess
I'm a special person
and I am worthy of respect.
Just -- shh!
It'll be over in a second.
Can you turn this off
and we can talk, maybe?
Nertz.
Huh.
J Underneath the prairie &
J Over sugar springs J
J We'll sing our song forever J
J This candy chorus rings 7
J La-da-da-da, la-da-da 7
Boy, did I fail deep.
Well, maybe I'll try again in
another 1,000 years.
I'm not sticking around to see
how this ends.
Mr. Fox, please roll me
someplace safe.
Oh, oh, wow. Okay.
[ Grunts ]
J Overlook the valley 7
J Under honeymoon J
What if?
Oh!
We're running out of time.
I am.
Glob!
Ding-dong.
It's me, classic Ice King!
Si-men!
I didn't like
being ditched earlier,
but if you and Betty
are cool now,
you can help us figure out how
to use LSP's power.
Wait, where's Betty?
Who?
Here, I bet this thing
can help
you.
[ Gasps ] It's Gunter!
Hey, Gunter! Come here, boy.
Okay, fair.
Hey, LSP, now that we've got
the Enchiridion,
maybe we can study it for
a way to figu--
No more studying!
All day long you've been telling
me what to do.
I already saved your life, so
quit telling me what to do.
Huh?
What's happening?
The jewels.
Oh!
What if your force of will
is influencing and attracting
elemental magic.
You mean these jewels love me
more than they love those
dumb-dumbs?
[ Laughs ]
Wenk! Wenk! Wenk!
And you!
Clam your face, you noid!
Clam your face,
you noid!
Okay.
Wenk!
My boy!
You bossed him back to normal.
Don't stop.
Uh, I don't think I can. The
jelly is out of the tube.
s Underneath the mountain 7
s Overlook the sea J
J I find my sweet friends
waiting J&
J And bring them close to me /&
Mama, Papal!
J Close to me 7
Excuse me.
Whoop!
Oh, blessings, what a trip.
Hey, Slime Princess.
Oh! Hello, Jake.
Uh, did you recently get
a haircut?
Unnnh. Lumps.
Oh, LSP.
Please be careful with yourself.
Ha-ha, fine, I guess.
Yeah, that's all of them!
[ Groans ]
LSP!
[ Weakly ]
I'm a hero.
Whoops.
You did it.
She did it!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Uh, I'd like to date you, LSP.
Thank you, Starchy.
[ Coughing ]
Wait, where --
Up here.
[ Clicks tongue ]
You really donked up.
Finn?
Jake?
Finn!
Oh, my gosh!
Come here.
What?
Over here.
Hey, buddy.
Jake? Are you okay?
Yeah...
[ Chuckles ]
You know, everything looks
different after a long trip.
You and I can fix whatever this
is together, whenever.
Fix what now?
I was really scared
when you left.
You're my best brother.
I love you.
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This is party is so crazy!