[ Squeaks ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Screeches ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We'll go to
very distant lands [
s With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ;&
s The fun will never end J
J It's adventure time &
;7
J Bass, bass, oh
bass, bass &
> Where'd I put my case
for my bass? »
2 I have trouble drawing
so I trace
J Oh, oh 7
J If I lick the amp
will I like the taste? &
J Bass to my face ;&
[ Knock on door ]
Good evening, ma'am.
I just now heard that
a bunch of vampires
came back to -- ooh!
I am the guy
who hunts those guys.
Show me all your vampires.
All the vampires got wiped out,
like, six months ago.
It's just down
to me again.
Really?
I apologize
for the intrusion.
Actually, I'm really glad
you're here.
Hey, BMO,
don't leave yet!
I need your help
with something technical.
Have a sit.
Ta-da!
It's an old USB drive.
I found it in the attic,
and I've been trying
to access it for weeks
using my old hardware.
It's funny, but I can't even
remember what's on it.
Hmm.
I don't know,
maybe you'll
have more luck,
Mr. Vampire Hunter.
I also hunt
data recovery!
Scanning...
[ USB drive humming,
beeping ]
It's going
to be a while.
A while, huh?
Let's use this opportunity
to catch up.
I love ketchup!
Did you make it yourself?
[ Laughs ]
BMO, no.
I mean how was your boat trip
with Finn and Jake?!
Hmm...
Well,
once we left Ooo...
we sailed for 100 days...
until we landed
upon a small island.
We were so tired from sailing,
we decided to take a nap.
Then the island started shaking
and rising from the water.
We were really sleeping
on a big cat
with legs on his back so he
could walk upside down.
What's going on here?
He said his name was Ted.
My name is Ted.
Whoaaaaaaaa!
A big blue jay
was making noise nearby.
WL EEEEL
So we walked somewhere else.
Whoa!
Oh!
Whoal!
We saw some boats
in the clouds.
Finn sang a song,
even though he was asleep.
J I want to ride on
a boat, boat, boat J
a goat, goat, goat 7
J Middle C is my favorite
note, note, note J
J I'm on a cat that floats,
floats, floats &
Then we floated
with the boats --
not in the boats,
but with the boats.
And we disappeared
into the clouds.
That's how I remember it,
though I might
have embellished.
So, what did you do
while i was on my trip?
Huh?
That was awesome,
BMO.
What are you making?
Puppets!
Oh, my blogs!
You are going to catch me up
with a puppet story?
Yup!
You gave me the idea!
I'm so happy
right now!
I'll try to make it
interesting -- the BMO way.
Once there was this...
lollipop girl.
Princess Bubblegum?
SR GEICRYES
this lollipop girl.
She was really sweet...
and really smart.
Her best friend was...
rock star girl.
[ Guitar strums ]
'"Nuff said.
They were pretty different,
but they grokked each other.
They lived on
a giant birthday cake
called Weekend City,
where clocks were illegal
and everyone
was chill as heck.
[ Horn toots ]
Ha ha! Hey!
Ha ha!
Hey!
J You don't need a pill
to be chill 7
J Just have a dill pickle &
J Go get tickled &
s And do not kill &
Hey, my page!
J I'm gonna go pee J
J Sorry [
But one day, a mysterious,
cold fart
brought the evil blue tranch
into town.
Ha-ha!
Hey, there!
Hi. You seem like you'd be into
fulfilling
your evolutionary potential
by becoming a potato-head.
Am I right
or am I right?
Remember that clocks were
illegal in Weekend City.
Well,
today's your lucky day...
'‘cause I'm offering
this magic fertilizer.
Whoo!
Marceline: Lollipop girl
turned her down cold.
[ Growls ] I'll never get
these normies
to understand
what they're missing.
To be pure potato.
Pure tato.
Marceline: And so, unwilling
to give up her bad plan...
[ Laughing ]
Marceline: The blue tranch
crop-dusted the whole town,
[ Cloud farts ]
turning everyone
into potato-heads!
[ Coughing ]
Huh?
[ Sniffs ]
Ew!
[ Screams ]
Marceline: But lollipop girl
got it the worst.
Her potato was growing potatoes
on potatoes.
She was turning into a full-on
potato-stack --
and I mean crazy tall.
How tall?
Mmm...
12 giants tall.
Oh! That is even taller
than when PB got tall.
[ Clears throat ]
Anyways...
Rock star girl was tough.
She fought back the curse.
;7
She promised lollipop girl
she would save her.
She travelled all the way
to Potato Town
to confront the blue tranch.
[ Screams ]
s Hey, Blue Tranch
I'll give you one chance J
J To fix my friend
Or I'll kick your pants [
J Lalalala
EFRERERER)
Stop!
I have migraines!
It turned out
the blue tranch's head
was too dense
to appreciate good music.
So rock star girl kicked
her pants with songs.
J Kicks, kicks, kicks
Take that and take this 7
Until, finally, the tranch
gave up the antidote.
There!
Are you happy now?!
Yes!
You go, rock star girl!
But now it gets sad.
Oh, no.
Why?
Well...
Rock star girl
wasn't really sure
if the blue tranch gave her
the real antidote...
or if it was just a trick
to get rid of her.
But the potato curse had
started to spread faster,
so it was kind
of her only shot.
Rock star girl used her last
bit of strength
to climb the potato stalk.
But when she finally reached
the top, she discovered...
[ Gasps |
That lollipop girl
was a completely
different person.
Ha, ha!
No!
Rock star girl
was heart-broken.
All she'd wanted was to have
her best friend back,
but she was gone.
As the potato curse consumed
her final thoughts,
she decided to
embrace her fate...
to -- to explode
into stardust!
[ Strums guitar ]
The end.
What?!
Okay.
But she was you,
right?
If that's how
you interpreted it.
That ending...
was not believable.
Come on. You had a cat
with legs on its back.
I was being emotionally
truthful.
Fine.
I sort of copped out.
I guess I just got some stuff
that's harder to talk about.
Maybe 'cause I never actually
talked about it for real --
not even to myself.
[ Bell dings ]
Pancakes are ready!
Oh.
[ Whirs ]
Burp.
So what's on
the drive?
I will show you.
;7
[ Gasps ]
BMO, pause slide show!
Mom.
Marceline?
Who's the nice lady
and the little girl?
It's um...
I don't know, Beems.
Why don't you tell me
a story
about the little girl
and the nice lady.
Okay!
Once there was a lady
who lived in the moon.
She was called Moon Lady,
and she could only come out
during lunar eclipses.
Once there was a little girl
playing alone by the sea.
"Hello,
little girl."
"Who are you?"
"I'm the moon lady,"
said the Moon Lady.
They became best friends.
They swam in
the dirty ocean water,
rolled down a hill
on a giant beach ball,
played
"can you catch me?"
And rode horses
or something.
They had so much fun.
But, soon, the eclipse
started to vanish...
and the moon lady
had to say good-bye...
because eclipses
can't last forever.
But the little girl
never forgot the moon lady.
Or their friendship.
I think I've heard
a story like that...
a long,
long time ago.
[ Sniffles ]
That was beautiful,
BMO.
Well,
it's a beautiful picture.
The end.
[ Upbeat music plays ]
Come along with me
And the butterflies and bees
This party is so crazy!