[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ Screeches ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Quacks ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We're going to
a very distant land 7
s With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ;&
s The fun will never end J
J It's adventure time &
Jake: Hey, brother.
Pass me that jam,
won't you?
Finn: Sure.
Thanks.
[ Sniffling ]
So, how is your toast?
Pretty good.
Funny, though,
I can kind of taste
the toast's emotions
or something.
Getting ground into flour
and then made into bread
really did a number on this
wheat's sense of self.
[ Whimpering ]
That's a pretty
hyper-developed
sense of taste
you've got there.
Hey. You seem
kind of different.
Nope.
Same old Jake.
You're blue,
you've got
those five eyes,
you're way bigger,
and you keep discovering
strange new abilities.
I think this might be
a situation.
Where's this coming from?
[ Gasps |
Whoops!
Tuck-tuck.
See?
Same old Jake.
Ahhh!
Whoa.
Jack is a crab!
Ahhh!
Same old Jake.
If you say so.
Hmm.
I think I'm handling these
minor changes pretty well.
Besides, a lot of people
are different these days.
Dirt Beer Guy,
you're practically a zombie.
How are you dealing
with it?
Well, I'm basically
the same as before.
The difference
is only physical.
So you agree Finn
is really overreacting?
Totally.
You're the same person
as before.
Heck yeah!
I'm still the same old Jake
on the inside.
Wait, you're Jake?!
Uh, pardon me.
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
That's really something.
You know, I think I figured out
why I make people uneasy.
They're used
to yellow Jake.
[ Speaking Korean ]
Mm-hmm.
[ Grunts ]
[ Laughs ]
Lady, that tickles.
[ Speaking Korean ]
It's okay, lady.
Thanks for trying,
but I'm fine, really.
[ Speaking Korean ]
I love me, too.
Ruff!
Woof!
[ Music playing in distance ]
Ahhh!
Jermaine?
Ahh, mountain colors.
I'm painting
this mountain.
I think it's really
coming together.
That's the mountain?
Yep.
I'm a mirror.
Hey, who's your friend?
Yipe!
Dad?
Look at this.
I can almost
walk the dog.
Your body looks like
one of my paintings.
Pretty weird dream, huh?
This isn't
just a dream body,
this is what my body
looks like when I'm awake.
Oh. Got it.
Ha! I've got it!
What?
I can almost
walk the dog.
Jake: Finn, you up?
Yeah, man.
I had a really bad dream
last night.
So ominous.
These images are going to haunt
me for, like, forever.
Sometimes it helps me
if I draw a bad dream
in picture form.
My crayons!
It was a weird scene,
all right.
Chanting ladies, labyrinths,
classical sculpture.
And Jermaine
was there, too.
The weird thing was that he was
painting abstract art.
So?
F.Y.I., Jermaine hates
abstract art.
He would never paint something
non-representational.
Maybe he's just trying
something new?
It's not in his nature.
Why would he
all of a sudden
get into painting
meaningless shapes?
He's probably fine.
Just feels so out of character,
you know, for Jermaine.
How's the drawing?
Just squiggles.
Fuelish tank!
You are too slow
for the Finnosaurus.
Give up!
Jake: I knew I had seen
that mountain.
[ Scoffs ]
Tank boys,
you have no hope.
[ Laughs ]
\VigaAVigaaVigad!
Brrt!
Who goes there?!
James, it's me, Jake.
You look nothing like Jake,
but I believe you.
I just have to ask
because I'm supposed
to guard the Wasteland.
I was just making
some beans.
Come to my tent!
Okay, but I don't
want any beans.
[ Laughs ] Man!
I could eat beans
all day, every day.
[ Gasps ] Where did you
get that painting?
One day when I was guarding,
I saw Jermaine painting it.
James was like, "Dang,
I like that painting!"
And he was like,
"You can have it."
And I was like,
"Waah?"
You like this?
It doesn't look anything
like a mountain.
I think you're looking
at it wrong.
Where'd Jermaine go...
after?
He went back to his studio,
behind the wall of water.
You mean a waterfall?
No, like the thing
I said.
[ Laughing ]
Hey! None but the
chosen may walk
beyond the wall
of water.
What have you done
with my brother?
Who's your brother?
Jermaine.
Wow. You guys don't look
anything alike.
We're practically twins.
Well, I guess you can walk
beyond the wall of water.
But just this once.
Ooooh!
Can I help you, sir?
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, Bryce.
I'm looking for Jermaine.
Is he behind that door
marked "private"?
No, no, no.
Mr. Jermaine won't be seeing
anyone today.
His wishes for privacy
were quite explicit.
You wouldn't want to interrupt
Mr. Jermaine.
He's a brilliant painter.
Yeah, he used to be.
Now you got him painting
all this nonsense.
I'm just his humble dealer.
So many times
I've watched him
painting,
painting, painting.
What's really going on,
Bryce?
My dad told me
all about your demon tricks.
Well, now I don't want to say
anything bad about your dad,
but...
[ Blows landing, grunting ]
[ Muffled words ]
Bro?
I'm here to save you.
Hmm?
Oh. Hey.
I'm not sure
if this is done yet.
It's hard to tell when an
abstract is finished.
Jermaine,
what's wrong with you?
Who's taken away your identity
as a landscape painter?
There's nothing wrong
with me, Jake.
I just changed a little.
You seem like you've changed
a little bit, too.
No, I just look different.
Eh, that sounds
like denial.
No, it doesn't!
Come on, bro.
Nothing's different!
I'm the same!
Same old Jake!
Completely... normal!
[ Groans ]
This looks bad,
but deep down,
I'm not different.
And you're not different
either, right?
You'll go back
to painting landscapes.
No one
is making me do this.
I painted so many landscapes
that the shapes of the land
began to lose
their meaning.
And the shapes
broke apart to me,
so I painted them
like that.
And it's not like
my new paintings
erase my old paintings.
They're both me.
Okay.
I think I'm starting
to get it.
I like the new look,
by the way.
'‘Cause you like your brothers
to be crazy shapes?
Sure.
Also, Dad told me you might go
through some changes one day.
Huh?
He told me
to be supportive.
But I would've
done that anyway.
I wonder what he meant.
You know
how secretive Dad was.
Sorry I don't have
more answers.
Well, do you have
any more of these paintings?
The shapes are always changing.
Changing is their normal state,
like us.
Even if we're not changing
on the outside,
we're changing
on the inside constantly.
There's some stuff about me
that I've been ignoring
for a long time.
I'm afraid of that stuff.
But it's part of who I am.
As long as I know the shape of
my soul, I'll be all right.
Wow. You really
understand my art.
Oh, I totally
don't understand anything.
[ Both laugh ]
[ Whistling ]
Hey, you're back.
Yeah, I went to see Jermaine.
He says hi.
No, I mean, like,
you're really back.
Huh?
Different, yet the same.
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!