[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ Screeches ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Quacks ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We're going to
a very distant land 7
s With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ;&
s The fun will never end J
J It's adventure time &
;7
Oh...bananas.
Bananas.
BMO, it's your turn
to say "bananas."
There is a strange cloud
following us.
Come and see.
I'm too comfortable
to move.
Can you just
describe it?
Forget the cloud.
Tell us a story instead.
A nice campfire
bedtime story.
Once upon a time,
there was this...
cool guy and a banana
with sunglasses.
Please, no.
Literally
anything but bananas.
Once upon a time,
there was a...
bandana with sunglasses.
Eh?
[ Both snoring ]
Good night, bed.
Good night, weird cloud.
Good night, weird orb.
[ Snoring ]
-Hey, Jake home.
[ Applause ]
-Hey, Joshua home too!
Whatcha doing, Dad?
Scrambling eggs?
Yes,
in the refrigerator!
[ Laughter ]
Oh, boy.
I can see
where this is going.
[ Laughter ]
Man, that got old quick.
What's going on here,
Jermaine?
Wha -- wha --
what do you think?
It's a dream, dum-dum.
Oh, right.
'Cause dream bro times.
And 'cause
we burned this place down.
Last year.
Anyway,
what's up, Jermaine?
Fine.
What do you think all these
blank canvasses represent?
These are,
um, mine actually.
I've really been getting into
landscape painting.
Mostly, like, forests
and seascapes.
Strictly
representational art.
Dude, that's awesome!
We should collab on
an interdisciplinary performance
or something.
Ah, that's not really my scene,
man.
I'm into real things.
[ Snoring ]
I'm flying!
No more walking for this guy.
You hear that dudes?
You're retired.
Just gonna float around
like a chubby bat.
Water Nymph:
Hey, Finn.
I made these cloud sculptures
for you.
Yes!
Flying Finn will never
miss out on anything.
People will be all,
"Too bad Finn's not here."
And T'll be like,
"Look up, surface dorks."
[ Disco music plays ]
Director!
Where are
your accessories?
Let's get the director's
accessories, please?
Okay, time for the show!
[ Applause ]
We never have any fun
when BMO's not here.
All we do is hit things.
[ Laughter ]
I love art.
Okay, boys,
I got a job for you.
Think you can handle it?
Of course you can.
Now, dig.
Jake: Yeah, okay.
Why are we doing this,
Papa?
Never you mind!
Dig.
[ Thumping ]
[ Sighing ]
Man, I'm out of shape.
I can hear my own heart
palpitating.
Jeepers creepers.
Don't mind that.
Just dig faster.
Dig faster,
you dew droppers!
Brrr!
Hey, it's PB.
Finn,
what are you up to?
Oh, nothing.
Just using my power of flight!
It's scientifically impossible
for a human boy to fly.
You're gonna wish it was
scientifically possible
to put those words
back in your mouth.
Look!
Huuup!
Grrr.
Stop holding me back!
[ Thunder crashes ]
Huh?
Aah!
Finn, what are these?
Aaaaahhhh!
I'm bored.
I'm boring.
There's only one person
who can save this play.
-Yay, he's here!
BMO! BMO!
[ Applause ]
-A bootleg BMO?
I'm bad!
But you still like me.
Boo!
This show is terrible!
I want to
talk to the director.
The director is right this way,
director.
Director, the director's here
to see you.
Listen, the play
started out good,
but it didn't have
any relatable characters.
[ Gasping ] Football!
I'm not Football.
Oh, good.
I'm AMO!
Oh, bad!
[ Digging ]
[ Shovels clanging ]
The heck!
Dad,
the hole is gone!
-Boys?
-Dad?
Joshua:
Boys, the hole is gone!
Looks like you buried me.
Why'd you do it?
Aah! Dig! Aah! Dig!
Mom. Mom.
What are you doing?
Mm.
I'm sure this is all
really symbolic,
but it's dang comfy.
[ Gasping ]
[ Slurping ]
I don't like
where this is headed.
I'm out of here.
Ohhh.
Mom, Dad....
[ Whimpering ]
How does it look?
I think it looks cool.
Nice.
Oh!
;7
What the plop?
-Help...
-Jake?
Jake:
I'm aging up here!
Okay, bird thoughts, Finn.
Eggs, nest, wings, worms!
Jake?
IEI
Finn....
[ Coughs ]
I'm old.
[ BMO cries ]
Now it's too relatable!
Cool, backup skin.
-Aah!
-That's not what I wrote!
Huh?
I really respect that
you do your own stunts.
You're brother's gonna
have to step up his game
to keep up with you.
We have to do something
about these crow's-feet,
or everyone's gonna know
you're too old to play Jake.
But I am Jake.
[ Hissing ]
What's he saying?
Your lines.
Hss, hss, shss, shss.
Uh, hss, sshs, hss.
Just read the cue cards.
BMO:
It's just a rehearsal,
but it's not okay
to be really bad.
BMO?
What are you doing here?
This is my nightmare!
-No, this is my --
Oh, our nightmares,
I guess.
And you're here with us.
[ Rumbling ]
-I am?
The unconscious
is so complicated.
Ahh!
Ahh! Ahh!
Bird thoughts!
Perches, birdseed, hooting!
It's not working!
That weird
eye cloud again.
This fall's taking longer
than I thought it would.
I wish I had a game
to pass the time
while we're plunging
to our death.
Or, like, a puzzle
or something.
A puzzle.
So what if
I put this here?
um...
;7
Uh, who are you?
Okay, you're some kind of
nightmare princess.
But where are we?
We're dead. I knew it.
I'm guessing we're still asleep
on the boat.
I think she entered
our nightmares
and mashed them up in order
to communicate with us.
What do you
want to tell us?
Banana?
[ Gasps ] She wants to hear
my banana story!
[ All gasp ]
She's harvesting
our mind-fruits!
Wait, do you just want us to
give you some bananas?
Well, there's loads on our boat.
You can take as many as you --
No, Finn!
You have to negotiate first.
We won't trade them
for anything less
than something pretty
and/or cool.
Enjoy those bananas!
Pretty!
What is this,
like, nightmare juice?
Let's drink it!
[ Yawns ] Hey,
look how close to home we are.
Land ho!
Hm.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Ooh, la-la.
How's it look, BMO?
Like a dream.
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &