[ Mouse squeaks ]
[ Penguins chirp ]
[ All cheering ]
[ Screeches ]
s Adventure time J
J Come on, grab your friends &
J We're going to
a very distant land 7
s With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ;&
s The fun will never end J
J It's adventure time &
[ Electronic hum ]
Finn: Squish.
Photosynthesize!
Photo--
You grabbing a snack, Fern?
Yeah.
Water and light combine
so I can make my own food.
In case
I don't catch anything.
Come on, man.
Don't be so dow --
[ Reel clicks, squeaks ]
[ Gasps |
Hey, I got something!
[ Reel clicking ]
Hey, I got something, too!
Nice.
[ Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
[ Sighs ]
Pretty weird fish, huh?
That's me --
the dude who dinks it up,
just like I dinked it up
when you left Ooo.
I was supposed
to protect it.
Instead,
it went all crazy.
I didn't even help.
I just covered myself
in root beer
and danced around
like a dummy.
I can't do anything right!
Hey, stop it.
You need a squoze?
Yes.
[ Grunts ]
I feel better.
Sometimes being a good dude
ain't about not dinking it.
Learn from your dinks.
Like, you know my first battle
with a giant?
I never told anybody this,
but --
You boom-boomed
in your shorts.
I know.
I have your memories.
Yeah, I boom-boomed.
The point is I learned from it,
and now I'm Finn.
You got to learn
how to be Fern.
[ Stomping, rumbling ]
Both: What's that sound?
Oh, I bet
it's @a monster.
Let's fight this dude
Fern's way.
Yeah.
[ Stomping, rumbling continue ]
Aaaaah!
Both: Sweet P?
WEEEELL
Both: Whoa!
Sweet P:
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
Both: [ Gasp ]
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Okay, Fern, what do you think
we should do next?
Mm, sever his tendons?
[ Winces ]
Before you say no,
it would stop him from running.
We're gonna handle this
librarian style.
[ Crying ]
[ Whispering ] Shh.
Librarian.
Kiss.
You can renew the book
and bring it back next week.
Library style.
Squ-0-0-0ze.
Ooh.
Mm.
Great thinking, Fern.
I just copied you.
Is that thinking?
What up, buttercup?
Why you run, pork bun?
The monster!
Was it LSP?
The monster that whispers me
bad thoughts.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Whispering stops ]
Sweet P: Mommy and Daddy came
to save me,
but they said
I was imagining things,
which was true.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
Sweet P: But last night,
I really did see it.
[ Screams ]
And I've been running
and running since then.
Aww, Sweet P.
It sounds like you might
just be having bad dreams.
No, I only have
one dream anymore.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
Uhh...
But the whisper monster is
even scarier,
saying stuff like,
"Sweet P, you're bad.
You always have been bad."
I don't want to be bad.
[ Crying ]
Oh, you're not bad.
You're super good.
Now, let's get you home.
But it's getting late,
and bogs are super dangerous
to travel in at night.
Your body will be preserved
for thousands of years.
No one will ever find you.
[ Wailing ]
Fern!
Okay, okay, we'll see you
in the morning, Tree Trunks.
[ Telephone beeps ]
All right, bedtime,
Sweet P.
You want me
to knock him out?
Er, not this time.
How about a bedtime story?
Yes, please.
Once there was
a kingdom of spaghetti.
Mmm.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Whispering ]
Punch, punch.
Kiss, kiss.
The Lich:
Listen to your bones.
Fern.
[ Teeth clicking ]
Fern!
[ Gasps |
Hey. What's up?
I heard something.
Can you see what it is
with your tree senses?
I don't have those.
[ Rustle ]
[ Footsteps ]
Uh, can I help you?
Oh, sorry.
We heard you scuttling
around and thought --
What?
You didn't hear me
"scuttling around."
Foxes are silent hunters.
I mean, geez, do you know
how rude that is?
[Groans] Gonna be brooding
about this all week.
Sorry, man.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
Look.
[ Whispering continues ]
Aah!
Get off him!
Lich Hand: Huh?
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
I got him!
Oh, no.
I know where I've seen
that thing before.
[ Ominous tones play ]
Huh?
Lich Hand:
[ Laughs evilly ]
BMO: Finn, Jake!
What's shaking?
You will not believe
what just happened.
It must've been the day that BMO
found that little sailor hat.
Hold him down, Fern!
That hand is
the flippin' Lich!
I know.
[ Chuckles evilly ]
Yes, child.
I returned once more to --
Bah! Bah! Bah!
Bah! Evil!
You're gonna get it for messing
with our boy Sweet P.
That vessel may appear harmless,
but he came from me.
Once I remind him of his legacy,
The Lich shall reign once more.
Isn't that right, son?
- Aah!
Finn!
Lich Hand:
[ Laughs evilly ]
Ugh!
I dinked it again!
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
Why did Mr. Hand
call me "son"?
Was that my monster daddy?
Okay, delegate,
delegate --
Fern, stay here
and guard Sweet P.
I'm gonna try and catch up.
Don't trust me
to guard anything.
I'm a total scrub-up.
Dude, there's already
one Lich loose in Ooo0.
If Sweet Pea turns
e-v-i-l tonight,
there might be a second.
I need you here.
You got this!
You got this.
[ The Lich's voice ]
Quickly, while the boy is gone,
we must seek out
my well of power.
Sweet P:
[ Normal voice ] No!
Am I turning
into a monster?
That's the working theory.
Jake:I can't come
to the phone right now.
I'm either hanging with Finn,
my kids, my G.F., or I'm dead.
Bye!
[Tone beeps]
Hey, man,
hit me when you get this.
[ Clicks tongue ]
Dude's missing a Lich fight.
Okay, Lich.
Get ready to die --
again --
for, like,
the fifth time.
Oh, hey,
it's this awful place.
[ Rustling ]
Oh, you're tricky, huh?
[ Indistinct whispering ]
I can hear you down there!
[ Whispering continues ]
Speak up, man.
What?
[ Rustling ]
Aah! Ooh!
Aaaaaah!
The Lich:
[ Chuckles evilly ]
You bested me
in many worlds, child,
but I always return.
[ Rock hisses ]
[ Grunts ]
You're so evil, it's boring.
You're basic, man.
Yes.
While a mortal world doubts
and questions,
I know exactly what I am.
I am the ceaseless wheel,
the last scholar of Golb.
I am your doom.
Sweet P: Skull man!
Huh?
I, too, am doom.
Hey, what's going on
up there?
[ Laughs evilly ]
Child, you have failed.
The vessel has turned.
We reign now
as twin kings of ruin.
Sweet P.
I'm not a king of ruin.
What?
Iam sweet.
You're just a naughty hand.
Beast, obey me!
Obey -- No!
[ Grunting ]
[ Slice ]
Eesh.
[ Groans ]
[ Spirits groan, scream ]
Hooray!
You're a natural!
But where's Fern?
He wouldn't let me follow you,
so I knocked him out cold.
Yeah, I met
my bio dad once, too.
He wasn't evil incarnate, but
he was kind of a crummy dude.
T.T. and Mr. P. love you.
That's all that matters.
Fern, Sweet P saved me
and slew The Lich!
That's great.
Sweet P:
You're just a naughty hand.
The Lich:
Beast, obey me!
Obey -- no!
Male voice:
End of message.
To repeat this message,
press 7.
What?
- To save...
Fern:I don't get it.
Why isn't it working out
being myself?
Finn's off having fun
defeating losers.
I can't even guard a baby.
It doesn't matter
how hard I try.
I'll always just be
in the shadow of the real Finn.
Unless I could become...
the only Finn.
Uh, yeah, but that's
a weird thing to call me.
J Come along with me J
s And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!