[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
J "Adventure Time" J
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time"“ J
[Gasps]
Whew.
A goblet of sparkling
apple juice for milady.
Thanks, Finn.
Hey...where'd you get
this goblet?
Oh, uh, I think we won it
in a fight with an octopus
we were fighting in, like,
a sea cave full of treasure?
(\\[o
It was from when BMO was
playing dress-up.
It reminds me
of a cup my uncle used to have.
You mean your Uncle Gumbald,
right?
Do tell.
You never talk
about your family.
I don't know.
Families are tricky.
You guys know what I mean,
right?
We have to go back a ways,
like 800 years ago.
[Whirs, beeps]
[Glass shatters]
[Sighs]
GOBLIN: Help!
Help me!
Oh, goodness me.
Someone please help me.
I'm a defenseless little goblin
surrounded by all this loot.
Boo-hoe.
[Animal grunts]
Oh, you poor thing.
Here.
Have a drink to ease your nerves
while I untie you.
Pfft!
Aah!
The time for faking is over now.
Give me all your stuff.
[Chuckles] What?
You brought a peashooter
to a techno-harpoon fight?!
-[Snap]
- Aah!
[Groans]
Aah-aah-aaah!
[Slurping]
Mm?
Another close call today, Neddy.
[Squeals]
[Whimpers]
Neddy, you sweet chicken.
[Beatboxing]
It was a lot different
back in the Mother Gum.
-[Squeaks]
- We all had each other's backs.
I'm going to make more of us,
Neddy.
I know you don't care,
and that's fine.
But I need to be
around people like me.
O-kay!
This is it, Neddy.
We're getting relatives!
[Electricity crackles]
[Whimpers]
[Grunts]
[Sizzling]
[Laughs] It worked!
Your name's Aunt Lolly!
A pleasure to meet you, dear.
And you're Cousin Chicle.
You're a full 2.3 meters tall.
Naturally. I am a gentleman
of high standing.
Oh, Cousin Chicle.
And finally, Uncle Gumbald!
This is your favorite mug.
Ah, yes.
I'm your great uncle.
The mug proclaims it so.
Aren't they great, Neddy?
You'll be my protectors,
my advisers, my family.
[Whimpers]
Hmm.
I'm heading out, Neddy.
What?
What?!
Morning, small niece.
Uncle Gumbald,
the taffy trees are gone!
I know.
I chopped 'em down last night.
Yesterday,
I realized these trees
were not being utilized
to their full potential,
so I elected to build
this cabin.
This is but the first step
in building my glorious
new candy city.
I've already drawn up
the plans for it.
All of this will be apartments.
And did you notice
the family crest I designed?
It's a "G" for, uh..."Gum."
Why does it look like your head?
[Laughs] You're such a curious
little girl.
We're a lifestyle brand now.
[Grunts]
Success!
Now instead of worrying
about his dumb city,
Uncle can come here
to picnic, swim,
and, uh...fish!
[Electricity crackles]
Welcome to life, Candyfish.
[Gasps]
I can't breathe air!
UNCLE GUMBALD: Bonnie!
What have you done
to my building site?
I made us a butterscotch lake
and a fish to live in it.
But that's where
the gift shop was gonna go.
Now it's just gonna be
volleyballs, water skis,
and shrimp cocktails.
Sounds nice.
Did you say you "made"
this creature?
Come on.
You'll appreciate him more
once you watch him swim around.
Bonnibel...you've micromanaged
me for the last time.
Huh?
Hmm.
I think it's time for Bonnie
to be re-branded.
Niece, now that I've had
to stare at it for weeks,
I've got to admit that
your lake was a very good idea.
- Ja! Sehr gut!
- Very wunderbar.
Oh, I'm so happy.
We got you a gift to say thanks.
It's right outside, Prinzessin.
[Gasps]
You got me a car?
Yes, a car.
But also...a boyfriend!
Hi, babe. Beep beep!
Wait, what?
All right, you nut.
Have fun on your date.
Date?!
-[Engine starts]
- Let's go, babe.
Beep beep!
[Tires screech]
What a naive little child.
Date's over, babe.
Pick you up tomorrow
to get matching tattoos.
I'm back
from that terrible date.
Hello?
UNCLE GUMBALD:
Thank you for coming
to the mandatory
optimization meeting.
Tonight, we address...
the "Bonnie problem."
Bonnie problem?
Our future city is on course
to be a rousing success,
barring only one obstacle --
our complete lack
of competent leadership.
BB's the leader?
I thought she was a mime.
'Cause I never hear
a word she says.
- Oh, Cousin Chicle!
Dang, Chicle, that's cold.
I have formulated a happy juice
that will render her
as docile and simple-minded
as her cutie BF,
young Mr. Creampuff.
[Gasps]
All we have to do is sprinkle
some of this on her breakfast,
and we'll be in charge.
Let us celebrate
with coup d'etat cupcakes.
Poisoned cakes.
[Poof!]
Where am I?
Oh, right, the poison.
[Poof!]
I don't know what's happening!
VL EERIEE
- Whee! Whee!
Ah! My first candy employees.
What have you done?
This isn't
what I made you to be.
No, you wanted us to be
lowly pet fish,
swimming
in your narcissistic pond.
But I am your equal!
You're not like me.
You're bad.
I am the future.
Come on, Bonnie.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'm going to fix you.
And then I'm going to fix
that sniveling gumwad, Neddy.
Don't touch my brother!
A pea-shooter?
The juice!
Nooooo!
[Laughs] Hey!
Where's the party?
[Goofy laughter]
[Sighs] What a mess.
But they do seem happier now,
so unburdened and pliable.
You, the crunchy ball,
dance for me.
Sure.
Come on, lady.
Do the crunchy dance.
Oh, Crunchy.
Sure, I'll dance
with my candy people.
Yay for the lady!
BONNIBEL:
Call me...Princess.
ALL: Hurrah!
Whoa, for real?
Like I said,
families are tricky.
[Gasps]
BMO!
Where did you get this cup?
From that guy!
The guy on the cup!
The guy whose face
is on the cup, that guy!
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!