[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
J "Adventure Time" J
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time"“ J
[Chatter, laughter, dinging]
Birthday boy-e-e-e!
Enjoying your party?
It's great having fun
with all my friends.
Well, some of my friends,
mostly banana guards.
Yeah, sorry about that.
The Candy Kingdom
is in full lockdown
until I can sort out the rumors
about my Uncle Gumbald.
He's been gone for years,
but we should stay vigilant.
Don't worry, Pb.
Now that I'm 17,
I'm feelin' ready for anything.
Feels like I'm really
hitting my stride, y'know?
MARCELINE: Finn, I want to give
you your gift before I forget.
It's a harmonica.
Awesome!
[Inhales sharply]
Finn, I designed
an exciting new game for you.
Show me.
It's called
"Birthday Boyfighter."
[Game music plays]
Looks like another hit.
STARCHY: Finn, Starchy
didn't get you squat.
I got you a present, too.
It has emotional
and metaphorical significance.
It's beautifully wrapped.
Wonder what it is.
It's an elk's heart.
Oh, cool.
I don't have one of those.
[Thumping]
What's that sound?
STARCHY:
It's zombies.
HUNTRESS WIZARD:
Sounds like hooves.
-[Galloping intensifies]
- STARCHY: Zombie cows.
You're
green
|
I'm the Green Knight!
And before you ask,
yes, of course,
I brought you
a birthday present.
It's a battle axe.
That's some axe.
Am I an axe guy, though?
I've always thought of myself
as a sword guy.
GREEN KNIGHT: But only if you
play me a game for it.
What's the game?
GREEN KNIGHT: Oh, this game
is called "All you have to do
is strike me with it,
and it is yours."
Mm?
[All murmuring]
[Inhales sharply]
I can't axe some stranger.
Wait a minute!
Where's Jake?
I know what's going on.
No, I don't think you do.
Relax, Princess.
Jake loves playing
birthday pranks on me.
Yes, of course,
one of Jake's classic pranks.
Okay, I'm in.
[Clank]
May your aim be steady.
[Laughs]
Sure thing...Jake!
[Clank]
- I win!
-[Cheers and applause]
- Yeah, Finn!
JAKE:
Happy birthday, Finn.
-[Scary music plays]
-[Shrieks]
Jake! When did you --
Whose head did I --
Are you pranking me?
What? No.
My prank is this fake-out gift.
Huh?
What's this guy's deal?
Oh, nuh-uh!
Banana guards, surround him!
And be on the lookout
for anything else strange!
BANANA GUARDS:
Hup, hup, hup, hup!
Surrender, please.
Princess, is that strange?
Yes!
I did good.
[Screaming]
My guards!
- I got this.
-[Shing!]
Raaahh!!
[Hisses]
Eell
[Shing!]
Get him!
[Vells]
[Groans]
Aw.
He might have
an invisible shield.
But I'm not sure,
because it's invisible.
Owiee.
Yes.
It's an invisible shield.
An invisible shield.
I've got a device
for the dissolution
of invisible shields.
[Whirring, beeping]
[Fizzles]
Impossible.
[Laughs maniacally]
Heh!
Back off, everyone.
He's using some advanced
mystery tech.
[Laughs maniacally]
Okay, let's talk.
What do you want to talk about?
Where did you come from?
Why are you playing
this weird game with Finn?
[Laughing maniacally]
He's playing
Mr. Laughing Silent Guy.
-[Green Knight laughs]
- Game's over, bro.
[Laughs] The game isn't over
until I strike you.
Hmm.
Let's come up with
a better way to settle this,
like reasonable late teens.
I'm listening.
Well, we've got everything
set up for party games.
How about if I beat you
two out of three,
you got to answer our questions.
Psst! Nuh!
And if I win...chop, chop.
Deal.
Wait, Finn, I think he's
plotting something --
I-It's fine. I'm 17.
I'm hittin' my stride.
[Beeps]
Hey, Green Knight,
why are they all mimey?
Ah, just to keep things fair.
[Clanking]
[Sighs]
I don't think he can hear us.
[Laughs sinisterly]
Okay, guy.
Why don't we start with
something basic
like...balls and coconuts.
Hup! Hup!
Hup, hup, hup, hup
hup, hup, hup.
[Clank]
Ba-ba-ba-boom!
Boom!
- Okay, Finn!
- Yeah, yeah!
- You got it, Finn!
- You go, boy!
FINN:
[Slow-mo] Boooooooom!
[Belches in slow-mo]
[Tap]
[Normal voice] Aw, what?
I'll let you have that one,
'‘cause I'm a big boy today.
But let's see you try and beat
four out of five, huh?
[Whirring]
How do you like them coconuts?
I hate them coconuts.
Somethings wrong.
Yeah, I swear that looked fake.
It was.
I saw it all with
my Huntress vision.
Finn is totally getting played.
[Inhales]
All right.
You got a freaky curveball, man.
But can you climb a greasy pole?
A greasy pole?!
It's hard enough climbing
a non-greasy pole!
Ready?
-[Chuckles] Mm-hmm!
[Speaks quickly]
One, two, three, go!
[Grunts]
Ha, ha!
-[Panting]
-[Slow clapping in distance]
-[Normal voice] Huh?
-[Slow clap]
Finn, you climb so good.
I guess you win this round.
Hmm.
Yay, Finn!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- That's right!
- Yay, yay!
- What, what?
Now's our chance, BMO.
Is -- Is Finn gonna be okay?
He's got this.
He's 17.
Who's the ma-a-a-n?
Who's the 17-year-old
ma-a-a-a-n?
Hoo!
You've been a good sport,
so I'll let you
choose the tiebreaker.
[Muffled] Don't do it!
- Wait, don't do it!
- Not a good idea!
Very well. Hmm...
How about a game of some good
old-fashioned arm wrestling?
Arm wrestling, huh?
I see what you did there.
My guns are obviously
weak as heck
from climbing that greasy pole.
If only I had some kind of...
-[Whirs]
-...superhuman robot arm.
Bam!
BOTH:
Three, two, one, go!
[Strained grunts]
[Strained] Ahh!
You can't tell from my face,
but I am smiling triumphantly.
Nooo!
It's...my...birthday!
I know.
It's my birthday, too.
Fern?
- Oh, no!
- No! Finn!
[Shing!]
[Fern chuckles]
Finally, I win!
-[Beeps]
- UNCLE GUMBALD: Fern!
We've seen enough.
[Beep, whoosh]
-[Groans]
- Finn! Finn!
Finn, are you all right?
STARCHY:
I love you, Finn!
Quick, eat this elk's heart.
What is this?
It's a family reunion.
Uncle Gumbald, Cousin Chicle,
Aunt Lolly.
How are you back?!
Here's a hint.
[As LSP] "Oh, my Glob."
Lumpy Space Princess.
[Whoosh]
When she reset Ooo,
she reset...you.
For 800 years, you kept us
imprisoned, Princezzin.
No, you were happier
as candy people.
We thought we were.
But don't worry.
It's your turn to be happy now.
Get juiced.
[Hisses]
Back off, gumwad!
The vampire girl
is legitimately scary.
Very well.
You've withessed
our superior technology
and watched
your champion crushed.
[Vomits]
We'll go...for now.
[Laughs]
This is my worst B-day ever.
BMO AND JAKE: & Happy birthday to you &
ALL: s Happy birthday to you J
J Happy birthday... &
& Mr. Finn Mart-ens J
J Happy birthday to you 7
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!