[Mouse squeaks]
[Penguins chirp]
[Screeches]
[All cheering]
[Quacks]
J "Adventure Time" J
s Come on, grab your friends 7
J We're going to
very distant lands J
J With Jake the dog
and Finn the human &
J The fun will never end J
J It's "Adventure Time"“ J
[Rapping] & C-C-C-C-Clam Rap &
J Juicy like nectar ;&
s My name is Neptr &
J I stay rapping no matter
what the weather [
J I'm by the fire 'cause
it's hot like a dryer J
Clams and rappin'.
Doesn't get any better
than this, right, Phoebe?
It's actually my first Clam Rap.
[Beatboxing]
[Rapping]
J; Clams, clams 7’
J Ate this plate of clams ;&
J Utensils weren't provided &
J So I had to use my hands 7
J I'm gonna be unhappy &
J If it happens agains &
Boom!
[Cheering]
Princess, what you got?
Yeah, dump it in, stir it up.
[Rapping] & I'm like a
library book, so check me out 7
J Read my front and back cover
so you know what I'm about &
J I'm straight droolin’,
spittin' out rhymes »
J People gather 'round
and they're waitin' in lines &
J I got a lot of combinations
of words to throw 7’
J To let you know I got glow 7
J I said it 'cause
you just don't know 7
J So what now,
what's up, what's up, bro? ;&
[Cheers and applause]
J You beat me fair and square 7
J 'Cause maybe
somethings in the air &
J I'm wearing unlucky shoes,
not my favorite pair &
[Audience groans]
[indistinct conversation]
Hello, there, young lady.
I heard you lay down
some serious rhymes earlier.
[Munches]
My card.
FLAME PRINCESS:
Victor Marilyn?
I'm a talent scout by trade,
and, uh...
[Munches]
And I'd love to book you for a
big-time rap battle next week --
Rap Fest Aid.
Whoa.
I've never heard
of Rap Fest Aid.
It sure sounds like
the big time.
But before I can
book you anywhere,
I'm gonna have to have you sign
some waivers and release forms.
Boilerplate stuff.
Don't bother reading it.
Okay.
[Chuckling] Okay.
I'll get this paperwork
processed,
and we'll be in business.
Toronto!
[Laughs]
Yes, it's me!
And I am making my move from
second banana to top dog.
As stated in the contract
that you just signed,
if you lose Rap Fest Aid,
the Fire Kingdom
becomes my property.
What?!
Aw, don't worry.
Look at this mug.
You could out-rap him
any day of the week.
TORONTO:
Oh, you won't be facing me.
You'll have to beat the most
gifted rapper of our time.
Son of Rap Bear!
See you in a week.
- Son of Rap Bear?
I wonder if he's any relation
to Rap Bear.
FLAME PRINCESS:
Rap Bear lives in there?
It's surprisingly nice.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Rap Bear.
What happened?
[Groans]
My son and I
were having Sunday dinner.
We were lightly rapping
back and forth.
It turned into a rap battle.
He threw out rhyme after rhyme.
I couldn't keep up.
You got beat by your own son?
Are his rap powers
that much greater than yours?
Yes.
Why are you asking about my son?
Flame Princess
is going up against him
one-on-one
in a freestyle battle.
[Gasps]
That kid will take you apart.
He rapped my legs off.
Rap Bear,
Son of Rap Bear's father,
said his son, Son of Rap Bear,
would be at tonight's open mic.
FLAME PRINCESS:
Dude, let's sit back here.
[Rapping]
J You're a small bear J
> With fuzzy hair over there &
J; Get away from me,
I don't wanna share my air J
J Doesn't matter where,
anywhere, everywhere with you &
J Chop you in two
with my rap kung fu &
Are you scared of me?
Boo!
[Rapping] & You're like a
cookie who's about to crumble 7
J Your rapping is stale 7
J Also, you mumble ;&
J Did you just make a mistake
smellin' like a cake 7
& Who just stumbled into
a lyrical rumble? &
2 Your raps causes naps J
J You look a little frail
and you're about to collapse 7
J You'll know you got beat when
you hear the people's claps 7
[Cheers and applause]
- Whoa.
Look who decided
to come out to play.
The news on the streets is
you're gonna battle me
at Rap Fest Aid.
This is a joke, right?
Hear me out.
What are you even gonna
rap about?
J You've been in a bottle
since the age of 2
J I got shampoo
more worldly than you
J I will do laps
around your raps J&
J I crush my opponents
and collect their caps &
J If you wanna keep yours on,
I suggest you run J
J People holla at me
because I'm number one J
Son of Rap Bear is right.
I just rap about rapping.
I haven't traveled the world
or done anything really.
Finn! Let's go on
some adventures!
What?
It would really help me build up
some quick life experience.
I don't know if life is like
a test you can cram for.
This is for my kingdom.
I've got to try.
Unh. Yo.
J Went along with Finn
from mission to mission J&
J To win the battle
for the Fire Kingdom J
J Worked at Pizza Sassy
'‘cause I'm not too classy ;&
s Climbed a rock, had to mind
the clock, ticktock &
J I go with Starchy,
I hunt ghosts &
J I blow fire
with my saxophone J
s I'm a submarine teen,
ain't nothin' I ain't seen ;&
2 All around I'm known,
I'm the girl on the throne ;&
J Givin' back rubs, in the
bathtubs, hittin' math clubs 7
s Makin mad grub
to outspit a rap cub [
J I got solutions
to this rap pollution 7
s When I'm done with
Son of Rap Bear ;&
J He's gonna need new shins &
2 Unh, yeah, I'm experienced 7
J Solid like a pebble
in aquarium J
J I drop knowledge like I'm
Bubblegum if she was librarian 7
[Groans]
That was good!
I thought trying new things
would make me new
and interesting,
but I just feel like a hack.
Maybe there is an interesting
thing about you
that you just don't realize.
Like how Neptr only just found
out there is a face on his can,
and now he thinks the can
is his conjoined twin.
I don't expect you to understand
the bond I share with my family.
Family.
FLAME KING: [Humming]
No room for the body.
Let's make him swim.
FLAME PRINCESS:
Knock, knock.
Is that you, bun bun?
- Aah!
- Hi, Dad.
You're not here to put me back
in lantern jail, are you?
I guess I wanted to talk.
Oh.
It seems like lots changed
since I last saw you.
Maybe we actually have a shot
at putting the past behind us
and, I don't know,
being normal with each other.
I know exactly
what you're saying.
I've totally gotten over being
in lantern jail, so we're good.
Well, I was kind of hoping
you could acknowledge
hurting me, like --
Phoebes, come on.
It's better to be thankful
for what you have now --
an awesome chipmunk dad.
Uh, I'm gonna put on some music.
You're totally welcome
to listen, or not.
Totally up to you.
So you won't even apolo-
-[Vocalizing]
-...gize?
[Rapping] & Water chestnuts
roasting in my gut J
J Acorn squash you
with a peanut butter cup
J IT'll tell you
what's the diff-er-ence J
J Between a legume and a nut J
J One goes in your mouth
and the other out your butt &
J Just put the cash into my
stash and I give you cashew ;&
J Put your face in my
almond butter paste, yo 7
-[Groans]
J Pecan can do J
s Or pecan you don't, bro 7
- Drama.
J On your way out,
take a pistachio &
TORONTO:
What's up, Rap Fest Aid?!
[Laughs]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the battle
for the Fire Kingdom!
To my left,
we have the Flame Princess.
[Cheers and applause]
And to my right,
the reigning champion,
Son of Rap Bear!
Yo.
[Cheers and applause]
And go, Son of Rap Bear.
J Yo, I'm a word wizard &
s I'm Son of Rap Bear ;s
J But you're a fire hazard,
maybe I should be scared &
s I mean, I do hear
you're dangerous J
J When your temper flares &
J Do guys even date you or just
cook wieners in your hair &
[Audience "Ohs"]
J I guess there was that fire
guy that wanted to marry you ;&
s Was it Don Jon
with the big guns?
J Oh, but you're not into
macho men, are you? J
J You like 'em soft and round
like cinnamon-flavored buns &
[Audience "Ohs"]
He's good.
[Cheers and applause]
J I got more rhymes in my hair
than you ever will &
J You better run away
like it's a fire drill &
J You're so lame and stinky,
more spark from my pinky &
J I'm a flaming master &
J I'm...slinky, hinky &
[Thinking] Oh, Glob.
What am I saying?
She's choking.
[Audience boos]
Oh.
FLAME KING: Hi, Phoebe!
Huh?
Dad, you came to see me rap?
No, I had no idea
you were in this.
Isn't that crazy?
Don't feel bad about losing,
though!
He's way out of your league!
Dad!
Why the heck did I even try
to talk to you?
J You only ever cared about
things like koalas 7
> And chipmunks
and baby kangaroos ;&
J It's actually pretty sad &
J I mean, I usurped you
when I was 14 7
J I thought
we could be friends &
J I don't know
what I was thinking &
J I don't need you or anyone J
J 'Cause I'm the real
Flame King &
-[Cheers and applause]
- Get it, girl!
And as for Son of Rap Bear...
J You're so unoriginal, you put
your own dad in a wheelchair &
J Just so you could steal his
name and ride on his fame J
J But without it, you're just
a sad kid full of hot air &
Hmm.
J Y'all can try to bully me
or scam me, I don't care J
J As if being a jerk's gonna
make you dummies happy &
[Groans]
J But my kingdom ain't
a commodity, Toronto 7
J It's a part of me &
J So sorry, you can't take
what isn't owned by me [
J; So take him away [
Boom.
[Cheers and applause]
I get it!
She owned him!
[Audience chanting "Phoebe"]
The winner is Son of Rap Bear!
[Chanting continues]
J I thought I was the Glob
of rap, rivaled by none
J But I'm more like bubble wrap
‘cause she squashed me for fun ;&
She's actually not bad.
Hey, honey!
You're actually not bad!
Pbht!
s Come along with me J
J And the butterflies and bees &
This party is so crazy!