[indistinct chatter]
[BMO] Did you know
there are more stars in the sky
than there are grains of sand in the sky?
It's true.
This is a rare giant asteroid
made entirely of heavy metal.
His name is Lars Darksaber.
I don't know any of these guys.
Whoa. Look at that big boy go!
That's gotta be the biggest comet | ever did-- |...
What the heck?
Let's forget we saw this.
Just another ineffable mystery
in a universe full of mysteries.
| wrote this song for my hat!
J Some people say that space is lonely &
J Silent, empty, sparkling, and immense J
J But wide-open spaces
Put smiles on cowboy faces &
J Even when they're stuck inside their tents &
J If I've got my mission to distract me &
J From friendly folks | had to leave back home J
J And | got my potatoes I
J More exciting than tornadoes J
J Potatoes J
J Buy my fresh potatoes &
J Terraforming Martian soil &
J Just put them in a pot to boil &
[yelling]
[suspenseful music playing]
Anybody get mashed?
Alert! Alert!
Time to make the doughnuts.
Boy, that meteoroid storm was scary.
There probably won't be scary cool things on Mars.
It will just be me, alone.
You'll always have me, BMO.
Yes, Football. But | meant new, interesting people.
[BMO] ; I've left my dream of grand adventure &
J For the quiet of my Martian tater farm &
Hi.
You can stretch!
Do you talk?
Oh. Well, you're round and green,
so I'm going to call you Olive.
After my favorite type of bread.
My name is BMO.
[giggles]
You like what you see, huh? You got good taste.
Huh? What are you doing?
[gasps] That was Mars!
We are going the wrong way!
Olive!
[yelling]
So trippy!
No, no, no! The stars are all jacked!
Olive! You interfered with my mission!
[growls]
Okay, | changed my mind!
You can interfere, Olive!
Please!
Fifteen minutes have elapsed.
Subject continues to struggle like a dumdum.
Its attempts are pitiful,
but | am sworn not to interfere.
[watch chiming]
[KS-2] Y4, report!
-1 found a weird bug bot on a rock!
-Hugo's not gonna care about that.
-Don't come back until you find something useful.
-Yes, ma'am.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Y4] This is great!
New entry.
Gray Elves and Shell people are squaring off
over a newly excavated site.
But which side will prevail?
Do the less dominant Shells fail to grasp
the importance of the Elves' unity mission?
Elves!
By the laws of the drift, we assert our claim
to this very sweet photon transmogger.
Heck, no, Cole. The transmogger belongs to Mr. M!
| have the receipt from you. You sold it, man.
That never happened!
And or | don't remember doing it.
We need that part! | challenge you to a drift duel.
One-on-one, Cole.
Last man standing gets the transmogger, aka me.
Oh, you think you're so tough
with your lava blaster.
But it's no match for my... [grunting]
stink sacs!
Such a rare and majestic sight.
[groans] No, thank you.
Ooh. Stink you right up.
On the count of five!
One...
two...
Now, Lenny Longlegs!
Hey! You're cheating!
This is it!
Ha-ha! The elves stand victorious--
It's ruined!
-No!
[all clamoring]
[laughing]
Whew. | thought that | was toast bread for sure.
But I'm completely uninjured.
Lucky, | didn't crash into anything important.
[all yell]
Huh. You weird babies. That's nothing to cry about.
It's just garbage trash.
Shelves!
Uh-- | mean, elves and Shells.
| propose a truce.
Let us put aside our conflict.
Good babies.
Let us join our forces.
And together, united, destroy that little robot!
What?
[all clamoring]
-Oh, no.
-Get him! After the robot!
But I'm so cute.
-[all] Huh?
-Get them!
[BMO chuckles] You're a rabbit!
[all yelling]
[Shafter] Get him!
[suspenseful music playing]
[yells]
They have terrible aim.
Keep both eyes open!
Robot, what the heck?
Cheese, I'm in trouble!
We'll go around!
[yells, then grunts]
[yells]
[groans] Why did | interfere?
Oh, stupid, stupid, stupid!
[all clamoring]
Tantrum babies.
[indistinct chatter]
[yells] Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Don't hate me!
[yells]
Move over. [grunting]
I'm stuck.
[horn honks]
[Shafter] Mr. M?
Well? Where's the transmogger?
Some little bot came out of nowhere and trashed it!
-But we'll track him down, sir.
-Forget him.
Go back and see if you can salvage the pieces.
Shouldn't we report this to Hugo?
Oh, no need to worry.
I'll take care of that personally.
[Y4] Field log, supplementary.
After, uh, thoughtful consideration,
I've scientifically decided
to take the alien robot in for further study.
Scientifically.
[gasps] So beautiful.
More Olives?
-Finally!
-Huh? Where are we?
[Y4] My secret lab.
[BMO] A secret lab?
[gasps] A secret lab!
It's just how I've always pictured it
for the last two minutes.
-There's gotta be an off switch somewhere.
-[yells] Don't look at my bottom!
It can simulate embarrassment.
Its maker must have been a weirdo.
I'm a self-made man. But who are you?
You can call me Y4. If you must.
No, that's boring. | will call you "Harmonica!"
| don't like that. It's funny though.
| have thought about calling myself something else.
Yeah, that's what | did.
| called myself BMO and the rest is history.
Really? 'Cause it looks
like it's just printed on your side.
Okay. Thank you. Pick a name now.
Okay. Hypothetically, how about...
Y57
| love it!
Y5 will take care of that.
| feel great about this new name.
Begin science log.
The alien robot entity's arm node seems
to be attached by a galaxy standard bolt.
There we go. Good as new.
Hello, BMO.
| guess | gotta knock you out now. For science!
[gasps] Oh.
He's yours?
BMO is his own big boy, thank you.
That old maintenance droid
seems to think you're important.
Olive? She's a no-good-for-nothing troublemaker.
Don't give me that puppy eye.
Serious?
What's the worst a little robot can do?
You know, you guys don't really have
to hang around.
[scoffs] That dang robot has
to come back to this ship eventually.
-Bob, do you have any threes?
-Uh, go fish.
-[gasps] My winning hand!
-1 got a bad feeling.
-[alarm wailing]
-[imitating alarm]
| hear that everywhere | go!
The atmosphere is getting sucked out
of the breach.
-We need to vacate this pod!
-No, | need my ship!
-Your ship is long gone!
-Lead the way, lady.
-[crowd clamoring]
-[Cole] | do not like this!
Come on, Y5! Toward the screaming!
-But that's not what | do!
-It's what | do. Sometimes.
[gasps] Hooray!
| can't stay mad at you, magic skateboard.
Come on, Y5!
[Y5 grunts]
Against all rational thought,
the intrepid researcher returns to the breach to--
Holy!
-[all clamoring]
-Help!
Look at those legs waggle!
Give me the blowtorch.
No. Mine!
-Oh, no!
-[both yelling]
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh.
Hey, wait...
He died as he lived. Sucking bigtime.
Crab guy!
You need to throw your shields all at once.
Uh, no. Why would 1?
Because BMO has a mission.
Shells!
Throw your shields
when the green box commands!
Now!
-Easy like potato pie.
-BMO, that was incredible.
You single-handedly saved everyone!
Olive!
Okay. | know what you're all thinking.
With my ship gone, | am trapped here.
So, yes, | will save your terrible land.
It does need saving, correct?
[power surging]
Yes.
Very well. Then | appoint myself your new sheriff.
Now show me where the trouble is!
Well, there's a lot of trouble in the drift.
Oof. Looks like I'm gonna need a deputy.
-l can't pay you.
-[watch chimes]
BMO, you've just been summoned
to meet some very influential citizens!
That's great! It will give me a chance
to check out my new stomping ground.
Great.
[BMO] Back home,
I'd only walk this far by accident.
[Y5] What was the name
of your home world again?
It is far from here.
A little blue and green planet called BMO World.
Never heard of it.
[sighs, then groans]
| need to make a pit stop.
[BMO] Oh, my goodness!
-[grunts] Hello, big cousin!
-Welcome, Diriftgoer.
It's just a Hugomat.
They're literally everywhere.
[BMO] Cool.
Your sports energy drink is ready.
Whew.
Energy drinks. The future is amazing.
Golly. Did you make all of this?
[Y5] No. | didn't personally
build an ancient space station.
[BMO] Whoa.
Buy my eggs! Buy my eggs!
Or | swear to glob I'll eat them myself!
[creature roars]
[BMO] Hey, check out this hothouse mess.
Nobody goes into jungle pod.
The life-forms have all mutated
into strange and dangerous things.
Come on.
| will play with you, strange things.
Dude, climb with your legs, not your arms.
[sighs] I'm getting tired!
-We're almost there, sweetie! Come on!
-What are you up to?
Uh, well, hello there, Sheriff BMO.
My brother and | are just climbing up
to the coin slot of this Hugomat
for some, uh, exercise.
We love fithess!
You two sound like some fishy four-flushers.
I've got my eye on you. Fishies.
I'm so scared.
[whistle quacking]
What's wrong, partner?
Hey, you're that new guy
who's all over the inter-pod streams.
Yes, | am famous.
Now tell us why you're crying, ugly man.
Well, it's one of my baby space lards.
It won't come back in from stargazing,
which is what | call grazing.
[BMO] They look so cold and scared!
[clicks tongue] BMO lasso!
[BMO grunting]
Man, | don't know what | would have done
if this tender, little baby had frozen
before | could eat it.
-What?!
-You want in on this? | make my own sauce.
-In my sauce gland.
-No!
| saved this lard.
You will repay me by caring for him
and keeping him safe forever.
Also, his name is Ricky!
[whimpers] Yes, sir!
Give me that!
This robot expends energy
in ways that yield it no benefit.
So weird.
[BMO] Deputy! Carry this! | don't have pockets.
-[mellow electronic music playing]
-[Y5] Mmm.
[all yelling]
It's another gravity outage!
[yells, then grunts]
-Blooey.
-This station is trash.
| got my work cut out for me.
Don't worry. Hugo's got a plan to fix things.
Who's Hugo?
[CGO] & Hey, baby, | hear the blues a-calling &
J Tossed salads and scrambled eggs &
Oh, my.
-1 think | know this song.
-Forget about that old robot!
We've got a mission, remember?
[CGO] Good night, Seattle! We love you!
[Y5] 01110000 01110011
01110011 0111001 01110111
01101111 01110010 01100100.
[BMO] Who are we going to see again? | forgot.
[gasps] Bunnies!
So many bunnies.
[chuckles] This one runs a hotel.
[Dad] If he's impressed with it,
our place on the unity pod is a lock.
-[KS-2] If Y4's data isn't flawed, which, you know--
-Um, I'm back. Mom?
Dad? Come look what | found!
Oh, my brain! A functioning service droid!
| haven't seen one of these in forever.
Mom, let me introduce you to...
Howdy, Mom! Nice to meet--
-There's bound to be useful U-pod parts in here.
-We should call Mr. M!
| did good, right?
These are some great parts.
-[rumbling]
-[alarm wailing]
Another failure?
It's in communications pod!
There's never been one this close before.
-What do we do?
-BMO likes alarms.
Y4, hush! The adults are talking.
--meet you! Huh?
BMO! There's a pod in danger!
Let's ride!
[BMO humming]
[KS-2] Y4!
What about Mr. M?
Don't worry. I'll watch over the, uh, parts!
[suspenseful music playing]
Come on, keep printing stuff
we can heist this thing with!
-We gotta bail!
-Wait!
It's our duty to evacuate the citizens!
-I'll save you, weird duck!
-I'm fine!
[gasps]
-Robots can't go in the water!
-Fine!
You are my arms and legs.
Now help me get everyone to safety!
[Bumbo] Excuse me.
We're too small and stupid to save ourselves.
Don't worry, Bumbos.
-[Bumbos] Uh-oh!
-Shush!
Hey! Use your big brain
and think of another way out of here!
Um... Oh!
There's another hatch over this way!
[Bumbos] Hop, hop, hop.
Through here!
Hop. Wait, I think | forgot something.
-Can | go back?
-Get out!
-Okay.
-[Darling & Sweetie] Sheriff!
-We messed up! Sheriff!
-We messed up!
You can swim, right?
-Yes, but badly. Ow!
-Giddyup!
[watch chimes]
-Hello?
-[KS-2] Y4, where are you?
Mr. M is on his way
to pick up that unit for dismemberment.
Heading back now! [yells]
-[9asps]
-What's going on?
[cracking noises]
-[yelling]
-Get me out of here!
Y5, chew through the glass
with your big, nasty teeth. Huh?
Yay, Olive!
-Swing! Swing now!
-[yells]
Jeez, careful much?
-You almost smashed our loot.
-Yeah, watch it next time.
Can't this rabbit swim any faster?
Onit.
-Did you just light a firework on my--?
-[all yelling]
| told you we would make it.
You sure are a worried wart, Olive.
Hey, flatfoot.
We found this thing inside the Hugomat.
We don't know what it does, so it's yours.
Ooh. That's smooth data.
[Y5 groans]
| can't believe | did that.
How did it feel?
-Kind of good, actually.
-Of course.
You're my deputy, after all!
Oh.
Right. Listen, BMO...
Yes, my true friend?
Uh, BMO, there's something | need to tell you.
Get in the car.
We should accept this ride from a stranger.
[sniffs]
This is a pretty sick ride, | gotta say.
[yelps]
[gasps] Is that...?
That's the answer to all the drift's problems.
Behold, the unity pod!
[BMO] Oh, | thought it was a popcorn maker.
Hugo's whipping up
some pretty sweet gadgets in there.
The raddest stuff your little bot eyes will ever see.
Oh, boy!
So, what if Hugo takes BMO apart? It--
It's for the greater good, right?
And I'm all about the greater good.
Greater good!
So many Hugomats.
Yep, yep. | actually came up with those myself.
Isn't that right, boss?
Huh? Uh, yes, the Hugomats were Mr. M's idea.
-Hugo.
-That boy loves flashy gadgets.
Me? I'm more of a pragmatist.
You must be KS-2's daughter.
-Nice to meet you!
-You too, also!
Is this the spicy tech | heard about?
You are so gray and bald!
Ha. Yeah, | am.
Oh, uh... [clears throat]
Noice.
Uh...
Mr. M, why don't you entertain our guests for a bit?
[clicks tongue] You're a kid.
Kids love dumb games, right?
-Um...
-Great!
[humming]
[groans] The greater good.
[ominous music playing]
What do you say we spice things up a bit?
If I win, | get those fancy grav boots.
What? No way!
Oh, come on!
If | lose, you get my fancy boots!
-[groans, then gasps]
-[drill whirring]
[Hugo] Dang. This robot is one of a kind.
But nothing here | can use.
[sighs]
Bummer. Well, maybe next time, KS-2's daughter.
Not so fast! The sheriff is here to help.
Tell me what you need.
Okay.
We've located the final component
for the unity pod, the genesis crystal.
Unfortunately, it lies
within the impenetrable jungle pod.
All our attempts to grab it have been hot "garbo."
So we're engineering our own.
How's it going, guys?
| think we finally cracked it, sir.
Permission to run a test?
[whistles]
[employee]
Cool, cool. Commencing test 325.
Huh?
That-- That shouldn't count!
-Tough beans, kid. A deal's a deal.
-No!
Sorry, Hugo. Please don't be mad.
You are not a very good scientist!
Oh. Reset for test 326.
No. | will get you the real junk!
-What--? Really?
-I'm your huckleberry.
[Mr. M] | gotta agree with the little bot, boss.
He's quick, plants won't eat him.
That's right. Plants hate me!
I'm smelling what you're baking. Smells good.
You know what? Let's try it. What the heck!
-Um, is that--?
-Saddle up, deputy!
We are going to find some treasure!
-Are you really sure about this?
-1 believe in us.
-I'll meet you out front.
-[clicks tongue]
-[both gasp]
-Mom! What, uh...?
There was some kind of accident
in the crystal lab.
-Apparently, the new prototype exploded again.
-[BMO] Oh, Mom.
Don't worry about that fake.
The BMO is headed to the jungle pod right now
to fetch the real one.
Why isn't BMO in a million pieces?
Uh, Hugo didn't need him?
Fantastic.
So we're back at square one.
Lady, stop talking. Come on, sidekick deputy!
What? You're following that little toy's orders?
-No! I'm just following Hugo's orders.
-Y4! Tell me the truth.
I'm sorry, Mom.
| was just humoring it at first.
So we could get to Hugo no fuss.
But | got carried away.
| know I'm not some deputy, all right?
It was just a dumb game.
You two coming or what?
Yeah. | am!
Because I'm the only one around here
that doesn't bite.
[BMO gasps, then groans]
Stop it, bad Olive!
-Olive! Let him go.
-1 don't need your help.
-BMO, I didn't mean to hurt your feelings!
-1 have no feelings!
Forget about her, champ.
Big cool guys like us don't need nobody else.
You make my feelings happy!
[KS-2] Y4, come on!
Yes, ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
Yep. This doesn't feel dangerous at all.
[laughing]
Aren't you coming?
Oh, uh, no.
It's real easy to get lost in J-pod.
So I'll be guiding you with this map.
-Oh, but couldn't we bring the map?
-Think fast!
We'll stay in touch through that walkie-talkie.
You'll only be alone in the, uh, literal sense.
BMO is never alone.
Right, Football?
Please. Don't bring me in there, BMO.
[Mr. M] Keep walking straight for 1400 frames.
Copy that.
One thousand two, one thousand and three,
one thousand four...
| don't like this place, BMO.
You are a delicate soul, Football.
But BMO will not be intimidated by nature! [yells]
So pretty.
[Football] BMO, I'm scared.
Oh, Football.
| know you're a scaredy cat,
but | have to complete my mission.
BMO, | think maybe
you're also scared of this mission.
Mm, no.
BMO, if you bonk this up and die,
| couldn't live with myself!
Oh, Football, | won't bonk up.
[yells] Whack! Whack!
[screams, then grunts]
Lucky, this hole was here.
Oh.
Not lucky, BMO.
You are in the dirt hole now.
Dirt hole!
-[screams]
-Run, BMO!
[yelps, then screams]
[suspenseful music playing]
Ew.
[gasps] You're my gross ticket out of here!
Crusty piece of crab!
Fly, Donkus!
Yay! You're my new best friend, Crusty!
Crusty!
[Mr. M] BMO? BMO!
There was a close call, Mr. M.
Mother drift got a taste of BMO.
-But I licked her right back.
-Whose mother?
[KS-2] Y4!
Could you bring me a J-clamp
from out by the--?
Where are your gravity boots?
-1 was playing cards with--
-You gambled?
What? No! It was Mr.--
Honestly, Y4! We'll talk about this later.
Ha!
Wait.
That's another Hugomat stick.
| wonder what's on these.
Wow, okay.
| didn't know you could do that.
Whoa.
-What the heck--?
-Hey, good job, little guy!
You'll be on top of the crystal in a mmm-bop.
[gasps]
It's mad indignant...
All of the Hugomat's are networked.
Mr. M has them identifying useful components
in each pod without anyone knowing.
That's so unethical.
[sighs]
| hope BMO is okay.
| don't feel good about this, BMO.
I'm going to take this crystal, Football.
I'm going to be a hero!
| don't need a deputy!
| don't need anybody!
[creatures screeching]
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
[Y5] Look, Olive! The genesis crystal is moving!
-BMO did it! Wait.
-[beeping]
Wait, wait, wait!
All of the failed pods are missing components.
By taking them, Mr. M is killing the drift.
We have to warn Hugo!
[screaming]
Blood!
Blood-erflies!
Mr. M! | got the crystal!
Throw it here, so you can run faster!
Yes!
Now catch me! [grunts]
Oh.
[whistles]
Very unfortunate.
Oh, BMO.
You tried, but you were never
the hero of the story | like to call "Life."
You were always just the cute sidekick.
Football!
Oh, no, don't cry, BMO.
You know I'm an empath.
-[rustling]
-Huh?
No, no! Football! Help!
BMO!
Oh.
This is probably bad, huh?
[chuckles] | think I'm dying. But that's okay.
BMO always bounces back.
[Purple BMO] Uh-uh. Not this time.
But I'm supposed to save the drift. That's my job.
Now your job is to be dead.
Oh, no.
BMO, you can get through this.
-Really?
-[Green BMO] Just kidding.
[Yellow BMO] You're not a hero.
[all] You're nothing but a little kid, BMO.
Oh...
No. BMO always bounces back.
Hugo! Hugo, Hugo, Hugo!
| never had to do this much exercise
before | ran into BMO-- [grunts]
I've been waiting for those J-clamps.
Mom, look what | grabbed from Mr. M's office!
He's behind all of it.
The drift collapse, the pod failures...
He's a no-good, rooting-tooting four-flusher!
| don't know if those are swear words,
but that sassy robot has messed you up.
[whistling]
What's up, bunnies?
Hopefully nothing slanderous.
| am so sorry, sir.
[gibbers]
No harm done.
Ha! I've already got all the proof
backed up right here!
Woof.
Mom!
-Where's BMO?!
-Bup, bup, bup.
The good news is that he got the genesis crystal.
The even better news is that little BMO died a hero.
-[both] Hurrah!
-No! | have to save him!
-No, Y4!
-[grunts]
My name is Y5.
BMO is my friend.
And | let him down
because | didn't wanna disappoint you.
-Y4!
-Ha! Kids, right?
Always calling out their deadbeat parents.
-What?
| can't do this alone.
Olive's gone. It's too far to the jungle pod.
I'm too slow!
Huh?
-[whistle quacks]
-[Ricky whistling]
Ricky! [yelps]
Stop. Stop! He's not here.
Listen, BMO's in trouble.
[grunting]
BMO! I'll get you out!
[shrieks]
[screams]
-Stop!
-Hey, back off!
We had to squeeze all these parts out
of a sealed pod.
That's my friend! [sobbing]
I'll sell you the parts.
Ain't this the bunny that saved us?
Please!
The drift is in danger
and BMOQO's the only one people will listen to!
[groans] My conscience gland.
We may know somebody who can help.
Ha-hal!
-Yo, CGO. You up?
-CGO?
| smell that goody scrap.
-| call dibs!
-Make us an offer.
What?! Cut it out!
| mean, ma'am, These two said
you could patch up the sheriff.
Hmm.
This is a moco-bot.
-You know this model?
-I'm practically a cousin.
-A janky, off-brand cousin.
-Yeah, but can you do it though?
Mmm. Probs.
[whoops]
With BMO's cred, we can convince Hugo
to stop Mr. M's schemes.
[CGO] Hugo?
| don't know what you've heard,
but Hugo is the worst.
What do you know?
Uh, duh.
He created me. We go way back.
To the real busted last days of Earth.
Hugo had a big brain and a rocket,
and led an exodus to the stars on the cheap.
[alarm beeps]
[all yelling]
The grays warned him about the dangers
of bio-hacking their alien style,
but Hugo gets his way.
[both] Ahem!
[all yelling]
Then we were saved by a orb.
The drift was already breaking down
when we got here.
But after Hugo set up shop...
Well, he just makes everything worse.
| got chucked into the trash.
That little service droid went back into space.
Poor thing. | wonder if she ever found
what she was looking for.
Hugo's a great guy,
as long as he thinks you're good for something.
Hey, quit leaking on my scrap!
Fingers crossed.
Maybe he needs to warm up a bit.
[whistles]
[power surging]
-[gurgling noise]
-Oop. Was that me?
Oow!
BMO, you have to wake up. | can't fix this.
I'm just a little kid!
[BMO] | said the same thing when | was dying.
[sobbing]
You saved me. You can save the drift.
But it's just too much.
Even when things look really, really stupid,
we still have to try.
[creatures clamoring]
Our suns all went out!
That's nothing.
All our crops are dying. It's gross.
-[watch chimes]
-Oof! Pod fails. They're spreading everywhere.
Y4 was right!
I've never heard you say those words.
Hugo!
You have to shut down the priming sequence!
We're on the verge of station-wide collapse!
Uh-- This is exactly the kind of problem
the unity pod team will be working to prevent.
-Hugocorp gold members, come on up here!
-[Ricky whistles]
[Y5 & BMO yelling]
Everyone, wait!
Hugo's up to no good!
-There's proof in this Hugomat!
-Oh.
Are you trying to get another drive?
Do you still have the data?
That smooth, smooth data.
Right here!
[crowd gasps]
[Y5] You're donking it all up, Hugo!
Do you deny it?
Nah, it's all true.
The unity pod was always designed
to save only myself and my loyal inner circle.
The rest of the drift is...
Well, it's unfortunate collateral damage,
in the grand scheme of things.
Besides, this all can't be on me.
Y'all thought the unity pod
sounded like a sweet deal,
as long as you thought
you were getting a piece of the pie.
But if anyone was offended by my actions,
| am truly, truly...
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
Well, time for me to get the heck out of here.
Uh-oh.
-There's no way to stop the activation process.
-The station's power will be sucked dry!
No! We were so close.
Why don't we just pull the plug?
If we remove the plug before it's powered up,
it won't turn on.
The robot is right.
The only way we can stop the U-pod from draining
all the juice from the drift is to eject it.
Yes! Brute force!
Everyone, we're going to need a lot of muscle!
| got muscle.
Lard muscle.
Go on! Put your bumps into it!
Swing those shields, Shells!
Use your handsome bodies!
Go, go, go!
Ice that pod!
[all] Go, go, go!
Well, here comes the rascal.
[sighs] We did it. [grunts]
No. We did it!
[all cheering]
Hold up, everyone!
| don't wanna be a downer, but we just launched
all of our best resources into space.
Is it too late to get on the U-pod?
[Y5] It's true.
Most of the station is dead now
and all communications are down.
We're going to have to manage
the remaining resources to survive.
We need to learn how to help each other.
| know it's hard, but we have to try.
Or we won't make it.
Ahem. I'll give it a shot.
Yeah!
-We can teach y'all how to steal and, uh...
-Forage for spare parts in the defunct pods.
We'll rebuild Hugo's old lab.
Maybe we can find some non-apocalyptic energy.
-[creature] Yeah.
-[KS-2] Y57
Can you forgive us?
We were so focused on getting our family
to a better place that we lost our way.
[KS-2] You're an amazing person, Y5.
Yep, it's time for this sheriff to move on.
Ricky! Let's ride! Yee-haw!
-[rustling]
-Huh?
Oh, it's you. Still disappointed in me?
[scoffs]
And | grabbed as many snacks as | wanted.
The end!
| should tell that story to Y5 next time | see her.
| bet she will be mayor by then. [giggles]
Huh?
We are here!
| will strap in.
Ricky, you beast!
Now go! Be free!
My name is Twinkletoes.
[BMO] Oh. Okay.
[chuckles] Who's that?
[upbeat music playing]